Chapter 1096: Each with Their Own Plans

"I just so happened to have overheard your conversation just now. You want to save your brothers, but you're worried that doing so will free the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity. What if I were to tell you that I have a way to save your brothers while also keeping the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity in check?" Qi Mozi asked.

"Is that true?" the white bone devil asked with a stunned expression, and the copper lion's expression also changed slightly upon hearing this.

"Of course. If the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity is freed, then I will also be doomed, so I certainly wouldn't dare to make a joke about something like this," Qi Mozi replied with a smile.

The copper lion remained silent as it turned to the white bone devil for a decision.

"How are you planning to keep the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity in check? Please elaborate," the white bone devil demanded.

A faint smile appeared on Qi Mozi's face as he communicated something through voice transmission, and the two devilish beings' expressions instantly changed slightly upon hearing what he had to say.

"I see. That definitely does sound like it could work," the white bone devil mused, and the copper lion also gave a contemplative nod.

"Rest assured, my life is on the line here as well, so I wouldn't devise an unsound plan," Qi Mozi assured with a smile.

"Alright, in that case, I agree to your proposal for a collaboration. However, I'm sure you must want something from us as well, right?" the white bone devil asked.

"You're just as direct and straightforward as ever, Fellow Daoist White Bone! Here's what I want from you: once I've helped you free all of your brothers, I want all of you to help me secure the Eon Divine Lamp and kill Han Li," Qi Mozi said with a smile that didn't reach his eyes.

"You want us to help you kill Han Li? That's not a problem at all! However, after we kill him, you have to give us all of his treasures," the copper lion immediately said.

"You can have all of the treasures and materials in his possession, but I want a cultivation art from him," Qi Mozi replied.

"That's fine," the copper lion said. "All I want are his immortal treasures, you can have everything else."

"What do you say, Fellow Daoist White Bone?" Qi Mozi asked.

"I can agree to this arrangement on behalf of my brothers, but Han Li is a very troublesome opponent to deal with, so my brothers and I will only be able to offer you some support from the side, while you'll have to be the one to directly confront and kill him," the white bone devil replied.

"That's fine with me," Qi Mozi replied without any hesitation, which came as a slight surprise to the white bone devil.

With the overall agreement made, the three of them briefly discussed some finer details before immediately setting off.

Shortly after their departure, three more figures appeared nearby amid a flash of azure light, and they were none other than Qu Lin, Lekima, and the azure-robed man.

"The situation is becoming more and more complicated," the azure-robed man mused.

"That Qi Mozi may be the chief warden of the Immortal Prison, but it sounds like he's here to claim the Eon Divine Lamp rather than to fortify the seals in the pagoda, so perhaps he could indirectly help our cause," Qu Lin mused.

"This is not necessarily a good thing for us. While his involvement increases the likelihood of the seals being broken, he's a Great Encompassment cultivator who's mastered the laws of time, so even the three of us won't be a match for him, let alone Fox 3 and the others. Our bonded soul tablets have been connected to the Eon Divine Lamp by Tai Sui, so if we try to approach the tablets, they'll immediately be attacked by the Flames of Eons.

“Hence, we can only rely on Fox 3 and the others to recover the tablets. If they fail and the tablets fall into Qi Mozi's hands, then we'll be reduced to slaves forced to do his bidding for the rest of eternity," the azure-robed man said with a grim expression.

Qu Lin and Lekima hadn't thought as far ahead as him, and only after hearing his analysis did they come to realize the severity of the problem.

"What do you think we should do then, Brother Liu? Should we try to intercept Qi Mozi now to buy Han Li and the others some time?" Qu Lin asked in an urgent manner.

"If he hadn't joined forces with the White Bone King and the Copper Lion King, perhaps we would've had decent chances of stalling him here, but it's too late now," the azure-robed man sighed, and the expressions of Qu Lin and Lekima immediately darkened slightly upon hearing this.

"Is there really no way out then?" Lekima asked.

"There are some solutions that we can turn to, but they'll be rather risky," the azure-robed man said as he flipped a hand over to produce a doll that was around a foot tall.

It was a doll of a woman in a long dress, and not only was there a gleam in its eyes, its body was also twisting vigorously from side to side, as if it were a living creature trying to struggle free from the azure-robed man's grasp.

Interestingly enough, the left half of the doll's body was a pure white color, while the right half was pitch-black.

The white half of its face bore a set of gentle and delicate facial features, while the black half of its face was twisted with intense, vindictive resentment, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

Lekima displayed no reaction to the doll, and it was clearly not the first time it had seen it, while Qu Lin was rather surprised at the sight of the doll.

"This is a puppet that I refined using some special materials. It's the only thing that will allow us to recover our bonded soul tablets," the azure-robed man said with a hint of mixed emotions in his eyes.

"What do you need me to do?" Qu Lin asked.

The azure-robed man swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a gray light barrier around the duo.

Moments later, the light barrier faded away, and the three of them departed.

......

Due to the severe restrictions on spiritual sense on this level, Han Li and the others didn't dare to travel too quickly.

Before long, the group had advanced onward for over two hours, and all of a sudden, they stopped in their tracks as they cast their eyes forward with excited looks on their faces.

Up ahead was a flat area, upon which stood a white jade plaza that was several dozen acres in size. The plaza was paved with rectangular slabs of exquisite jade, which were giving off wisps of white mist, forming a majestic cloud above the plaza that presented a breathtaking sight to behold.

Planted around the plaza was a series of tall trees of an unknown species, and the trees were entirely a translucent, white color, from their leaves to their trunks.

After examining the plaza to verify that there were no traps or restrictions, the group descended onto it, and ahead of them were three small staircases that led in different directions.

Beside each staircase stood a white jade plaque, upon which were inscribed the names of "Origin Fire Palace", "Heavenly Earth Hall", and "Divine Wood Tomb".

Upon seeing these three names, it immediately occurred to everyone that the three places had to have been the homes of the remaining three altars.

Everyone's eyes lit up slightly as they began to eagerly peer down the three staircases, but all of a sudden, Lei Yuce, Wen Zhong, and Su Anqian appeared in everyone's path.

"Two array cores have already been broken. If the remaining three are also broken, then the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity will be freed, and our lives will all be forfeit, so please proceed with the utmost caution!" Lei Yuce said in a solemn manner.

However, before he even had a chance to finish, Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 had already risen up into the air to fly toward the Heavenly Earth Hall, paying no heed to Lei Yuce's warning.

"Please stop now, fellow daoists. Otherwise, I'll have to stop you by force!" Lei Yuce declared as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing several dozen golden swords to intercept the two of them.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this.

There were around sixty to seventy of these swords, all of which were giving off extremely formidable metal law power fluctuations. The majority of these flying swords were eighth tier immortal treasures, and a few of them had even reached the seventh tier.

However, Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 displayed no intention of stopping, completely unfazed by the flying swords in their path.

A furious look appeared on Lei Yuce's face upon seeing this, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which the flying swords converged to form the Almighty Sword Array that he had previously unleashed once before.

However, before the sword array had a chance to completely take shape, a burst of radiant, dark red light erupted out of Wyrm 3's body before washing over the entire array.

The golden light emanating from the flying swords quickly faded away, and in the blink of an eye, the sword array was brought to the verge of collapse.

At the same time, the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber appeared in Fox 3's grasp, and he swung it through the air to unleash a crimson saber projection that completely outshone the entirety of heaven and earth around it.

Chapter 1097: Splitting Up

The white trees around the plaza rapidly wilted in the face of the crimson light released by the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, while the ground instantly turned black and completely devoid of life.

All of the spiritual qi in the white jade plaza was also sucked dry in the blink of an eye, following which all of the jade slabs exploded into countless stone shards.

In a mere instant, all of the vitality within several hundred kilometers of the plaza had been sucked dry.

Immediately thereafter, an earth-shattering boom rang out, and the Almighty Sword Array collapsed violently.

All of the flying swords were scattered in all directions, and around a dozen of them were snapped in half.

Lei Yuce shuddered violently as he stumbled back several steps before steadying himself, and an unnatural flush had appeared on his face.

All of the crimson light up above faded away, and at this point, Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 had already flown past Lei Yuce.

"You won't be able to stop us, Fellow Daoist Lei. We do not wish to fight you, so please stand down for your own good," Fox 3 declared, following which he and Wyrm 3 vanished down the staircase up ahead.

Right at this moment, Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan shot forth toward the Divine Wood Tomb as two streaks of blue light.

"Get back here!" Su Anqian yelled as she made a grabbing motion in their direction.

Countless balls of blue water that were roughly ten feet in diameter instantly appeared in the nearby area, and giant arcs of blue lightning were flashing over all of the balls of water.

The balls of water converged toward Lan Yuanzi's duo in unison at Su Anqian's behest, but Lan Yan remained completely unfazed as she summoned that blue pouch, which immediately released a burst of radiant, blue light.

All of the oncoming balls of water were instantly stopped in their tracks before flooding into the pouch, and in the blink of an eye, all of the balls of water had disappeared, as if they had been nothing more than an illusion.

An incredulous look appeared on Su Anqian's face upon seeing this, while Lan Yan's complexion had noticeably paled.

Even though she had only briefly used the blue pouch's power, over half of her immortal spiritual power had been expended.

Lan Yuanzi grabbed onto Lan Yan, and the two streaks of blue light combined into one, accelerating drastically in the process.

As a result, the two of them were able to quickly fly past Su Anqian before vanishing into the distance.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li shot forth toward the Origin Fire Palace as a streak of golden light.

Wen Zhong had been keeping a close eye on him this entire time, and he immediately attempted to intercept Han Li, summoning numerous streaks of formidable swordlight to oppose him.

However, Han Li was able to fly past Wen Zhong at an astonishing speed by channeling his Reversal True Axis ability, and before long, he had also vanished out of sight, leaving Wen Zhong to look on with a resigned expression.

Right at this moment, another streak of golden light shot forth through the air, and this time, it was Xiong Shan.

Wen Zhong was still staring after Han Li, so he was completely caught off guard by this, and by the time he reacted to what Xiong Shan was doing, he was already a step too late.

In the blink of an eye, Lei Yuce, Wen Zhong, and Su Anqian were the only ones remaining on the plaza.

"Those short-sighted fools! They'll be kicking themselves once the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity is freed!" Wen Zhong yelled in a furious voice.

"None of them are from the Golden Origin Immortal Region, so they don't know just how terrifying the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity is. On top of that, the immortal treasures in the array cores are all extremely powerful, so it's no wonder that they've been blinded by greed. What should we do now?" Su Anqian asked as she turned to Lei Yuce.

"At this point, it looks like we'll have no choice but to also split up and do our best to dissuade them from trying to claim the treasures in the array cores. If that doesn't work, then we'll have to repair the arrays as much as we can," Lei Yuce replied as he recovered his set of golden flying swords.

"It seems like that's all we can do at the moment. What exactly do you need us to do, Fellow Daoist Lei?" Su Anqian asked, and Wen Zhong also turned to him for further instructions.

"Please wait a moment," Lei Yuce said, then flipped a hand over to produce two sets of array tools, one red and one yellow, as well as two jade slips, and he distributed these items to Wen Zhong and Su Anqian.

"The arrays are very complex, and they won't be easy to repair, but as long as you follow the instructions laid out in the jade slips, you'll definitely be able to repair them. If you find yourself unable to, then contact me right away," Lei Yuce said as he handed a communication array plate to Su Anqian.

It was clear that he and Wen Zhong could contact each other through alternative means.

Wen Zhong and Su Anqian briefly inspected the contents of the jade slips, following which the former bade farewell to the other two and began flying toward the Origin Fire Palace.

"I'll be going as well then," Su Anqian said as she turned to depart.

"Celestial Maiden Su! The Lan siblings are quite powerful to begin with, and now that they've obtained that blue pouch, they'll be even more difficult to deal with, so make sure you don't directly confront them. If worse comes to worst, just let them claim the treasure. Make sure to prioritize your own safety above all else," Lei Yuce called out after her.

Su Anqian nodded in response, then set off toward the Divine Wood Tomb.

Lei Yuce stared after her all the way until she disappeared out of sight before making his way toward the Heavenly Earth Hall.

Shortly following their departure, three streaks of light flew onto the plaza, revealing Qi Mozi and the two devilish beings.

"Those people have already arrived here, and it seems like there was a brief conflict as well. It appears that they split up into three groups to go after the three array cores separately," the white bone devil remarked after inspecting the surrounding area with two beams of white light shooting out of its eyes.

"Very keen observations, Fellow Daoist White Bone," Qi Mozi praised with a smile.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Qi Mozi. Now that they've split up into three groups, we can easily eradicate any one group that we please. Should we strike now?" the white bone devil asked.

"There's no hurry. Those people are clearly determined to claim the treasures up ahead, so why not let them break the array cores to free your brothers?" Qi Mozi replied.

"That's true," the white bone devil agreed with a nod.

"Seeing as they've split up, let's also do the same. The three array cores all contain powerful treasures, and we certainly can't allow them to claim those treasures," Qi Mozi said.

The two devilish beings immediately nodded in response, and one of them flew toward the Heavenly Earth Hall, while the other set off for the Divine Wood Tomb.

A cold sneer appeared on Qi Mozi's face as he watched the two of them depart, following which he abruptly vanished from the spot.

......

After flying over the staircase for some time, Han Li's expression eased slightly as he noticed that he wasn't being pursued by Lei Yuce and the others.

He wasn't afraid of Lei Yuce's trio, but just as Fox 3 had said, he didn't want to engage any of them in battle, so if a conflict could be avoided, then that would naturally be ideal.

A faint gleam of excitement appeared in his eyes as he sped up a little more.

While he was averse to the idea of engaging Lei Yuce and the others in battle, he was determined to claim the treasure in the array core up ahead. As for the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity that Lei Yuce had mentioned, that wasn't a major concern for him.

Given his current powers, he was confident in his ability to ensure self-preservation as long he didn't have to directly face a Dao Ancestor.

He had already reaped some significant spoils in this pagoda, so if something were to go awry, then he could simply leave. Even if he couldn't find a way out, he would just have to run away for now.

Of course, he also wanted to secure the Eon Divine Lamp if possible, but it wasn't a huge priority, and he would only try to secure the treasure if he didn't have to take on excessive risk.

The staircase was unexpectedly long, and even after flying for fifteen minutes, there was still no end in sight.

Tendrils of white mist had begun to appear nearby, and even though the mist was harmless, it was very obstructive when it came to visibility.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he slowed down while scouring the nearby area with his spiritual sense.

After flying onward for a while longer, his eyes suddenly lit up as he abruptly accelerated and shot forward, arriving above another plaza, where there was no mist in the surrounding air.

The entire plaza was paved with black volcanic rock that was riddled with countless tiny holes that were releasing plumes of smoke incessantly.

Beyond the plaza was a fiery red palace that seemed to be giving off intense heat, causing the air around it to shimmer and warp in an indistinct fashion.

Even though there was a plaza that was thousands of feet wide between them, Han Li could still feel waves of scorching heat surging toward him from the palace.

Instead of immediately stepping onto the plaza, he scoured his gaze over it with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

However, he failed to detect anything amiss about the plaza, and he finally descended onto it after some careful inspection.

Chapter 1098: Solo Venture

As soon as he set foot onto the plaza, his brows immediately furrowed slightly. There was intense heat rising up from underfoot, as if he were stepping barefoot over hot coals.

However, after walking a few steps, he quickly acclimated himself to the sensation, and it didn't take long before he reached the end of the plaza.

He stepped onto the stone staircase leading up to the fiery red palace, then looked up to discover a plaque that read "Origin Fire Palace" in antiquated characters, above which was a copper tablet with a strange-looking flame symbol engraved onto it.

Han Li's expression suddenly changed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly sprang to the side as if he were trying to evade something.

Immediately thereafter, the flame symbol on the tablet flashed momentarily, and a beam of crimson fire that was around the same thickness as a finger shot out of the tablet toward Han Li's glabella.

Even though he had already anticipated this, he was still unable to evade in time, and the beam of fire struck his glabella, sending intense pain spearing into his head.

Despite his incredible physical constitution, the beam of fire was able to instantly burn through his skin and flesh to reveal the bone underneath.

Han Li felt as if his skull were about to melt, and the pain was utterly excruciating.

In this dire situation, a silver flame erupted out of his glabella to clash against the beam of crimson fire.

Han Li's pain was eased significantly with the emergence of the Essence Fire Raven, and his skin and flesh began to quickly heal.

The Essence Fire Raven let loose a loud cry as it rose up toward the copper tablet, devouring the beam of fire before pouncing onto the tablet itself.

Within mere seconds, the copper tablet was melted away, while the fiery power within was completely devoured by the Essence Fire Raven.

The Essence Fire Raven flew back to Han Li's side, then flew in a triumphant circle around him, as if it were looking for praise.

Han Li smiled as he made a beckoning motion to stow it away, following which he raised a hand to massage his own glabella.

The skin and flesh there had already healed, but there was still a small, red mark lingering there.

He swept his gaze over the palace gates, then pressed his hands against them, and they opened inward without much resistance.

After stepping into the palace, Han Li looked around to discover that the furnishings inside were very simple.

There were two rows of wooden shelves on either side of the palace, all of which were laden with lotus flower lamps that each had a pea-sized flame burning inside.

At the center of the palace was a round altar that was identical to the two previous ones, except this one was crimson in color, and as was the case with the previous altars, there were two items hovering above this one.

Hovering above the left side of the altar was a longan-sized white bead that was enshrouded in a layer of near-transparent white flames, giving off incredibly potent fire law power fluctuations.

As usual, there was a golden flame hovering beside it.

Han Li channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra before sweeping a sleeve through the air to release his time spirit domain upon seeing this, and time law power fluctuations began to emanate from his body as he made a beckoning motion toward the golden flame from afar.

The golden flame swayed slightly, as if it were tempted to fly to his side, but it then quickly fell still again.

A self-deprecating smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

It looks like I won't be able to get anything before I unravel the array on the altar.

With that in mind, he began to carefully examine the altar while walking in a circle around it.

Moments later, he stopped in his tracks with tightly furrowed brows as he fell into deep thought.

However, it didn't take long before he decided on a course of action, and he flipped a hand over to produce a stack of array flags and array plates, which he began setting up around the altar.

Before long, an octagonal array had taken shape around the altar.

After carefully examining the array to ensure that there was nothing missing, he made a hand seal to activate it.

A faint buzzing sound rang out as all of the array flags and array plates on the ground lit up, and a burst of radiant golden light erupted out of the octagonal array, forming a set of octagonal golden walls around the entire altar.

As soon as the array commenced operation, the altar instantly shuddered violently, and the near-transparent flame around the white bead hovering above it reared up before surging into the altar below.

Countless fiery runes instantly lit up over the altar, and a burst of crimson fire erupted toward Han Li in a frenzy from within.

However, the flame had only just arisen when it was contained by the golden walls. With nowhere to go, the flames erupted upward, blasting through the ceiling of the palace with a resounding boom.

Han Li was very pleased as he looked up at the giant hole that had appeared in the ceiling above.

The array that he had set up allowed him to contain the power of the altar, and once all of its power had been expended, he would be able to enter the array to secure the treasures inside much more safely.

However, right at this moment, a series of strange, fiery runes suddenly appeared over the walls on either side of the palace, giving off bursts of peculiar aura fluctuations.

The restriction in this place isn't on the altar!

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face at this realization, and before he had a chance to do anything, a pair of monstrous creatures with deer antlers on their ox-like heads and long, serpentine bodies slithered out of the walls.

As the two creatures burst out of the walls, they just so happened to fly over the rows of wooden shelves, and the flames in the lotus flower lamps on the shelves instantly rose up before converging toward them.

In the blink of an eye, the two monstrous creatures erupted into flames, and they opened their cavernous mouths as they swooped down upon Han Li like a pair of fiery serpents.

Han Li hurriedly sprang up into the air to evade the pair of fiery serpents, which immediately circled back around to form an encirclement around him with their bodies.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. Just as he had constructed a wall around the altar, the pair of fiery serpents had now formed a wall around him.

The two monstrous serpents glowered down Han Li as they each let loose a thunderous roar, and scorching, crimson flames surged out of their gaping mouths.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li was inundated by the crimson flames, and the ground beneath his feet quickly shattered into countless pieces, unable to stand the overwhelming heat.

Immediately thereafter, a loud thump rang out as all of the ground beneath Han Li's feet disintegrated into molten lava that rippled up and down like the surface of a disturbed lake.

Han Li was swaying unsteadily atop the undulating, molten lake, and he had conjured up a golden light barrier around himself as he fought to prevent himself from being swallowed up by the lava.

The entire surrounding area was completely filled with scorching fire, and he was struck by a sense of asphyxiation, as if he had been thrown into a pill refinement cauldron.

He gritted his teeth against the intense heat as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts before spinning around in circles while swinging his hands through the air over and over again, sweeping up gusts of fierce wind that forced back the surrounding flames.

As he spun faster and faster, the wind generated by his hands became stronger and stronger, but the gusts of wind didn't spread very far, only filling an area within several dozen feet around him.

Furthermore, the violent air currents were contained by the surrounding flames, forming a vacuum wall around Han Li.

Right at this moment, Han Li channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, and he sped up even further in his revolution while also swinging his hands through the air at a far higher frequency.

The pressure around Han Li continued to increase until it became too much to contain, at which point the vacuum wall exploded, sending countless palm projections sweeping through the air in all directions.

It was as if a tornado had suddenly risen up from the ground, and all of the molten lava was flung up into the air.

The crimson flames surging out of the mouths of the fiery serpents were sucked into the rising tornado, following which the serpents themselves were swept up as well, and their bodies were shattered into pieces by the flurry of palm projections, forming an enormous, fiery vortex.

Han Li flew out of the fiery vortex, then threw a punch to both his left and his right, destroying the walls on either side of the palace, as well as the wooden shelves that were laden with lotus flower lamps.

After that, he turned his attention to the altar, upon which he discovered that fire was still rising up from it, but at a far slower rate than before, clearly indicating that the array he had set up was serving its intended purpose.

Chapter 1099: Sneak Attack

There's no telling what could happen if I stay here for too long, so perhaps I should take a risk...

With that in mind, Han Li decided to immediately secure the white bead without waiting any longer.

He swept a sleeve through the air to release the Essence Fire Raven, and thanks to their spiritual connection, it knew exactly what he wanted without even requiring any verbal communication.

The Essence Fire Raven transformed into a cloak of silver flames that enveloped Han Li's entire, and Han Li noticed that his right arm was currently also enshrouded in a layer of flames, but as opposed to the silver flames all over the rest of his body, these were rainbow flames that had condensed the power of all of the Rainbow Fire Pill Sand that the Essence Fire Raven had devoured up to this point.

With the preparations completely, Han Li immediately sprang into the altar without any hesitation.

As soon as he entered the altar, the severely weakened crimson flames instantly reared up violently, becoming even more powerful than before.

Han Li felt a grueling, scorching sensation spread all over his entire body, and not only did it feel as if his skin, flesh, and blood had been set alight, even his bones, meridians, and tendons felt as if they were being roasted over an open flame.

At the same time, a vast sea of fire seemed to have appeared in his consciousness, subjecting his soul to immense torment.

As his consciousness wavered, he felt as if he could smell the acrid odor of burning meat in the air.

He immediately channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique and Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts to bolster his own spiritual sense and physical constitution, and only then was the excruciating state that he was in somewhat alleviated.

In a rare display of focus and restraint, the Essence Fire Raven fought back the urge to devour the crimson flames as it focused solely on keeping the lethal flames away from Han Li, but even so, he was still in a far from pleasant situation.

The white bead and the golden flame were both situated at the very center of the altar, which was also where the crimson flames were at their hottest. Standing on the edge of the altar was already almost unbearable for Han Li, yet he had to force his way deeper if he wanted to secure the treasures ahead.

He gritted his teeth tightly with an agonized look on his face, and plumes of white mist were rising up from his body as his perspiration instantly evaporated upon flowing out of his pores.

He trudged arduously through the flames while reaching a hand out as far as it would go, grabbing toward the white bead at the very center of the altar.

Right at this moment, a figure suddenly rushed into the palace, and to Han Li's dismay, he discovered that it was none other than Xiong Shan.

Upon catching sight of Han Li on the fiery altar, Xiong Shan hurriedly assured, "Don't mind me, Fellow Daoist Han, I just wanted to see what's in here. I won't do anything stupid."

"You can stay here and watch if you want, but make sure you don't do anything out of line," Han Li warned, then returned his attention to the task at hand.

If Xiong Shan dared to make any false moves, then he was confident that he would be able to kill him in a span of mere seconds.

Xiong Shan remained silent as he stood at the entrance of the palace, progressing no further beyond that point.

The crimson flames in the altar were excruciatingly hot, and even though Han Li's right arm was protected by the layer of rainbow flames, he was still in a state of intense agony.

As his hand gradually approached the white bead, a white shadow suddenly flashed over its surface, following a burst of white flames erupted out of the bead to form a white light barrier to oppose Han Li's outstretched hand.

Han Li's hand was kept at bay by the light barrier, unable to advance any further, but at the same time, the light barrier was also clinging to the rainbow flame over his right hand, preventing him from withdrawing his hand.

Right as he was planning to channel his true spirit bloodlines to force his way through the light barrier, Xiong Shan's expression suddenly changed drastically as he abruptly swept a sleeve through the air.

A silver badge flew out of his sleeve before racing over to the altar in the blink of an eye. The runes on its surface were glowing radiantly, and countless silver threads that gave off formidable spatial fluctuations erupted out of it.

Han Li could sense what was happening behind him, but his hand was still stuck to the white light barrier ahead, so he could only instruct the Essence Fire Raven to peel itself away from his body, thereby allowing him to struggle free from the white light barrier.

The surrounding crimson flames swarmed toward him from all directions, and he was only just barely able to leap out of the altar before he was burned alive.

However, he had only just made it out of the altar when he spotted a fiery red figure emerging from the flurry of silver threads, and the figure was plunging a hand directly toward Han Li's heart like a sharp blade.

The red figure was none other than Qi Mozi, and Han Li's expression changed drastically upon seeing this.

He hurriedly channeled his Reversal True Axis ability in an attempt to get away, but he was rooted to the spot by Qi Mozi's Time Severing Torch.

Qi Mozi plunged his hand forward, piercing it straight through Han Li's heart without any hesitation, following which he gave his own arm a vicious twist to completely pulverize Han Li's entire chest cavity.

After that, he grabbed onto Han Li's throat with his other hand as he cackled, "Not getting away this time, are you, you little bastard?"

Having been thwarted by Han Li multiple times in their previous battles, Qi Mozi had developed intense resentment toward him, so it was a very cathartic experience for him to have finally come out on top.

With his chest cavity completely destroyed, Han Li immediately fell limp, as if all of the strength had been sapped from his body, and the light in his eyes also quickly faded away.

A perplexed look appeared in Qi Mozi's eyes upon seeing this, and he was just about to smash open Han Li's head to capture the nascent soul inside when a layer of white light suddenly appeared over Han Li's body, and he abruptly transformed into a white puppet.

The puppet had been crafted out of some type of white beast bone, and there were many profound talismans adhered to its body. It was the substitution puppet that Han Li had obtained from Dongfang Bai.

A flash of recognition appeared in Qi Mozi's eyes at the sight of the puppet, but before he had a chance to do anything, Han Li suddenly appeared nearby, as did his five law treasures, all of which were working in tandem to contend against Qi Mozi's Time Severing Torch.

Immediately thereafter, a tiny, translucent sword shot out of Han Li's glabella before vanishing in a flash, only to reappear an instant later directly in front of Qi Mozi.

Before Qi Mozi had a chance to react, the Spiritual Sense Sword had already pierced into his glabella, and his consciousness was instantly riled up like a turbulent sea.

Han Li pounced on this opportunity as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts before throwing an almighty punch into Qi Mozi's chest, sending him flying into the altar as blood came spewing out of his mouth.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and before Xiong Shan had a chance to intervene, Qi Mozi had already fallen into the altar before being blasted high up into the air by the crimson flames inside.

At the same time, Han Li sprang into the altar once again, while the Essence Fire Raven descended upon him to drape him in a new cloak of silver flames.

Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and true spirit bloodlines in unison, instantly transforming into a devilish deity with three heads and six arms, and this time, he was able to force his hand through the white light barrier to grab onto the white bead within.

With the white bead taken from the altar, the array was unable to function any longer, and the crimson flames surging out of it rapidly abated.

A furious roar rang out from above as Qi Mozi swooped down upon Han Li with an enraged look on his face, but as soon as Han Li sprang back out of the altar, a silver lightning array instantly took shape around, and he was gone in the blink of an eye.

Qi Mozi slammed heavily down onto the ground, causing the entire altar to shudder violently as a series of huge cracks appeared over its surface.

He then slowly rose to his feet with his hands balled up into tight, enraged fists.

After a long hesitation, Xiong Shan approached him before cupping his fist in a respectful salute as he said in a careful manner, "Please forgive me for my inability to distinguish Han Li from that puppet of his."

Qi Mozi was silent for a long while, then heaved a forlorn sigh.

"You're not to blame. This type of substitution puppet is produced in the inner sect of the Hundred Creations Mountain, and it's difficult even for me to identify them. What a cunning bastard that Han Li is. He most likely already adopted these precautionary measures as soon as you began following him."

"I was too complacent. I've already lost my life to him once, yet it seems I haven't learned my lesson at all," Xiong Shan sighed.

"I don't know if it's just my imagination, but it feels like he's become a lot more powerful once again since our last encounter..." Qi Mozi mused, and it was unclear whether he was making this remark to himself, or if it was directed toward Xiong Shan.

He massaged his own throbbing glabella as he spoke, then turned his gaze to the golden flame that was still hovering above the altar, and only then did his expression ease slightly as he said, "At the very least, we'll have something to show for our efforts…”

Chapter 1100: Devouring the White Bead

Qi Mozi made a grabbing motion as he spoke, and time law powers surged out of his body to form a huge, golden hand that caught the golden flame in its grasp.

A pleased look appeared on Qi Mozi's face as he sensed the time law powers imbued within the golden flame, and he quickly stowed it away.

In the wake of the golden flame's departure, the altar finally completely collapsed, and a massive black hole appeared on the ground, with devilish qi surging out of it in a frenzy.

Dozens of sinister devilish creatures sprang out of the hole in rapid succession, howling in elation at their newfound freedom.

The devilish creatures were led by a devilish being that was over a hundred feet tall with a head resembling that of a mountain goat. Its body was almost identical to that of a human, and except it had a pair of white, fleshy wings on its back, and its arms were bright red and riddled with sharp bone spikes.

The crimson-armed devilish being's gaze fell upon Qi Mozi, and a hesitant look flashed through its eyes as it detected Qi Mozi's vast aura, but it didn't take long before its rational thinking was overwhelmed by the bloodlust and fury that had been brewing in its heart for countless years.

"Go and tear those two eyesores apart! They can serve as your first meal back in this world!" the crimson-armored devilish being yelled in a void so horrifically unpleasant to listen to that Xiong Shan couldn't help but wince.

All of the devilish creatures were ecstatic to hear this, and they threw themselves at Qi Mozi and Xiong Shan in a bloodthirsty frenzy.

Qi Mozi's brows furrowed slightly in disgust at the sight of the oncoming devilish creatures, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a wave of golden flames, which formed a fiery barrier before him.

The devilish creatures charging at the very forefront ran straight into the fiery barrier, and a string of anguished howls instantly rang out as their bodies rapidly withered away as if the life force were being sucked out of them.

Before long, they had disintegrated into ashes, while all of the other devilish creatures hurriedly retreated in alarm.

The crimson-armed devilish being was furious to see this, and it reached out with one hand, which swelled drastically to tens of thousands of feet in size within the span of mere seconds, descending from above like a dark cloud.

The eyes of all of the devilish creatures beneath the palm of its giant hand instantly turned bright red, and their auras also swelled drastically as they pounced at Qi Mozi's duo once again in a fearless manner.

Xiong Shan was standing behind Qi Mozi, so he was quite far away from the crimson hand, but even so, he could still feel his own heartbeat accelerating as a sense of irrepressible violence began to well up in his heart.

"Protect your consciousness!" Qi Mozi said, and his voice was like a rumbling thunderclap in Xiong Shan's mind, instantly snapping him back to his senses.

He hurriedly did as he was told, channeling his spiritual sense to protect his own consciousness, while Qi Mozi stepped forward before sweeping a sleeve upward, releasing a burst of golden light that struck the giant, crimson palm up above with a deafening boom.

The crimson-armed devilish being shuddered violently, and its hand shrank down rapidly as it was withdrawn to its side.

"I'm not your enemy, Blood Hand. Do not make your minions attack me again or I'll be forced to kill all of them," Qi Mozi yelled.

"You know who I am? Who are you?" the crimson-armed devilish being asked as a hint of wariness surfaced in its eyes.

"Take a look at this," Qi Mozi said as he casually tossed an item through the air.

The crimson-armed devilish being drew the item into its own grasp, revealing it to be a white bone badge that resembled a skeletal hand.

"This belongs to Brother White Bone!" the crimson-armed devilish being exclaimed.

"White Bone and Copper Lion have already been freed, and I've come here to free you," Qi Mozi declared.

"You still haven't answered my question yet. Who exactly are you?" the crimson-armed devilish being asked.

"If you were smart, then you wouldn't ask so many questions. Your brothers are waiting for you," Qi Mozi harrumphed coldly, then vanished from the spot with Xiong Shan.

The crimson-armed devilish being looked down at the bone badge in its hand as it fell into deep thought.

Moments later, it issued an order to all of its minions, and the horde of devilish creatures departed from the Origin Fire Palace.

Only after the entire plaza was completely deserted did Wen Zhong finally arrive on the scene, far too late to make any difference.

He swept his gaze over the severely ravaged Origin Fire Palace and the destroyed altar, then cursed under his breath as he began repairing the altar.

......

After leaving the Origin Fire Palace, Han Li continued to fly upward.

He flew for quite some time, and only after verifying that Qi Mozi and the others weren't pursuing him did he flip a hand over to summon the white bead.

The white flames around the bead had completely faded away, leaving it looking as unremarkable as a mortal trinket.

However, not only was Han Li not disappointed to see this, a hint of elation appeared in his eyes.

The average immortal treasure would release spiritual power and law powers even in a passive state.

In contrast, the white bead's spiritual power and law powers were completely subdued, and only when used would its true power be displayed.

This was a sign of an immortal treasure of an extremely high caliber, and at the moment, out of all of the immortal treasures currently in Han Li's possession, only the Heaven Controlling Vial and that golden plate obtained from the True Mantra Sect were on the same level.

Han Li opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light, which vanished into the white bead, and at the same time, he cast a rapid string of incantation seals into the bead as well.

A layer of white flames instantly appeared over the bead, giving off bursts of terrifying heat that caused all of the space within a radius of several hundred feet to tremble and warp incessantly.

The sweltering heat was intermingled with incredibly formidable fire law power fluctuations, in the no more than the blink of an eye, all of the white mist within a radius of dozens of kilometers had evaporated.

Prior to examining the bead's power, Han Li had already taken some precautionary measures to protect himself, conjuring up a layer of golden light around his own body to use his own time law powers to keep out the fire law powers.

With the fire law powers kept at bay, the heat released by the bead on its own wasn't enough to pose much of a threat to him, and he was able to ward off the heat by channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

Right at this moment, a clear cry rang out as the Essence Fire Raven flew out of his sleeve before perching itself on his shoulder, where it stared intently at the white bead with a greedy look in its eyes.

As soon as the Essence Fire Raven emerged, most of the heat in the air was instantly absorbed into its body.

Han Li continued to cast more incantation seals into the white bead, and before long, a slight spiritual connection had taken shape between him and the bead.

All of a sudden, a long tongue of white flames erupted out of the bead at his behest, then circled around a lone mountain nearby.

The mountain was roughly two thousand to three thousand feet tall with a diameter of around three hundred and fifty feet, and it was giving off immense metal-attribute spiritual power fluctuations.

The world's origin qi was incredibly abundant on the seventh level of the Eon Pagoda after countless years of accumulation, and as a result, many of the normal plants and rocks on the mountain had been converted into exceptional spirit materials over time.

In the case of this mountain, it had transformed into an enormous piece of metal-attribute ore, namely Profound Copper Stone, which wasn't of a sufficient caliber to be used for immortal treasure refinement, but was very hard and durable, so it was a popular material for constructing fortresses and secret chambers.

Upon making contact with the mountain, the tongue of white flames passed through silently without encountering any resistance, and the top half of the mountain immediately began sliding away to the side before tumbling down onto the mountain face below with a thunderous boom.

The cross-section of the severed part of the mountain was as smooth as a mirror, as if the mountain had been sliced into two by some type of divine weapon.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, but a look of disappointment then appeared on his face.

The white bead was even more powerful than he had anticipated, but he wasn't using any fire-attribute cultivation arts, nor had he cultivated any fire-attribute secret techniques, so he wouldn't be able to tap into anywhere near its full power.

Perched on Han Li's shoulder, the Essence Fire Raven let loose a loud cry to express its desire for the white bead.

"Don't worry, I can't use this bead to its full potential, so I'll definitely be giving it to you. However, it's an extremely powerful immortal treasure, so make sure to consume it with caution," Han Li warned, then tossed the white bead at the Essence Fire Raven.

The Essence Fire Raven was ecstatic to see this, and it eagerly swallowed the bead without any hesitation.

As soon as the bead entered its body, its silver flames instantly reared up significantly, and bursts of rainbow flames also surfaced over its body.

It hadn't been long since the Essence Fire Raven devoured those pieces of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand, so it hadn't been able to completely refine them yet.

At this moment, several types of flames were flashing over the Essence Fire Raven's body, clashing violently with one another amid bursts of thunderous rumbling, and parts of its body began to bulge erratically, as if it were about to explode.

Han Li hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air upon seeing this, releasing a burst of golden light to enshroud the Essence Fire Raven while also releasing his spiritual sense to inspect its internal condition.

Chapter 1101: Awakening Fire Law Powers

The Essence Fire Raven turned to Han Li with a pained look in its eyes, but its pain was clearly far outweighed by elation.

All of a sudden, a white flame appeared over its body, sweeping rapidly over it from head to tail.

All of the rainbow flames on its body were instantly eradicated, and the power of the Rainbow Fire Pill Sand was completely refined and integrated into its body.

Not only that, but all of its fiery power had also been purified, eradicating all of the impurities to leave only the most essential power behind.

The bulges all over the Essence Fire Raven's body had also disappeared, and it abruptly shrank down to roughly half its original size, but its aura had swelled drastically, and there was even a hint of fire law power fluctuations emanating from its body.

This was the same as the fire law power fluctuations from the white bead. Instead, it was reflective of fire law powers of a higher level.

Over the years, the Essence Fire Raven had been steadily becoming more and more powerful as it devoured more and more flames, but up to this point, no fire law powers had arisen within it. However, the power of the white bead seemed to have purified and refined its power, giving rise to fire law powers of an extremely high caliber.

The Essence Fire Raven let loose an elated cry as it spread its wings and soared through the air, transforming into a giant silver fire raven that was over a thousand feet in size.

In its current form, the Essence Fire Raven's body had become far sleeker and more streamlined than before, and a fiery crown had appeared on its head, while nine long, fiery feathers had grown from its tail, giving it an air of regal majesty.

Bursts of terrifying fiery power that weren't inferior to those emanating from the white bead earlier were surging out of the giant fire raven's body, causing the nearby space to tremble violently.

The Essence Fire Raven continued to circle around in the air, and its cries grew louder and louder as its eyes glowed with excitement.

All of a sudden, streaks of silver flames erupted out of its wings like shooting stars before raining down upon the mountain face below.

The silver flames were able to burrow their way deep into the mountain face with ease, leaving unfathomably deep holes in their wake.

A string of resounding explosions rang out as the silver flames exploded violently before connecting together to form a sea of silver fire that was dozens of kilometers in size.

The sea of silver flames was giving off terrifying heat that rapidly melted away everything within and around it, and an enormous crater was melted into the mountain face in the blink of an eye.

However, the mountain was so enormous that this crater was insignificantly tiny in comparison, and the mountain itself wasn't moved in the slightest.

A look of excitement flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this. The Essence Fire Raven had become even more powerful than he had anticipated.

However, his brows then furrowed slightly with concern as he realized that they still weren't very far away from the Origin Fire Palace, so causing such a massive commotion could draw the attention of Qi Mozi.

With that in mind, he immediately instructed the Essence Fire Raven to stop what it was doig through their spiritual connection.

However, the Essence Fire Raven seemed to have been too absorbed in its play to heed his instructions, and it completely ignored him as it let loose another loud cry, opening its mouth to release the white bead in the process.

The white bead swelled rapidly in size from only around three inches in diameter to roughly thirty thousand feet in the blink of an eye, and there were incredibly sweltering white flames burning over its surface, giving it the appearance of a blinding white sun hanging in the sky.

Everything within a radius of hundreds of kilometers was illuminated a pure white color, and the air temperature also swelled to a terrifying degree as the mountain face began to rapidly melt away once again.

A devastating aura of destruction was emanating from the giant white bead, and all of the space within a radius of dozens of kilometers had become warped and blurry, following which countless spatial rifts of different sizes appeared in the surrounding area.

Han Li was just about to fly through the air to intercept the Essence Fire Raven when a series of spatial rifts appeared in his path.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him at his behest before releasing countless waves of golden ripples that instantly spread over the entire area within a radius of around a thousand feet.

All of the spatial rifts that were caught within the golden ripples instantly fell still, but they were filled with such astonishing power that the golden ripples were trembling violently, as if they were struggling to contain the spatial rifts.

Han Li hurriedly injected more immortal spiritual power into his Mantra Treasured Axis to stabilize the golden ripples before turning to the Essence Fire Raven and the giant, white bead with a stunned expression.

The tongue of white flames that he had unleashed with the bead earlier couldn't even hold a candle to the power that the bead was currently putting on display.

Not only that, but the power unleashed by Xiong Shan and Lan Yan using the Primordial Ancient Sword and the blue pouch, respectively, also paled in comparison to that of the white bead.

After flying out of the Essence Fire Raven's beak, the giant, white bead came crashing heavily down onto the mountain face below with an earth-shattering boom.

This time, the entire mountain began to tremble amid a burst of dull rumbling, and countless loose rocks came falling like rain.

The white bead had embedded itself into the mountain face, and it was rapidly burrowing its way deeper and deeper into the mountain as the white flames over its surface melted through the rocky material, seemingly determined to burn a hole all the way through to the other side.

However, right at this moment, a burst of radiant, golden light appeared, encompassing the white bead within it.

The golden light contained tremendous time law powers that instantly slowed down the speed of the white bead's advance to a crawl, while Han Li appeared near the mountain face before making a grabbing motion with one hand.

Over two hundred time law threads flew out of his sleeve, then intertwined with one another to form an enormous, golden hand that reached deep into the mountain face to grab onto the giant, white bead.

The flames on the surface of the white bead were scorching the golden hand with all their might, but the latter refused to budge.

"Alright, that's enough!" Han Li said in a stern voice as he gave the Essence Fire Raven a cold glare.

The excitement in the Essence Fire Raven's eyes quickly faded upon seeing this, and a timid look appeared on its face as it rapidly shrank down into its silver, child-like form.

The white bead also shrank down to its original size in the blink of an eye before flying back to the fiery, silver figure's side, while the surrounding sea of silver flames was snuffed out in a flash.

The silver flames on the fiery, silver figure's body had dimmed significantly, and the hint of fire law powers that had arisen in its body had been significantly depleted, to the point that it was barely even detectable anymore.

However, this didn't seem to bother the silver figure, and it flew over to Han Li's side while hanging its head like a child that had been caught doing something wrong.

Han Li couldn't help but be amused at the sight of the silver figure's sheepish display, and he gave it a pat on the head as he said, "It's fine, just don't be so naughty next time."

The silver figure was ecstatic to have been forgiven, and it sat down onto Han Li's shoulder, then opened its mouth to swallow the white bead.

As a result, the silver flames on its body began to burn a little brighter, and wisps of fire-attribute spiritual qi were also surging into its body from the surrounding space.

A surprised look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

In the past, the Essence Fire Raven was only able to replenish its expended spiritual qi by devouring other flames, but with the assistance of the white bead, it was now able to directly absorb the fire-attribute spiritual qi in the environment.

The white bead was already an extremely formidable offensive weapon, but it seemed that it was also able to serve some other purposes as well.

Even Han Li wasn't confident that he could directly withstand the devastating attack unleashed by the white bead just now, and he wouldn't have been able to capture it so easily if it wasn't for the fact that the bead had already expended most of its power burrowing its way into the mountain.

By Han Li's estimates, the Essence Fire Raven should've been able to unleash that attack with the white bead twice in succession.

With this additional trump card up his sleeve, Han Li fancied his chances against Qi Mozi a little more than before.

He took a deep breath to suppress the excitement in his heart, then continued flying up the mountain as a streak of golden light.

At the moment, the seventh level of the Eon Pagoda was a very perilous place. There were many freed devilish creatures on the level that could pop up anywhere, and in the wake of the massive commotion that the Essence Fire Raven had just caused, he had to leave this place right away.

After the white bead was swallowed by the silver figure, tendrils of white mist began to reappear nearby, and before long, Han Li had vanished into the mist.

Mere minutes following his departure, two streaks of light flew onto the scene from below, then stopped in their tracks where Han Li and the Essence Fire Raven had been not long ago to reveal Qi Mozi and Xiong Shan.

Qi Mozi observed the severely ravaged mountain face for a moment, then looked up at the sky with a contemplative expression.

"It looks like a fierce battle must've taken place here," Xiong Shan remarked as he inspected his surroundings.

"I can sense some residual time law power fluctuations in the air, so one of the combatants was most likely Han Li. Whoever his opponent was, they've mastered the laws of fire and were fighting him using that Heavenly Li Fire Bead," Qi Mozi mused.

Chapter 1102: Mystery of the Divine Lamp

"Didn't Han Li obtain the Heavenly Li Fire Bead? Could it be that someone took it from him?" Xiong Shan asked with a puzzled expression.

Qi Mozi offered no response as he flipped a hand over to summon a palm-sized golden mirror, which released a burst of golden ripples that quickly swept through the surrounding area in a radius of several dozen kilometers before returning to the mirror.

Three bursts of light then appeared over the mirror's surface, one golden, one white, and one red.

The golden light was giving off bursts of time law power fluctuations, while the white and red light were both emanating fire law power fluctuations.

In particular, even though the red light was far smaller than the white light, the law power fluctuations that it was giving off were far more formidable than those released by the white light.

"What are these red fire law power fluctuations? They must be extremely formidable to be able to dominate the fire law powers of the Heavenly Li Fire Bead!" Xiong Shan remarked.

"What you're seeing is a wisp of essential fire law powers, so of course it far surpasses the fire law powers of the Heavenly Li Fire Bead," Qi Mozi explained.

"I see," Xiong Shan mused with a stunned expression. "But who could've left these law power fluctuations behind? I don't recall seeing anyone cultivating the laws of fire among the people who entered the Eon Pagoda."

Qi Mozi's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this.

Among all of the laws of heaven and earth, the three paramount laws reigned supreme at the top, but essential laws were nothing to scoff at, and they ranked below only the three paramount laws in power.

Qi Mozi was familiar with everyone who had entered the Eon Pagoda, and he knew that there were none among them cultivating the laws of fire. With that in mind, he couldn't help but wonder if someone else had snuck into the Eon Pagoda without his knowledge.

"There's no point in thinking too much about it, we'll find out once we catch up to them," Qi Mozi said, and Xiong Shan naturally raised no objections to this.

With that, the two of them departed as two streaks of golden light.

......

Meanwhile, Han Li was continuing to make his way up the mountain with the fiery, silver figure perched on his shoulder.

The higher up they went, the thicker the surrounding white mist became, and it had almost taken on a substantial form, clinging to the streak of light around Han Li to drastically slow him down.

As the mist became denser, the resistance continued to increase, and before long, Han Li's speed had been reduced to only 10% of its peak.

All of a sudden, Han Li's expression changed slightly as he stopped in his tracks, then peered into the dense, white mist up ahead with a peculiar look on his face.

The silver figure turned to Han Li with an inquisitive expression, as if to ask why he had suddenly stopped, but he offered no explanation as he continued to look straight ahead.

He could clearly sense a burst of incredibly formidable time law power fluctuations up ahead, and it was clearer and more pronounced than ever.

He could tell that the golden flames on the altars shared the same origins as the source of the time law power fluctuations up ahead, and if he wasn't mistaken, then what was up ahead was most likely the Eon Divine Lamp.

Earlier, Han Li had questioned Lei Yuce in detail about the seal on the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, and he had learned that the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was trapped in a primary array where the Eon Divine Lamp was also situated, while the five array cores only acted as subsidiary structures to bolster this primary array.

Now that he was able to detect what he strongly suspected to be the Eon Divine Lamp, the place where the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was sealed was most likely just up ahead.

Han Li wasn't as fearful of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity as Lei Yuce's trio, but there was a very good chance that this was a devilish deity on par in power with a Dao Ancestor, so he naturally didn't want to have to face them in battle.

During his time in the Eon Pagoda, he had obtained three Fire Age Firefly hives that had significantly increased the number of time law threads in his possession, and he had also just obtained that white bead, and all of that already amounted to a massive haul.

If he were to continue onward, then he would have to venture into the place where the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was sealed, taking on far more risk in the process.

Right at this moment, a resounding thump rang out from somewhere, causing the nearby mist to ripple slightly.

Han Li immediately began inspecting his surroundings with a wary expression, while the white bead flew out of the silver figure's body on its own.

At this moment, the bead was glowing brightly while trembling and buzzing incessantly, seemingly resonating with something.

However, this phenomenon only lasted a few seconds before the bead quickly reverted back to its original state, and the silver figure hurriedly gulped it back down, then clasped its hands firmly against its little belly for fear that the bead would fly away again.

Could it be that the other two array cores have also been broken? Han Li wondered to himself as he patted the silver figure's head in a reassuring gesture.

The five array cores were all interconnected with one another, and the white bead had been presiding over one of the cores, so it most likely had some ties with the other array cores.

After pondering the matter for a moment longer, Han Li rid himself of that train of thought as he cast his gaze forward.

Following this brief delay, he had made up his mind to continue onward, even though doing so would entail taking on additional risk.

Having already made it to this point, it would be a huge waste to turn back now, and he was also very interested in seeing the Eon Divine Lamp for himself.

Furthermore, he had already agreed to join forces with Fox 3 and the others earlier, and leaving on his own now would be going back on their agreement.

With that in mind, Han Li didn't hesitate any longer, conjuring up a giant, golden sword projection around his own body as he continued to fly onward.

There were arcs of golden lightning flashing over the sword projection, and it was giving off tremendous sword qi as it sliced through the mist up ahead, drastically enhancing Han Li's speed.

However, after advancing for a while longer, the surrounding mist became even denser and more resilient, and before long, he was forced to slow down once again.

A displeased pout appeared on the silver figure's face upon seeing this, and it sprang up from Han Li's shoulder before opening its mouth to release the white bead, which fused into the golden sword projection around him.

Wisps of white flames surged out of the bead to bolster the sword projection, allowing it to slice through the mist up ahead with ease to drastically elevate Han Li's speed once again.

However, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he said, "We don't know what's up ahead, so you should conserve your energy."

In response, the silver figure gave him a nonchalant smile, as if to tell him that this amount of energy expenditure was more than manageable.

Han Li took a moment to inspect the silver figure's internal condition upon seeing this, and to his surprise and elation, the energy expenditure incurred from its usage of the white bead really was quite insignificant.

In light of this, he hurriedly flew onward at full speed, and it didn't take long before the white mist ahead suddenly began to thin out.

At the same time, he was beginning to be able to make out the outline of the entire mountain, and it seemed that he had finally reached the mountain summit.

This was naturally a very encouraging sign, and he sped up even further.

However, in the next instant, a resounding boom rang out as he crashed into what seemed to have been an invisible wall, and the golden sword projection around him was instantly shattered, while he was knocked back through the air.

Fortunately, he remained unscathed thanks to his tremendous physical constitution.

The white bead within the sword projection was also knocked back by the impact, and the silver figure hurriedly devoured it again.

What just happened?

After taking a moment to steady himself, Han Li cast his gaze forward, upon which he spotted a barely visible white light barrier in the mist up ahead.

The light barrier was semi-transparent, and there seemed to be no end to it in sight.

Han Li was unable to gauge its full scale with his spiritual sense, and it stood before him like an all-encompassing barrier.

Deep within the white light barrier, he could see a ball of radiant, golden light that was giving off bursts of time law power fluctuations.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up slightly upon seeing this, and he flew over to the white light barrier before trying to peer into the golden light beyond, but he was unable to make out anything.

However, he was certain that that was where the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was sealed.

He turned his attention back to the white light barrier before him, then pressed a hand against it.

The light barrier was slightly soft to the touch, but at the same time, he could tell that it was extremely resilient.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as all of his profound acupoints lit up, following which he threw an almighty punch into the light barrier.

A resounding boom rang out as his fist sank deep into the light barrier, causing it to ripple violently, and the nearby space also began to rumble and quiver.

However, the white light barrier didn't display any signs of weakness, and it released a burst of tremendous, repulsive force that sent him flying back through the air for two to three thousand feet before he managed to arrest his own momentum.

The repulsive force was so strong that his internal organs had been given a massive jolt, and even with his immense physical constitution, his complexion had paled noticeably, and he was forced to take a moment to steady himself.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, transforming into an enormous devilish deity with three heads and six arms in the blink of an eye.

The three heads were those of the Giant Mountain Ape, the True Dragon, and the Kun Peng, and an enormous aura erupted out of the devilish deity's body, causing the nearby space to tremble violently.

The golden light beyond the white light barrier suddenly rippled slightly, only to immediately revert back to its original state.

Han Li was too busy focusing on the light barrier to notice this fleeting change in the golden light beyond it, and he let loose a thunderous roar as he rammed his six fists into the white light barrier.

His fists sank deep into the light barrier, causing it to ripple and shudder far more violently than before.

However, even so, the light barrier was still able to hold itself together, and a burst of tremendous, flexible power surged forth to slowly nullify the unfathomable power in Han Li's fists.

Chapter 1103: Heavenly Damnation Lightning

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and in the next instant, the white light barrier sprang back to its original state, sending him flying back through the air once again.

The giant devilish deity stumbled back close to twenty steps before finally managing to steady itself, and it cast a flabbergasted gaze toward the white light barrier.

In terms of offensive power, the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts ranked at the very top out of all of Han Li's cultivation arts, yet it still wasn't enough to break the light barrier.

Of course, Han Li had some other things that he could try, but judging from the current state of affairs, it was most likely the case that none of his cultivation arts or secret techniques would be able to change the outcome.

All of a sudden, the silver figure on his shoulder let loose a loud cry as it took on its fire raven form again.

Right as the Essence Fire Raven was about to launch itself forward, the nearby mist rippled violently once again with a deep, thunderous rumble.

The white bead flew out of the Essence Fire Raven's body on its own for a second time, and Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this.

Has the final array core been broken as well?

Han Li had already anticipated that this would happen, but not this quickly, and in the wake of this turn of events, he didn't have much time left.

If he couldn't clear the obstruction up ahead in a short time, then things could take a messy turn very soon.

With that in mind, Han Li turned his gaze back to the white light barrier, but to his astonishment, the light barrier suddenly began to flash erratically, and just a few moments later, it disintegrated with a dull thump, dissipating into countless specks of white light that quickly faded away.

Han Li was scarcely able to believe his own eyes.

Could it be that this light barrier is designed to automatically fade away once all five array cores have been broken?

......

At this moment, Lei Yuce and Su Anqian were standing together behind a large rock on a short mountain.

The two of them were enshrouded within a white light barrier with misty, white light flashing over its surface, giving it a rather ethereal appearance.

There was a green palace several dozen kilometers away from the mountain, but it had already collapsed, and at this moment, Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan were flying out of the rubble.

The streaks of light that they were situated in combined as one, drastically enhancing their speed, and they vanished into the distance in a flash.

Immediately after them came a series of black figures that were giving off tremendous devilish qi, and these devilish beings also quickly flew away into the distance amid a chorus of elated cheers.

Lei Yuce made a hand seal, and the white light barrier around him and Su Anqian faded away, transforming into a white ring that flew up his sleeve.

"Lei Yuce, why did you insist that the two of us stand by and do nothing? We would've had good chances of saving this array core had we tried!" Su Anqian said in an accusatory voice.

"It would've been a futile effort. Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan are no less powerful to begin with, and with that blue pouch now in their possession, there's no way we would've been able to stop them. If I were here on my own, I would've perhaps taken a risk, but I can't afford to take any risks with you by my side," Lei Yuce sighed.

Su Anqian fell silent as a hint of mixed emotions flashed through her eyes.

"All five of the array cores have been broken now. What do we do?" she asked in a concerned manner after a brief silence.

"Don't worry, the situation is still under control. Let's go and repair the array for now," Lei Yuce said as he set off toward the wreckage of the green palace, followed closely by Su Anqian.

......

At the summit of the giant mountain, Han Li flew out of the sea of white mist, and he was greeted by the sight of a sapphire-blue sky and sparse white clouds.

The golden light that he had seen through the white light barrier was hovering in mid-air above the mountain summit, and within it was a massive palace that was extremely imposing and majestic.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly as he flew toward the palace, but all of a sudden, the sky began to churn violently as a white cloud with countless bursts of white light flowing through it appeared out of thin air.

All of the world's origin qi in the nearby area surged toward the cloud in a frenzy, causing it to swell rapidly in size, taking up virtually the entire sky in the blink of an eye.

Bursts of thunderous rumbling could be heard within the cloud, accompanied by flashes of white lightning that gave off a burst of tremendous pressure.

Fierce gusts of wind began to sweep over the entire mountain beneath the cloud, violently stirring up the sea of mist while felling trees and disturbing rocks.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he was just about to take a closer look at the sky above when a loud commotion suddenly rang out in the white cloud.

Immediately thereafter, the white lightning within the cloud suddenly became a lot more violent, and thick bolts of lightning came crashing down upon all parts of the giant mountain.

These bolts of white lightning were so bright that all onlookers were forced to avert their eyes, and they contained such tremendous lightning law powers that even Han Li couldn't help but feel alarmed and unsettled.

The lightning law powers within these bolts of lightning were very similar to those of the Heavenly Damnation Lightning that Han Li had seen before, except these bolts of lightning were countless times more powerful.

Han Li was just about to revert back to his human form and rush back in retreat, but it was already too late, and around a dozen thick bolts of lightning came crashing down upon him at once.

It was as if the very heavens were aiming to strike him down, and the will of the heavens was suppressing his will to resist.

Han Li's willpower was suppressed by this aura of heavenly damnation, but in the next instant, his enormous spiritual sense shrugged off these suppressive effects.

However, at this point, the bolts of white lightning were already upon him, and he hurriedly plummeted out of the sky as quickly as he could, attempting to buy himself some time.

At the same time, he launched his fists up at the sky, releasing countless fist projections that hurtled toward the bolts of white lightning crashing down from above.

Every single one of those fist projections was giving off astonishing devilish qi and immense power, leaving trails of visible marks in the space in their wake. The surrounding space warped and trembled violently as countless spatial rifts emerged, but as the fist projections collided with the bolts of lightning, there was no intense explosion or thunderous commotion.

Instead, as soon as the fist projections came into contact with the white lightning, the former instantly melted away into plumes of black smoke.

The bolts of white lightning were able to pierce through the black fist projections with ease before striking the body of the flabbergasted devilish deity below.

Around a dozen massive wounds that were deep enough to expose bone were instantly inflicted upon the devilish deity, and its enormous body crashed down heavily onto a mountain below, creating a massive crater while sending countless rocks flying through the air in all directions.

Bolts of white lightning roamed over the devilish deity's body, instantly eradicating all of the devilish qi that it came into contact with.

With so much devilish qi eradicated in the blink of an eye, Han Li was unable to maintain his devilish deity form and quickly reverted back to his human form.

His face had turned extremely pale, and there his body was riddled with horrific wounds that were bleeding profusely, but thankfully, he was able to reposition himself slightly at the last second to avoid sustaining any injuries to his vital regions.

Hence, despite how horrific the injuries appeared, none of them were actually all that severe.

Han Li hurriedly took a crimson pill, and bursts of crimson light flashed over his wounds as they began to rapidly heal at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

After that round of lightning strikes, the white cloud above and the arcs of lightning within it had thinned out somewhat, but before Han Li even had a chance to catch his breath, another bout of lightning came crashing down.

This time, there were far fewer bolts of lightning than during the previous round of lighting strikes, but the bolts of lightning were no less formidable than before.

At this point, Han Li already knew what to expect, so he was far more calm and composed as arcs of golden lightning appeared over his body, and at the same time, he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which released countless wave of golden ripples to envelop his entire body as well.

He had only been wounded by the first round of lightning strikes as he had been caught off guard. Now that he was fully prepared, he was confident in his own ability to ward off the lightning strikes, even if this bout of lightning were twice as powerful as the previous one.

However, the second round of lightning strikes didn't fall upon Han Li. Instead, they fell upon other parts of the giant mountain, and a string of dull thumps rang out from beneath the sea of mist, accompanied by a chorus of anguished cries.

Could it be that this white lightning only attacks those with devilish qi in their bodies? Now that I think about it, that makes sense. Immortal Lord Tai Sui must've already anticipated that the five array cores would be broken, and in the case of this happening, the white light barrier would transform into a lightning restriction to unleash those bolts of Heavenly Damnation Lightning and eradicate all of the freed devilish beings.

It looks like this white lightning was designed specifically to counteract devilish qi, so it's no wonder that it was so potent against my Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

By channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, devilish qi had arisen in Han Li's body, and that was why he was mistakenly targeted as a devilish being by the white lightning.

Now that he had reverted back to his human form, and his aura was concealed by his time and lightning law powers, the white lightning immediately ceased to target him any longer.

With that in mind, Han Li remained still on the spot, deciding that the best course of action was to wait out the storm.

Meanwhile, a third round of lightning strikes had already come crashing down, and once again, there were fewer bolts of lightning than during the second round.

After that came three more rounds of lightning strikes, and only after the sixth round did the white cloud above slowly fade away, having expended all of its power.

The tranquil, blue sky above was revealed once again, and it was as if nothing had happened.

Chapter 1104: Venturing Into a Sword Array

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this, then withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis before flying toward the golden palace up ahead.

Upon arriving at the palace, he discovered a massive plaque hanging above its entrance, one that read "Eon Palace" in large, flowing characters.

The palace gates were slightly ajar, and radiant, golden light was pouring out of the gap. The golden light was giving off immense time law power fluctuations that were also intermingled with several other powerful auras, all of which seemed to belong to certain immortal treasures.

However, the opening wasn't large enough to see through, and given how severely spiritual sense was restricted here, it was impossible to detect what was inside the palace.

Han Li stood in front of the palace with a contemplative look on his face.

He hadn't immediately entered the palace as there was a large plaza directly in front of it, and there were numerous yellow stone swords standing on the plaza with their tips pointed upward and their hilts downward.

Each stone sword was around a thousand feet in size, and they were giving off formidable earth law power fluctuations.

There were thirty-six of these stone swords in total, and they were arranged into a sword array on the plaza.

Given the positioning of the sword array, it was impossible to access the palace gates without venturing through it first.

The Essence Fire Raven sprang up from Han Li's shoulder as it began flying toward the Eon Palace, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, following which he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of golden light that swept up the Essence Fire Raven before forcibly throwing it into the Flower Branch domain.

After attaining its essential fire law powers, the Essence Fire Raven had become far more powerful than before, but it had also become more bold and adventurous, making it more difficult to keep under control.

Han Li turned his attention back to the stone sword array, and a frustrated look quickly began to appear in his eyes.

The sword array appeared to be quite simple, but the more he examined it, the more profound it revealed itself to be.

Given enough time, he was confident that he would be able to unravel the array, and doing so would perhaps even be very helpful to honing his expertise in the art of arrays, but at the moment, time was of the essence, so he had to hurry.

With that in mind, Han Li flicked a finger through the air, releasing a streak of golden sword qi that was around a hundred feet in length and thirty feet wide toward one of the stone swords up ahead.

A dense layer of yellow light instantly appeared over the sword's surface, and upon striking the yellow light, the streak of golden sword qi instantly vanished into it without a trace.

After devouring the streak of golden sword qi, the layer of yellow light faded away.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he knew that he wouldn't be able to bypass it using any cheap tricks.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he made a hand seal to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis, which released waves of golden ripples that encompassed the entire surrounding area within a radius of a thousand feet.

From there, Han Li stepped into the stone sword array, and as soon as he did so, he found himself standing in a yellow desert.

Not only was there nothing but yellow sand underfoot for as far as the eyes could see, the clouds above were also a dark, yellow color, and they were giving off a burst of tremendous pressure.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he discovered that unlike the average illusory array, this yellow desert space was extremely solid, with no identifiable weak points to be exploited.

Furthermore, this space contained only earth-attribute spiritual qi, thereby significantly weakening all other types of law powers.

Han Li channeled his Infernal Devilish Eyes to inspect his surroundings, but right at this moment, thirty-six giant, yellow, stone swords emerged over the landscape around him.

All of the stone swords were radiating dazzling, yellow light, and they rose up into the sky as giant pillars of yellow light.

At the same time, steaks of yellow sword qi emerged over the stone swords, giving them the appearance of thirty-six blooming flowers.

Immediately thereafter, all of the streaks of sword qi vanished into thin air, only to reappear around Han Li amid bursts of violent spatial fluctuations before sweeping toward him from all directions.

Han Li remained calm and collected as he made a rapid string of hand seals, and the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him accelerated drastically in its revolution, while the area encompassed within the golden ripples became significantly smaller and more condensed.

All of the streaks of oncoming sword qi were imbued with immense power, but they were immediately immobilized as soon as they pierced into the golden ripples.

All of a sudden, it was as if a ring-shaped wall of yellow swords had appeared around Han Li.

More and more streaks of sword qi continued to pierce into the golden ripples, only to also fall completely still.

However, these streaks of yellow sword qi contained astonishing power, and there were also a staggering number of them.

Within the span of no more than a few seconds, the wall of sword qi around Han Li had reached an incredible level of density, forming a watertight barrier around him.

More and more streaks of sword qi continued to crash into the solid wall of swords, and a string of resounding booms rang out amid explosions of yellow light.

A burst of terrifying spiritual pressure was emanating from the wall of sword qi, compressing toward Han Li from all directions, and the surrounding golden ripples began to tremble in an unsteady fashion, as if they were on the verge of being overwhelmed.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he took a glance at the giant, yellow swords around him.

The thirty-six pillars of yellow light had converged somewhere high up in the sky to form a yellow cloud, and there were countless yellow runes flashing within it, giving off an indescribable aura that was becoming more and more powerful.

A grim look surfaced in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he immediately switched to a different hand seal, upon which his body swelled drastically in size before transforming into a giant, devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

Over nine hundred profound acupoints had lit up over the devilish deity's body, releasing radiant starlight to form a barrier over its body, following which it let loose a thunderous roar before slamming all six of its fists into the surrounding wall of sword qi.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the wall of sword qi was shattered to create an opening, and Han Li immediately withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis before flying out of the opening, pouncing at the nearest stone sword.

The countless streaks of yellow sword qi seemed to have detected his intentions, and they converged from all directions to strike him with immense power.

However, the starlight barrier over his body was extremely resilient, and it was able to keep all of the yellow sword qi at bay.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li was able to reach one of the stone swords before slamming it with an almighty punch.

The giant, stone sword instantly exploded into countless specks of yellow light that then dissipated into nothingness.

Simultaneously, Han Li swung his other five fists through the air in different directions, sending five fist projections crashing into five other stone swords.

Three resounding booms rang out as three more stone swords were shattered in rapid succession, but the sword that was furthest away remained intact as the fist projection directed toward it had been weakened too much by the obstructive sword qi along the way.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, only to immediately fade away a moment later.

Even though the four stone swords had been shattered, the four corresponding pillars of yellow light hadn't faded away. Instead, they were still rising up toward the heavens, but they were looking far dimmer than before.

The earth-attribute spiritual qi in the surrounding environment was surging into the four pillars of yellow light in a frenzy, and four yellow sword projections instantly appeared within them.

With the continued influx of earth-attribute spiritual qi, the four sword projections quickly took on a more substantial form, and before long, it appeared that the four stone swords were about to be reformed.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he immediately summoned his time spirit domain before sweeping all six of his arms through the air to release over two hundred time law threads.

The time law threads split up into two batches, forming a pair of enormous, golden blades that were each close to ten kilometers in length before sweeping through the air in either direction.

At the same time, thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew out of Han Li's body, then combined as one to form a giant, golden, lightning sword that was tens of thousand of feet in length before launching itself up at the yellow clouds in the sky.

A string of resounding booms rang out as the two blades of golden light shattered the majority of the stone swords, but their corresponding pillars of yellow light were still intact, and the broken stone swords began to rapidly reform once again as earth-attribute spiritual qi surged into the pillars of yellow light.

Another resounding boom rang out as the giant lightning sword struck the yellow clouds above.

The clouds didn't appear to be remarkable in any way, but they were extraordinarily resilient, and they only shuddered slightly upon being struck by the lightning sword before falling still again.

Han Li's expression finally completely darkened upon seeing this.

All of a sudden, the yellow clouds in the sky began to churn violently, and all of the nearby earth-attribute spiritual qi surged into them like turbulent waters through a broken floodgate.

The pillars of yellow light around the thirty-six stone swords below were also completely devoured by the yellow clouds, causing them to rapidly expand, while a set of yellow gates that were neither round nor rectangular appeared deep within the clouds.

There were a series of sword-shaped patterns etched onto the gates' surface, and it was giving off tremendous sword qi and earth law power fluctuations.

This burst of earth law power fluctuations was far more vast and profound than average earth law power fluctuations, as if these gates were directly connected to heaven and earth.

All of a sudden, the gravitational force in the entire space became over a hundred times more potent, making it very difficult for Han Li to move.

Chapter 1105: Almighty Sword Array

Under the pressure of the significantly increased gravitational force, Han Li let loose a thunderous roar,and dazzling starlight erupted out of his six fists before converging to form a starlight array on each of his fists.

As he thrust his fists through the air, six mountainous fist projections were sent hurtling toward the yellow clouds above, and these fist projections were far more powerful than the previous ones.

At the same time, the two blades of golden light formed by his time law threads and the giant lightning sword formed by his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords also began racing toward the yellow clouds as three massive streaks of golden light.

A string of earth-shattering booms rang out in rapid succession as the six fist projections struck the yellow clouds before exploding violently into giant balls of light, followed by the two golden blades and the giant lightning sword.

The yellow clouds were extremely resilient, but an opening was still torn into them by the ferocious barrage of attacks, exposing the yellow gates beyond.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he was just about to direct the golden blades and lightning sword toward the yellow gates when it suddenly began to rumble violently, following which a layer of yellow ripples erupted out of its surface.

The golden blades and lightning sword were instantly sent flying back through the air as if they had been dealt a heavy blow, while Han Li also shuddered as he involuntarily stumbled a few steps back.

Right at this moment, the yellow gates began to glow radiantly while opening itself up just a sliver.

Countless rays of yellow light surged out of the opening like a radiant, yellow waterfall cascading down from the heavens, and through the opening, Han Li could see a vast, yellow space beyond the gates, as well as a boundless expanse of rippling yellow light.

Every single ray of light was formed by extremely pure earth law powers that had been condensed to a near liquid state, and they surged out of the gate to form an enormous yellow vortex.

The sword-shaped patterns on the gates were flashing incessantly, and the yellow light cascading down from above split up to form countless yellow stone swords that came raining down upon Han Li in a fearsome downpour.

All of these stone swords were etched with law patterns and giving off incredibly heavy earth law power fluctuations, further increasing the weight of the gravitational force in the environment.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he hurriedly made a string of hand seals, upon which his devilish deity body shrank down to only less than two hundred feet tall.

At the same time, his time spirit domain also shrank down to only several thousand feet in size, but in the process, it had become several times more condensed.

The two blades of golden light flew back into the spirit domain before splitting up into individual time law threads to bolster the spirit domain, and all of the stone swords that pierced into the golden spirit domain were instantly slowed down significantly.

Simultaneously, Han Li made a grabbing motion with all six of his hands, and the giant lightning sword flew back to him before splitting up into six slightly smaller lightning swords that fell into his grasp.

Immediately thereafter, he began swinging the six lightning swords through the air in a rapid blur, unleashing countless sword projections that formed a dense net to oppose the falling stone swords.

A string of resounding booms rang out in rapid succession as the descending stone swords were destroyed by the golden sword net, but Han Li's body was trembling violently from the repeated impacts, and to his alarm, his arms were also beginning to throb with pain.

Every single one of these stone swords was imbued with extremely heavy earth law powers, and with each sword that fell upon him, it felt as if he were deflecting away a huge mountain, resulting in immense physical strain.

As more and more stone swords came falling from the sky, the pressure was only mountain further and further.

What type of accursed sword array is this?!

At the moment, all Han Li could do was channel his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might while bolstering the golden sword net and his time spirit domain to the best of his abilities.

......

At the same time, two streaks of light were approaching the stone sword plaza from close to a thousand feet away, and they contained none other than Wyrm 3 and Fox 3.

"That turtle shell devilish creature just now truly had some remarkable defenses. I had thought that its fate was sealed after it was crushed under my seal, but it was still able to get away," Wyrm 3 mused with slightly furrowed brows.

She was examining a yellow seal in her hand as she spoke, and there was a carving of a fearsome beast perched on top of the seal, while on the underside of the seal were engraved the words "Vast Earth" in antiquated characters.

The seal was giving off tremendous earth law power fluctuations, accompanied by the occasional wave of yellow light, and Fox 3 smiled as he said, "You're not using any earth-attribute cultivation arts, so you're unable to tap into the seal's full power. Having said that, the devilish creature from earlier definitely wasn't able to get away unscathed."

Wyrm 3 nodded in response, and she was just about to stow the yellow seal away when she suddenly cast her gaze toward the stone sword plaza up ahead.

At the moment, the entire plaza was enshrouded in a vast expanse of chaotic sword qi, making it impossible to see anything within.

"This looks like quite a powerful sword array. On top of that, it seems to have already been activated. Could it be that someone is currently trying to force their way through it?" Wyrm 3 speculated.

The two of them had only just descended onto the edge of the stone sword plaza when the Lan siblings also arrived on the scene.

The four of them exchanged a glance with one another, but none of them said anything as they turned their attention to the stone sword plaza and the majestic palace beyond.

Right at this moment, three more streaks of light arrived on the scene, containing Lei Yuce, Su Anqian, and Wen Zhong.

Even before landing on the plaza, Lei Yuce's gaze was already fixed intently on the sword array, and an ecstatic look appeared on his face as he communicated to Wen Zhong through voice transmission, "Do you see this, Junior Martial Brother Wen? This is the Almighty Sword Array, the truly complete version!"

"But the complete version of the sword array has already been lost for countless years, why is it here?" Wen Zhong hurriedly asked.

"I've been studying the Almighty Sword Array for as long as I can remember, yet I've never been able to restore it to its complete form. This is what I've been searching for all along! It looks like the rumors were true; Immortal Lord Tai Sui really did take the array diagram of the Almighty Sword Array from our sect before placing it in here," Lei Yuce said, barely able to contain his own excitement.

Su Anqian raised an eyebrow at the sight of Lei Yuce's excited expression, then asked in a curious manner, "What's going on, Fellow Daoist Lei? You seem very worked up."

Lei Yuce was a little embarrassed by his loss of composure in the presence of Su Anqian, and he explained, "My apologies, Celestial Maiden Su. I simply wasn't able to contain my own excitement at the sight of our sect's long-lost Almighty Sword Array."

"You're saying this is the Almighty Sword Array?" Su Anqian asked with a surprised expression, and the expressions of Wyrm 3 and the others also changed slightly upon hearing this.

Contrary to popular belief, the Almighty Sword Array wasn't named after the Almighty Sword Sect. Instead, it was actually the sect that had been named after the Almighty Sword Array.

It was no exaggeration to say that the Almighty Sword Sect only existed because of the Almighty Sword Array, and that was sufficient testament to how important the array was to the sect.

As the symbolic sword array of the Almighty Sword Sect, its power was naturally not to be understated.

"Fellow Daoist Lei, it looks like someone is already in the process of breaking the array, so let's not waste any more time here. Otherwise, whoever's currently inside the array could reach the palace on the other side of the plaza before us," Wyrm 3 said.

Lei Yuce's brows furrowed slightly in hesitation upon hearing this, and he was just about to say something when he suddenly turned his gaze to a certain direction.

Wyrm 3 and the others also quickly cast their eyes toward the same direction, where a group of several figures were approaching from afar amid a vast cloud of black mist.

These were the leaders of the devilish creatures that had been freed from the altar, and in addition to the Copper Lion King, the White Bone King, and the Blood Hand King, there were also two new faces.

One of them was a black figure that was around a hundred feet tall with dragon horns on its head and scales all over its body, as well as a huge turtle shell on its back that was etched with some strange-looking patterns.

There was a crack with very sharp edges that was around three feet in length on the edge of the shell, and it seemed to have been quite recently acquired.

As soon as it landed on the ground, it immediately turned to Wyrm 3 with a resentful look in its eyes, and it was clear that the crack on its shell had been inflicted by Wyrm 3's Vast Earth Seal.

Compared with its companions, the other devilish being's appearance wasn't all that remarkable. In fact, it could almost have passed for a human if it weren't for its eerie, green eyes. It had a very tall and pronounced nose that was curved like an eagle's beak, as well as a pair of white eyebrows that extended all the way into its sideburns.

The hook-nosed devilish devilish being's gaze fell upon the Lan siblings, and its expression remained unchanged, but a hint of cold killing intent had appeared deep in its eyes, and it was clear that a conflict had arisen earlier between them as well.

Lan Yan didn't waver in the slightest as she met the creature's gaze with a provocative smile on her face, then flipped a hand over to summon a green cane with a series of thin, willow-like branches extending out of it, giving off formidable wood law power fluctuations.

The hook-nosed devilish being's pupils instantly contracted slightly at the sight of the cane, clearly feeling quite wary of it.

Wyrm 3 swept her gaze over the five devilish beings one after the other, following which her gaze settled on the two people accompanying them. These two weren't giving off any devilish qi, but they were clearly the leaders of the group.

The two people in question were none other than Qi Mozi and Xiong Shan.

Chapter 1106: Joining Forces

Qi Mozi could sense the tension in the air, and he stepped in to play the role of mediator as he said, "There's no need for such hostilities, everyone. All of us are here with the common objective of hunting for treasures in this place. There are no personal vendettas here, so why the animosity?"

"These devilish creatures were sent to wreak havoc in our Immortal Realm, and for their transgressions, they've been trapped here for over a million years. Are we just supposed to believe that they don't harbor any resentment and are to be trusted?" Lei Yuce scoffed.

"What do you think should happen here then, Fellow Daoist Lei? Should we all engage in a battle to the death here? Those who perish naturally won't be able to secure any of the treasures in the place, but what about the survivors? What chance will they have of bypassing this Almighty Sword Array? Oh, silly me, I almost forgot that you were from the Almighty Sword Sect, so that won't be a difficult task for you, will it?" Qi Mozi mused with a smile.

An enraged look appeared on Lei Yuce's face in response to Qi Mozi's blatant attempt at sowing dissension.

Sure enough, hesitant looks appeared on the faces of Wyrm 3 and the others upon hearing this.

"Don't listen to him, everyone! These devilish creatures are not to be trusted!" Wen Zhong urged with tightly furrowed brows.

"When it comes to treachery, I'd say that we have much to learn from you humans," the White Bone King sneered.

"I already told you that there's no point in trying to settle things peacefully. Let's just fight them and get it over with," the Copper Lion King harrumphed coldly, while the Blood Hand King and the Turtle Back King remained silent.

The Eagle Nose King also remained silent as he gave the Copper Lion King a cold glare, and a fearful look immediately appeared on the latter's face.

Right at this moment, Xiong Shan suddenly said, "Please pardon my interjection, but while we're standing here bickering about whether we're going to fight or not, there's someone already inside the sword array right now. If we allow them to get to the palace first, not only will all of the treasures inside slip through our grasp, the old devil in the palace will most likely be released as well, and I'm sure that's not a desirable outcome for any of us."

A concerned look appeared in Lei Yuce's eyes upon hearing this. At the moment, almost everyone in the Eon Pagoda was already gathered here, so it wasn't difficult to deduce the identity of the person in the sword array by process of elimination.

If anyone else were in the array, Lei Yuce wouldn't be overly concerned, but there was a very good chance that the person in the array was Han Li, who he had always found to be unfathomable, and that was a very unsettling thought for him.

Most importantly, he absolutely could not allow the array diagram for the Almighty Sword Array to fall into Han Li's hands.

With that in mind, Lei Yuce heaved a faint sigh as he acquiesced, "In that case, let's set our differences aside for now and work together to bypass the array."

Qi Mozi turned his gaze to the Eagle Nose King, as if to ask for his opinion on the matter, and the latter said, "I'll leave it up to you, Fellow Daoist Qi Mozi."

"We would be more than willing to join forces, it's just a matter of whether this is an agreeable arrangement to all of you," Qi Mozi said.

Lei Yuce turned to Wyrm 3 and the others upon hearing this, and no one raised any objections to the idea.

"As a gesture of sincerity, I've already ordered all of their subordinates to stay far away from this place, so how about you display some sincerity in exchange as well?" Qi Mozi asked.

"What do you suggest?" Lei Yuce asked.

"The Almighty Sword Array comes from your Almighty Sword Sect, so surely you have some insights on how to break the array, right?" Qi Mozi asked.

"I'm afraid not. The complete version of the sword array has already been lost to our sect for countless years, so we'll have to figure out how to break the array after we enter it," Lei Yuce sighed.

Qi Mozi raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, clearly skeptical of his claims.

"If you don't believe me, then there's nothing I can say to convince you. If you wish to do so, you can go in ahead of us and try to break the array," Lei Yuce said as he spread his hands open in a resigned manner.

"It's fine. In that case, let's enter the array together. I'm sure that once you're in the array, you'll have no choice but to dedicate your full effort to breaking it," Qi Mozi said with a smile.

"Of course. Once I've entered the array and had a chance to assess its internal workings, I'm confident that I'll be able to unravel it," Lei Yuce replied with a nod.

With that, everyone split up into the two groups and arranged themselves in front of the sword array.

"After entering the array, make sure you move around as little as possible. The more you move, the more aggressively the sword array will attack you," Lei Yuce said to Wyrm 3 and the others through voice transmission.

No one displayed any outward reaction to this, but it was clear that they had all heard the warning.

Qi Mozi took a derisive glance in their direction, then declared, "Enter the array!"

Everyone sprang into action upon hearing this.

Right as they were about to enter the array, Lei Yuce suddenly grabbed onto Su Anqian's hand as he urged, "Stay close to me."

Su Anqian's heart skipped a beat at this sudden gesture of intimacy, and her cheeks were suddenly feeling a little hot.

Everyone had only just entered the sword array when they were forced to descend to the ground by a burst of invisible pressure.

Before they had a chance to figure out what was happening, the entire surrounding area had already descended into complete chaos.

Bursts of thunderous rumbling rang out as heaven and earth tumbled violently, and it was impossible to see anything aside from patches of hazy, yellow light, and the suffocating, yellow clouds up above.

Having entered the array together, Su Anqian and Lei Yuce were still able to see each other, but they were no longer able to see or detect anyone else.

The gravitational force in the environment seemed to have increased in potency by at least tenfold, making even standing a rather strenuous task.

They could see a pillar of yellow light rising up into the sky from the ground nearby, piercing straight into the cloud above, and situated within the pillar of yellow light was a giant stone sword.

"It looks like the array has been established upon a foundation of earth law powers, so it's not going to be easy to unravel it," Lei Yuce remarked.

"What does that mean?" Su Anqian asked in a puzzled manner.

"In itself, the Almighty Sword Array is an attributeless array, and it can give rise to different phenomena in accordance with the law powers imbued within the flying swords used to set up the array. This is why I said that I'll only be able to figure out how to unravel the array once I've entered it myself," Lei Yuce explained.

"In that case, how do we unravel the array?" Su Anqian asked.

"Sword arrays are supposed to be controlled by cultivators, yet this one is able to function without anyone presiding over it, so it's most likely the case that the array diagram is being used to serve as the core of the array. Hence, the fastest way to unravel the array would be to find the array diagram and displace it," Lei Yuce replied.

Right at this moment, a dull thump suddenly rang out from above.

It was an extremely deep and dull sound that had come from within the yellow clouds in the sky.

Lei Yuce and Su Anqian reflexively looked up to find that there was a majestic heavenly gate up above, and it was slightly ajar to reveal a narrow opening.

Through the opening, a massive, yellow vortex could be seen, and it was releasing terrifying earth law power fluctuations.

Su Anqian was just about to say something when the vortex within the gate began to flash erratically, following which bursts of yellow light erupted out of the opening between the gates before raining down from above.

These bursts of light transformed into numerous giant, yellow swords that were over a hundred feet in length, and they came crashing down upon all parts of the sword array with tremendous power.

Two of the giant swords were descending toward Lei Yuce and Su Anqian, and even before it had fallen upon them, it was already giving off a sense of asphyxiating pressure that made them feel as if the sky were falling upon them.

"Look out!" Lei Yuce yelled out in alarm as he hurriedly positioned himself in front of Su Anqian before raising his hands to the sky.

A circular array that was several hundred feet in radius instantly appeared beneath his feet, and it was glowing with radiant, golden light, while massive sword projections emerged from it like spring bamboo shoots after heavy rainfall before rising up into the heavens.

A string of resounding booms rang out as the sword projections that had risen up from the ground clashed against the two giant swords descending from the sky.

The pair of giant swords were tearing through the opposing sword projections with ease as it plummeted out of the sky with mountainous force, and a stunned look appeared on Lei Yuce's eyes upon seeing this.

So this is the power of the true Almighty Sword Array?

Right at this moment, a layer of water law power fluctuations spread through the air from beside him amid a flash of blue light.

A blue light barrier had appeared around Su Anqian, and her palms were joined in front of her own chest with a longan-sized bead clasped between them. Blue springwater was currently following out of the bead before revolving around her slender hands, and her eyes were gently shut as her entire body was basked in hazy, blue light, giving her the captivating appearance of a breathtaking celestial maiden.

All of a sudden, her eyes sprang open as she raised her palms up to the heavens, and the blue springwater flowing around her hands erupted into the air, then swelled drastically in size to form an enormous wave that swept toward the pair of descending swords.

Opposed by the torrent of rising water, the two giant swords were still descending out of the sky, but they had been slowed down significantly.

Chapter 1107: Search for the Array Core

Lei Yuce let loose a thunderous roar, and the circular array beneath him began to glow even brighter as numerous radiant, golden swords emerged from the ground, with all of them pointed directly up at the heavens above.

In contrast with the sword projections from before, these were all real flying swords, and there were thirty-six of them, all of which were etched with array patterns that were giving off metal law power fluctuations.

The golden flying swords trembled and buzzed violently, following which countless golden sword threads erupted out of them at Lei Yuce's behest before rising up into the air like a golden waterfall in reverse.

The two giant swords in the sky were already being severely impeded by the torrent of blue water unleashed by Su Anqian, and with further resistance posed by the flurry of golden sword threads, all of the earth law powers within them were finally exhausted.

The pair of swords exploded in unison into a vast expanse of yellow light, and Lei Yuce and Su Anqian exchanged an elated smile upon seeing this.

However, before the two of them had a chance to relax, a burst of dull rumbling rang out from the heavenly gates in the sky.

"Looks like the attacks aren't going to cease until we break the sword array," Lei Yuce mused.

"The array diagram must be somewhere in the array, right? You go and search for it, I can fend for myself just fine," Su Anqian said.

A concerned look appeared on Lei Yuce's face upon hearing this, but before he had a chance to say anything, a Su Anqian put on a stern expression as she asked, "Fellow Daoist Lei, are you looking down on myself or our Heavenly Water Sect?"

"Of course not, it's just that..."

Lei Yuce's voice trailed off here as a wry smile appeared on his face.

Su Anqian's expression eased slightly as she said, "Just go, I'll be fine on my own."

"Alright, in that case, make sure to look after yourself," Lei Yuce reluctantly acquiesced.

"You too, Fellow Daoist Lei," Su Anqian replied, and Lei Yuce was ecstatic to hear her words of concern.

He nodded firmly in response, then began making his way toward the center of the array, and despite the crushing pressure weighing down upon him, his footsteps felt very light and energetic.

The heavenly gates up above were still ajar, and yellow swords continued to fall out of the sky upon the devilish beings and Wyrm 3 and the others.

As a result, much of the pressure on Han Li was alleviated.

With so many people in the array, it had no choice but to split its power to attack everyone, rather than focusing solely on attacking Han Li.

At this moment, he was channeling his true spirit bloodlines and Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, and held in each of his six hands was an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which he was constantly swinging through the air, releasing bursts of lightning sword qi to eradicate the giant swords crashing down from above as he trudged toward the center of the sword array.

In his mind, it stood to reason that the core of the sword array was most likely at its center, and if he could find the core, then he would have a chance to break the array.

All of a sudden, bursts of chaotic light appeared in the surrounding space, accompanied by gusts of fierce wind, and everything up ahead had become very hazy and indistinct, as if he had stepped into a boundless illusion.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately began inspecting his surroundings with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

However, even under the scrutiny of his Infernal Devilish Eyes, his surroundings didn't change in the slightest, and giant, yellow swords were still raining down upon him from above, forcing him to defend himself while traversing arduously through the sword array.

He channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique and spread his spiritual sense throughout the surrounding area as far and wide as it would go, but that didn't yield any useful discoveries, either.

Spiritual sense was even more severely restricted in this sword array than it was elsewhere in the Eon Pagoda, and all Han Li could detect with his spiritual sense was a boundless expanse of earth law powers.

He was beginning to grow a little agitated, but there was nothing that he could do aside from continue to forge ahead in the direction that his instincts told him was correct.

However, as he trudged onward, the pressure in the environment only became more and more potent, and it had become over ten times heavier than when he first entered the sword array.

With each step that he took, the ground beneath his feet would shatter, leaving a trail of deep footprints behind him.

On top of that, with each giant sword that came crashing down, the pressure that he was forced to withstand would increase a little more.

What a pain in the backside this sword array is! Even if a Great Encompassment cultivator ventures into it, they'll be worn down and killed if they can't find the right way to unravel the array.

A sickly sweet sensation welled up from the back of Han Li's throat, and he spat out a globule of blood-infused saliva.

Even though he appeared to be just fine, his internal organs were under immense pressure, and if he couldn't find a way to break out of the sword array, his life would eventually come under threat.

After trudging arduously onward for several thousand more feet, he had left behind a long string of deep footprints in the ground.

All of a sudden, a thought seemed to have occurred to him, and he closed his eyes before advancing in different directions in an experimental fashion.

Each time, he would walk around a dozen steps before retreating back to his original spot, then repeat the process in another direction.

Before long, the entire surrounding area in a radius of over a hundred feet had been filled with massive footprints, and as he returned to his original spot one final time, he opened his eyes and exhaled before turning to a certain direction with a faint smile on his face.

The entire surrounding area was in a state of complete chaos, and nothing could be detected aside from earth law powers, but all law powers displayed certain patterns in the way that they flowed and moved.

There should've been a change in the density of law powers in the area where the core of sword array was situated, and Han Li had walked in all those different directions in order to detect for changes in the law powers in the environment.

Sure enough, he was able to detect an increasing degree of density of earth law powers in the air in a certain direction to his right, and that was where he presumed the core of the array to be.

With that in mind, he swung his six arms through the air in rapid succession, swatting away the giant swords crashing down upon him from above before turning to walk in that direction.

Even though the general direction had been ascertained, the sword array was so chaotic that it felt like the surrounding orientations were constantly changing, so Han Li was forced to stop every dozen or so steps to reaffirm his sense of direction again.

The footsteps he left behind were becoming deeper and deeper, and finally, an octagonal altar appeared in the distance.

After taking a few steps toward the altar, Han Li was able to see eight yellow stones that contained earth law powers embedded into the sides of the altar.

Furthermore, there was a stone sword protruding out of the ground on each side of the altar, and they stood like eight loyal guardians protecting an octagonal jade plate that was hovering above the center of the altar.

The jade plate wasn't giving off any earth law power fluctuations, but it was flashing with spiritual light, and a series of complex patterns could be seen etched onto its surface.

As soon as Han Li began to approach the altar, a burst of azure light instantly emerged over the jade plate, and the eight stones embedded into the sides of the altar also lit up.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li heard a ringing sound emanating from the eight stone swords on the altar.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he swung his arms vigorously through the air one more time to deflect the falling giant swords, then launched himself at the altar before the next wave of giant swords had a chance to descend upon him.

Thanks to his Reversal True Axis ability, his speed was greatly enhanced, but it was still far slower than normal due to the immense spatial pressure in this place.

Thankfully, there was a safe zone of roughly three hundred feet around the altar that was untouched by the giant swords falling from the sky. Otherwise, the sword array would be destroying its own core.

As Han Li flew toward the altar, a string of loud clangs suddenly rang out as the eight stone swords rose up from the ground before hurtling directly toward him.

These eight stone swords seemed to have been dedicated solely to protecting the array diagram on the altar, and they were far more formidable than the stone swords falling from above.

Bursts of dark yellow light appeared over the flying swords before splitting off into countless sword projections, and in the blink of an eye, there were several thousand flying swords racing toward Han Li at once.

All of these flying swords were giving off bursts of identical earth law power fluctuations, making it impossible to tell which eight of them were real.

Han Li reverted back to his human form upon seeing this, then swept a sleeve through the air to release thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which fanned out before him, then also released countless sword projections of their own.

Chapter 1108: Battle for the Array Diagram

The countless streaks of sword qi released by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were sent hurtling through the air at Han Li's behest, sweeping toward the thousands of oncoming stone swords.

A rapid string of loud clangs rang out as the sword projections released by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were rapidly eradicated, and it took dozens of them to destroy a single stone sword.

Thankfully, the number of the sword projections released by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords far exceeded that of the stone swords, so they were able to hold their own for now.

There was a solemn look on Han Li's face as he made a rapid string of hands seals, and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew forward in a steady manner at his behest, forming a giant net of swordlight that forced back the opposing stone swords.

Before long, the vast majority of the sword projections released by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had already been destroyed, while the number of opposing stone swords had also been whittled down to fewer than forty.

However, the clashes between them were still as fierce as ever, and Han Li was gritting his teeth tightly as large droplets of sweat began to bead up on his forehead.

All of a sudden, he let loose a low roar as he injected his immortal spiritual power into his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in a frenzy, and countless arcs of golden lightning erupted out of them to destroy most of the remaining stone swords in an instant.

All that remained were the eight original stone swords, and they were still hovering in the sky with their tips aimed directly at him.

At the same time, the number of sword projections released by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had been reduced to fewer than ninety.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly as he took a step forward to step onto the altar, but right at this moment, the yellow stones embedded onto the sides of the altar abruptly lit up.

The eight stone swords in the air shuddered violently as if they had just received a potent injection of power, and radiant, yellow light erupted out of them to eradicate all of the remaining Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword projections in an instant.

The thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were able to keep seven of the stone swords at bay, but the eighth one was able to slip through the cracks, and in the blink of an eye, it was no more than ten feet away from Han Li's chest.

Han Li immediately channeled his Reversal True Axis ability while stepping to the side, and the stone sword just barely flew past his ribcage, tearing a large gash into his robe.

He hurriedly made a beckoning motion toward his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords while taking a step back, but right at this moment, all of the stones embedded onto the sides of the altar suddenly turned completely dim before shattering into pieces.

The seven stone swords in the sky also tumbled to the ground, seemingly having been drained of all power.

It appeared that the law powers within the stones had already been completely exhausted over the course of the countless years that the altar had been standing, and a relieved look appeared on Han Li's face as he prepared to step onto the altar again.

However, his expression then suddenly changed slightly as he hurriedly looked down at his own waist.

Blood was seeping into the torn section of his robe, but the gash wasn't very deep.

However, as Han Li pulled back his robe to inspect the wound, he discovered that it had turned a lifeless, gray color, and that it was as cold and hard as stone to the touch.

It immediately occurred to him that his wound had to have been petrified by the earth law powers within the stone sword.

Thankfully, as aforementioned, the gash wasn't very deep, and the petrified area was only around an inch in size.

Han Li severed the affected piece of skin and flesh from his own body with his finger, and the newly formed wound began to heal on its own.

After that, he stowed all of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and he was just about to make his way onto the altar when he heard a burst of rumbling ringing out nearby. It seemed that someone else had also found the array core and was on their way here.

With that in mind, he hurriedly stepped onto the altar without any hesitation, then grabbed onto the octagonal jade plate before pulling it out of the altar.

He inspected the jade plate briefly with his spiritual sense, following which an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

This octagonal jade plate was none other than the Almighty Sword Array diagram that had been taken from the Almighty Sword Sect by Immortal Lord Tai Sui, and it was far more complex and profound than Han Li had imagined.

Even after just a brief inspection, Han Li could tell that this was a priceless treasure, and he hurriedly stowed it away.

In the next instant, a resounding boom rang out from above, and Han Li looked up to discover that the heavenly gates in the sky had swung shut, while the yellow clouds around it were quickly fading away.

All of the giant swords falling from the sky had already vanished, and the entire array was beginning to disintegrate.

The suffocating pressure in the air was slowly abating, but the chaotic mist in the area still lingered for now. However, the earth law powers within it were already completely undetectable.

Han Li stepped down from the altar, and he was just about to take a pill when a voice rang out from behind him.

"Thank you for your hard work in breaking the array, Fellow Daoist Han."

Han Li turned around to discover Lei Yuce approaching him with a smile, and as he did so, he swept a sleeve through the air, casually stowing away the eight stone swords scattered over the ground.

"I wouldn't have been able to do it on my own," Han Li replied with a smile.

"You're far too modest, Fellow Daoist Han," Lei Yuce continued, and Han Li merely smiled again and offered no response.

A hesitant look appeared on Lei Yuce's face, following which he said, "Fellow Daoist Han, I have a request for you."

Han Li could already guess what Lei Yuce wanted, but he put on an oblivious facade as he asked, "What is it, Fellow Daoist Lei?"

"I'm assuming that you saw a sword array diagram while breaking the array. That's a long-lost treasure that's extremely important to our Almighty Sword Sect, and I'm hoping that you can return it to me. Of course, our Almighty Sword Sect will compensate you handsomely in exchange," Lei Yuce said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Han Li feigned a perplexed expression as he said, "I've only just managed to free myself from the sword array, and I'm afraid I saw no array diagram or anything of the sort."

"Fellow Daoist Han, the sword array is one of an extremely high caliber, but for you, it's nothing more than a powerful sword array, while to our Almighty Sword Sect, it holds great symbolic importance, so please return it to me. I'm willing to give you a fifth tier immortal treasure in exchange, and on top of that, you can receive the benefits granted to the inner sect elders of our sect without having to perform any of the obligations," Lei Yuce insisted.

This was a tremendous amount of compensation, and it was certainly true that Lei Yuce was displaying the utmost sincerity. However, this Almighty Sword Array was simply far too appealing to Han Li to pass up. If he could unleash it using his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, then it would most definitely become another powerful trump card of his.

With that in mind, Han Li feigned a disappointed expression as he replied, "I appreciate the kind offer, but I'm afraid I truly have not seen this array diagram that you speak of. The terms that you offered are extremely appealing to me, but I can't bring myself to lie to you for my own personal gain."

Lei Yuce raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and he asked, "Did you really not see an array diagram on this altar, Fellow Daoist Han?"

"No. There were only those eight stone swords on the altar, and I didn't even get a chance to look at them before you took them," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

Lei Yuce remained silent as he scrutinized Han Li intently, trying to see if there were any holes in his facade, but it appeared that he really was telling the truth.

"If there's nothing else that you wish to speak to me about, then how about we go and explore the Eon Palace, Fellow Daoist Lei?" Han Li suggested.

Lei Yuce's brows furrowed tightly as he suddenly made a hand seal while chanting an incantation, and a white jade badge that was strapped to his waist abruptly lit up.

At the same time, a storage ring on Han Li's finger also began to flash rhythmically, and that was the storage ring that was holding the octagonal jade plate.

"Are you really not willing to return the array diagram, Fellow Daoist Han?" Lei Yuce asked.

"I've already done you a favor by allowing you to take those stone swords, so I suggest that you don't try to push me any further. If you want to try and take the array diagram from me by force, then go ahead. I certainly wouldn't mind recovering those stone swords for myself," Han Li replied in a cold voice, then passed through the plaza and made his way onto the stone steps leading up to the Eon Palace.

Lei Yuce remained standing on the spot with a look of mixed emotions in his eyes.

At this point, the mist on the plaza had already faded away, and everyone was beginning to converge toward the Eon Plaza.

Lei Yuce heaved an internal sigh at the sight as he suppressed the anger in his heart.

There were still more important things that he had to do in the palace, so he had to focus on the task at hand.

Chapter 1109: Dao Warrior Array

Upon reaching the top of the stone staircase, Han Li arrived before the palace, and his brows immediately furrowed slightly at the sight that he was greeted by.

Every single brick and pillar was etched with runes that resonated with one another to form a massive array, all of which were designed to fortify the palace, making it as structurally resilient as a powerful immortal treasure.

However, there were no other restrictions at the entrance of the palace, and Han Li was able to push its gates open with ease.

He stepped into the palace, then looked around to discover that its interior was far larger than he had imagined.

Directly up ahead was a huge, pentagonal stone platform that was tapered from the bottom to the top, giving it the appearance of an upside-down pentagonal bowl.

The stone platform had a total of five sides, each of which was constructed from a different material, and they were golden, azure, blue, crimson, and yellow in color. At the center of each side was engraved a strange-looking rune, and the structure also appeared to have been an altar.

Han Li could see an antiquated golden lamp on the platform.

The lamp post was slightly curved like the stalk of a lotus flower, while the lamp itself resembled a budding lotus flower, at the center of which was a small, golden flame.

The lamp was radiating golden light that formed a hemispherical protective barrier that encompassed the entire altar, and even though Han Li was standing some distance away from the altar, he could sense the waves of time law power fluctuations emanating from the golden lamp.

"Is that the Eon Divine Lamp? It sure is giving off some formidable time law power fluctuations..."

Right at this moment, Wyrm 3 and the others entered the palace, accompanied by Qi Mozi, Xiong Shan, and the five devilish beings.

Qi Mozi's gaze was immediately drawn to the Eon Divine Lamp as soon as he stepped into the palace, while the five devilish beings were looking at the five-colored altar with fearful looks on their faces.

Right as everyone's attention was drawn to the lamp and the altar, two streaks of light, on black and one white, flew into the palace, then vanished into the ground.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly as he cast his gaze toward Qi Mozi and the others, but right at this moment, Qi Mozi suddenly proposed through voice transmission, "Fellow Daoist Han, I suggest a temporary truce while we're in this Eon Palace. What do you say?"

"I was about to suggest the same thing," Han Li immediately replied without any hesitation.

Of course, he had no trust in Qi Mozi, but as long as Qi Mozi didn't attack him, he was happy to avoid a battle. After all, given the presence of so many people, the situation was very complex, and a battle against Qi Mozi here would only be detrimental to him.

In Han Li's eyes, self-preservation was an objective that had to be prioritized above all else, including his personal differences with Qi Mozi and his desire to obtain the Eon Divine Lamp.

"The bonded soul tablets are also here," Fox 3 suddenly said, and sure enough, there were three palm-sized crimson tablets placed in an orderly fashion within the shadow cast by the golden light emanating from the Eon Divine Lamp.

Those were clearly the bonded soul badges of Qu Lin, Lekima, and the azure-robed man.

There was also a triangular, black tablet placed next to the three bonded soul tablets, and there seemed to have been something etched onto its surface, but it was rather blurry and indistinct.

Han Li noticed that Wyrm 3's attention was primarily drawn to the Eon Divine Lamp and the black tablet.

A curious look appeared in his eyes upon seeing this, but he chose not to ask any questions.

Additionally, there was also a rolled-up golden scroll on the altar, and it was loosely bound by a length of thin, golden string.

A hint of clear excitement flashed through Lei Yuce's eyes at the sight of the golden scroll, and he exchanged an ecstatic glance with Wen Zhong, indicating that the scroll was something of great importance to the Almighty Sword Sect.

As Han Li swept his gaze over everyone present, he couldn't help but wonder where Qu Lin was.

Before he had a chance to ponder this matter any further, the entire palace suddenly shuddered violently, and its gates swung shut on their own.

At the same time, dazzling golden light began to ripple through the air around the palace, and the entire surrounding area was enshrouded in bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations.

Everyone felt as if they had been thrust into a golden space, in which the flow of time had slowed down significantly. As a result, their thoughts and spiritual sense had all been severely restricted.

Han Li immediately made a hand seal, and a burst of golden light erupted out of his body before rapidly expanding to encompass Lei Yuce and the others, while Qi Mozi also released his spirit domain to encompass Xiong Shan and the five devilish beings.

The spirit domains restored everyone's ability to think clearly, but the speed of movement was still severely hampered.

Right at this moment, a massive ring of light suddenly appeared on the ground in front of everyone, following which a series of blurry humanoid figures emerged one after another.

All of these humanoid figures were as tall and thin as bamboo poles, and they were clad in suits of ill-fitting golden armor that clattered as they walked.

All of them were Dao Warriors that appeared thin and frail, but they were giving off formidable auras.

To everyone's surprise, instead of attacking right away, the Dao Warriors spread themselves out in an orderly fashion to form layers upon layers of encirclements around everyone.

Before long, the Dao Warriors had already arranged themselves into an array, and as soon as the array took shape, blinding golden light began to radiate from their suits of armor.

Han Li felt a sharp pain in his eyes from the overwhelming brightness, and he hurriedly narrowed his eyes while channeling his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

A protective, purple film seemed to have appeared over his eyes, making the blinding, golden light more bearable to look at, and everyone else was also adopting their own measures to protect their eyes against the golden radiance.

Han Li could see streams of runes of different colors flowing out of the armor worn by the Dao Warriors, and these streams of runes transformed into bursts of light of different colors that surged back into the Dao Warriors' bodies.

With these influxes of light, the Dao Warriors began to undergo strange transformations. One group of Dao Warriors received an influx of azure light, and their bodies quickly swelled to around twice their original size, while each of them also acquired an azure longsword.

The neighboring group of Dao Warriors received an influx of yellow light, and their bodies swelled to thrice their original size while also transforming into imposing stone golems with massive stone hammers in their hands.

The influx of blue light liquefied the suits of armor worn by the affected Dao Warriors, turning them into puddles of golden liquid that flowed down the Dao Warriors' bodies and onto the ground below.

As for the crimson light, that set the suits of armor worn by the Dao Warriors alight while also granting each of them a large, fiery saber.

Only the Dao Warriors that received an influx of golden light didn't take on any physical changes, but each of them had been equipped with a corkscrew-tipped golden spear.

"What's going on? How are there Dao Warriors of so many different attributes here at once?" Wyrm 3 exclaimed with an incredulous expression.

"Every single one of these Dao Warriors is comparable in power to a Golden Immortal, and there has to be at least five hundred of them here! On top of that, all of them are enhanced by the law powers of the five elements! How is this possible?" Fox 3 exclaimed.

"Looks like I had too low an opinion of that old bastard, Tai Sui," Qi Mozi mused.

"What's going on here, Fellow Daoist Lei?" Lan Yuanzi asked.

"I... I don't know, either," Lei Yuce replied, clearly also very much taken aback by this turn of events.

He was the one who knew the most about the Eon Pagoda out of everyone present, but even so, he had still been surprised on many occasions, so his knowledge of the Eon Pagoda was clearly far from comprehensive.

"The Dao Warriors have taken on transformations of different attributes because the array that they've set up is resonating with that five-elemental altar," Han Li analyzed.

"You're saying that the altar is the thing that gave rise to all these transformations?" Wyrm 3 asked.

Chapter 1110: Unifying Against the Five-Elemental Dao Warriors

"It's more accurate to say that these Dao Warriors are drawing upon the power of the five-elemental altar to enhance themselves," Han Li corrected.

Right at this moment, the blinding, golden light faded away, and the five-colored Dao Warriors pounced at Han Li's group with their weapons raised.

These Dao Warriors appeared to be charging forward in a rather chaotic fashion, but in reality, they were displaying exceptional teamwork, and there were no holes in their formation to be exploited at all.

Everyone quickly realized this, and they hurriedly adopted defensive formations to ward off the enemy.

Meanwhile, Qi Mozi sprang up into the air and flew toward the fire-attribute Dao Warriors, then summoned his Time Severing Torch, seemingly intending to immobilize the Dao Warriors with his time law powers.

However, he quickly discovered that his time law powers had no effect on these Dao Warriors.

Xiong Shan had been carefully trailing along behind Qi Mozi this entire time, and he was instantly rooted to the spot by the Time Severing Torch.

Qi Mozi cast his gaze toward the golden lamp on the altar, and a look of realization instantly appeared on his face.

These Dao Warriors were able to draw upon the power of the altar, so they were naturally also able to borrow the power of the lamp to help them ward off the effects of time law powers.

With that in mind, Qi Mozi withdrew his Time Severing Torch, then flipped a hand over to produce his black stone ax, which he swung through the air at the hundred or so oncoming fire-attribute Dao Warriors.

A streak of crescent-shaped black light erupted out of the blade of the ax before sweeping toward the fire-attribute Dao Warriors, which immediately stopped in their tracks before quickly switching to a different formation.

The crimson flames burning over their suits of armor connected together to form a wall of fire, and at the same time, the Dao Warriors at the forefront of the formation swung their sabers through the air in unison.

A resounding boom rang out as a massive wall of fire surged forth, sweeping toward Qi Mozi with burning fury.

The wall of fire burned holes into the surrounding air to form spatial vortexes, and immediately thereafter, the second row of Dao Warriors swung their sabers through the air as well, forming a second wall of fire, then a third, then a fourth...

By the time the black ax projection struck the first wall of fire, over ten spatial vortexes had already appeared in the surrounding area.

The first wall of fire was eradicated by the black ax projection, while the latter continued onward, slicing through the second and third walls of fire as well.

The destroyed walls of fire exploded into countless flames that were immediately devoured by the spatial vortexes in the air.

Meanwhile, the black ax in Qi Mozi's hand had already transformed into a black whirlwind that encompassed his entire body, and he flew straight through several walls of fire to force his way into ranks of the fire-attribute Dao Warriors.

Meanwhile, the five devilish beings were opposing the wood-attribute Dao Warriors, and all of them turned to the Eagle Nose King for a plan of attack.

"Just adopt a defensive formation for now. There's no need to strike too early when we can just wait for the others to test out the waters for others," the Eagle Nose King said as he crossed his arms, and it seemed like he had no intention of doing any of the dirty work himself.

The other four devilish beings seemed to have already grown accustomed to this, and a wide grin appeared on the White Bone King's face as he said, "It's been a long time since we've gotten any good exercise, so let's start off with the four symbols array for now."

"Sounds like a good warm up!" the other three devilish beings eagerly agreed, and they rushed forward while plumes of black smoke began to rise up from their bodies.

Enshrouded within the black smoke, the four devilish beings adopted their true devilish forms, with the Copper Lion King at the front, the White Bone King bringing up the rear, and the other two on the sides.

It was clear that they were very familiar with fighting alongside one another, and they resembled a single, unified entity.

The oncoming wood-attribute Dao Warriors displayed no fear as they plunged their weapons into the ground, which immediately began to rumble and tremble violently.

The Eagle Nose King's brows furrowed slightly as he looked down to discover a layer of slick moss rapidly spreading over the ground toward him, while thick vines erupted out of the earth.

The ground below crumbled with a thunderous commotion, and countless vines sprang out of the ground like devilish tentacles before piercing into the four symbols array.

"You know what? I may get involved, after all," the Eagle Nose King murmured to himself, following which a layer of black devilish flames emerged over his body, and he sprang up into the air like a majestic bird of prey before also swooping into the array.

Meanwhile, Han Li and the others were facing off against the remaining Dao Warriors.

Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan seemed to have connected their immortal spiritual power through the use of some type of secret technique, and they were locked in battle against the water-attribute Dao Warriors.

The two of them swept their sleeves through the air to release torrents of water that kept the oncoming Dao Warriors at bay, and the water was also releasing plumes of white smoke that gave off a mesmerizing aroma.

At the same time, Lei Yuce, Wen Zhong, and Su Anqian were battling the earth-attribute stone golems.

These stone golems didn't possess any strange abilities, but they were extremely strong and resilient. Every time they were struck down, they were always able to fully regenerate in a matter of seconds, and it was as if they possessed undying bodies.

As for Han Li, he had joined forces with Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 against the golden, spear-wielding Dao warriors.

Their suits of armor were no less resilient than the bodies of the stone golems, and with each thrust of their spears, arrows of golden light would erupt out of the corkscrew-shaped tips.

These arrows of golden light were extremely sharp, and even though Han Li was maintaining a distance of over a hundred feet from the Dao Warriors, the arrows of light were still able to reach him in an instant.

What was even more problematic was that even though these Dao Warriors didn't seem to possess any intelligence, they were working together extremely seamlessly like a disciplined and well-trained army, and there were no holes in their defense for Han Li's trio to exploit.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly yelled, "Look out!"

Fox 3 immediately twisted to the side upon hearing this, and he was only just barely able to evade two arrows of golden light that had suddenly shot down at him from above.

Even though he was able to evade the attack, a gash was still sliced into his shoulder, and blood began to flow from the wound.

He took a glance at the gash, and it wasn't severe, so he threw himself back into the battle.

However, shortly thereafter, he discovered that not only had the gash not healed, his entire arm had become incredibly heavy, as if it had been injected with lead.

He hurriedly called out for Han Li and Wyrm 3 to cover him, while he took several pills before closing his eyes to meditate. However, to his astonishment, he discovered that the pills had no effect on the wound at all.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he flipped a hand over to produce a yellow gourd, which he turned upside-down to conjure up a yellow vortex.

A series of yellow beans flew out of the vortex before transforming into an army of lightning-armored Dao Warriors to oppose the golden Dao Warriors.

Han Li's Dao Warriors were of a far inferior caliber, so they were no match for their opponents, but they excelled in numbers, and they were able to assist Wyrm 3 in holding off all of the enemy Dao Warriors for now.

Taking advantage of this opportunity, Han Li immediately flew over to Fox 3's side, and the latter looked up at him with tightly furrowed brows as he said, "Make sure you don't get struck by those arrows of golden light, Fellow Daoist Han. This tiny gash refuses to stop bleeding, and it's made my arm so heavy that I can barely lift it. On top of that, even taking pills hasn't had any effect."

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this, following which a burst of golden light emerged over the palm of his hand as he gently brushed it over the wound.

A small tree projection appeared over the wound amid a flash of golden light, and it was none other than the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree.

As soon as the tree emerged, its roots burrowed deep into Fox 3's wound before releasing waves of golden ripples, and Fox 3 immediately felt a burst of heat flow through his entire arm.

To his surprise, his arm didn't feel as heavy as before, and the bleeding had also ceased.

"I've only used my time law powers to temporarily seal your wound so that it won't affect your mobility, so you're going to have to find some other way to expel that burst of power from your body later," Han Li said.

"That's fine. You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Han," Fox 3 replied with a nod.

Chapter 1111: Fight for the Lamp

Han Li turned and cast his gaze toward the five-colored altar beyond the Dao Warriors as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

"What is it, Fellow Daoist Han?" Fox 3 asked.

Instead of answering his questions, Han Li turned to Wyrm 3 as he called out, "Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, these Dao Warriors are able to draw power from the altar, and we won't be able to eradicate them unless we can cut them off from their power source."

"Do you have any ideas, Fellow Daoist Han?" Wyrm 3 asked as she also disengaged herself from the battle.

"I want to try and use my spirit domain to cut off this connection, but my spirit domain alone most likely doesn't possess the power required to accomplish this, so I'm going to require your assistance," Han Li said.

"So all you need me to do is release my spirit domain?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"That's right. Just release your spirit domain to encompass a small area and focus only on the metal-attribute Dao Warriors. Once we've eradicated them, we'll be able to wipe out the rest," Han Li replied.

"Alright, in that case, let's begin," Wyrm 3 said.

"There's no hurry, I'll inform the others of my plan first," Han Li replied, then informed Lei Yuce and the others of his proposed course of action so that they could prepare themselves accordingly.

Once everyone had been alerted to what was going to happen, Han Li gave Wyrm 3 a nod, following which his time spirit domain abruptly shrank drastically in size, while a dark red spirit domain emerged at almost the exact same moment.

The two spirit domains overlapped virtually perfectly with one another, only encompassing the metal-attribute Dao Warriors within it.

As a result, Lei Yuce and the others were left exposed outside the time spirit domain, and they hurriedly channeled their immortal spiritual power with all their might to ward off the effects of the Eon Divine Lamp's time law powers.

Meanwhile, a peculiar aura began to emanate from Han Li and Wyrm 3's spirit domains, and the two spirit domains began to glow far brighter than before.

The golden spears wielded by the metal-attribute Dao Warriors trapped within the two spirit domains immediately began to dim, and the arrows of golden light that they released faded away altogether.

"It's working! Don't let them get away!" Han Li yelled in an elated manner, and the three of them immediately sprang into action, quickly eradicating all of the metal-attribute Dao Warriors with the assistance of Han Li's lightning-armored Dao Warriors.

Immediately thereafter, a resounding boom rang out elsewhere in the palace, and a burst of flames rose up into the air. It seemed that the Dao Warriors over there had been eradicated by Qi Mozi as well.

With two groups of Dao Warriors destroyed, the five-elemental array was instantly rendered incomplete, and it was only a matter of time before the rest of the Dao Warriors were going to be wiped out.

Han Li hurriedly stowed away what remained of his Dao Warriors upon seeing this, then began to rush toward the altar.

However, right at this moment, a burst of black and white light abruptly rose up from the ground, then transformed into a black and white figure that sprang over everyone, flying directly toward the altar.

It was a young woman dressed in a black and white robe. The woman was completely expressionless, and there was a layer of faint black and white light over her body.

To Han Li's surprise, even though he was able to see the woman, his spiritual sense wasn't able to detect any aura from her at all, as if she were nothing more than an illusion, and judging from everyone else's stunned reactions, it was clear that the same applied to them as well.

"A puppet imbued with yin yang law powers? That's certainly a rare sight. Which one of you does this puppet belong to?" Qi Mozi asked with a cold sneer as he swept his gaze over everyone present.

Puzzled looks appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this, and even though they had no idea who the puppet belonged to, they immediately launched themselves at the altar as well.

The yin yang puppet thrust a palm forward through the air, releasing a burst of black and white light that formed a circular, yin yang shield that was around three feet in radius. The black and white halves of the yin yang shield were revolving incessantly, and it was able to ward off the restrictive power in the air to reach the altar without any resistance.

As opposed to the golden scroll, the black, triangular tablet, or the golden lamp, the puppet was reaching for the bonded soul tablets of Qu Lin's trio.

An urgent look appeared on Fox 3's face upon seeing this, and he summoned his Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber before slashing it at the puppet from behind.

A streak of crescent-shaped crimson light immediately swept through the air toward the puppet, and in response, the puppet made a strange hand seal with its other hand, upon which a giant yin yang symbol was conjured up behind it.

The streak of crimson light struck the yin yang symbol, and the latter shuddered violently, following which piercing, crimson light exploded in all directions, slicing through the surrounding space.

However, in the next instant, the yin yang symbol began to revolve rapidly while releasing a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations, and all of the crimson light was sucked into it in the blink of an eye.

At the same time, the puppet was already reaching down to grab the three crimson tablets beneath the golden lamp.

However, right at this moment, the lamp suddenly shuddered violently as it began to glow with dazzling, golden light, and the flame at its center reared to release waves of golden fire that proliferated through the air in all directions.

The puppet was closest to the lamp, so it was naturally struck first, and it only just barely had time to conjure up another yin yang symbol in front of itself before the wave of fire crashed into its body, sending it flying over everyone's heads before tumbling to the ground, where it instantly vanished into the earth.

Lei Yuce and the others hurriedly rushed back in retreat in the face of the oncoming waves of fire, but they had been caught off guard.

Lan Yuanzi hurriedly pulled Lan Yan behind himself, then swept a sleeve through the air to summon the blue pouch, which released a wave of blue water that formed a barrier of water in front of them.

The flames clashed against the barrier of water, resulting in an explosion of blue water lightning, Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan retreated as quickly as they could before tumbling to the ground.

The latter was completely unscathed, but the former couldn't help but throw up a mouthful of blood.

"Are you alright?" Lan Yan hurriedly asked as she grabbed onto his arm to support him, and Lan Yuanzi assured her that he was fine before stowing the blue pouch away again.

Compared with them, everyone had been dealt even heavier blows, and they were all reeling from the impact.

Even the five devilish beings had been forced back in retreat, despite their formidable physical constitutions.

Xiong Shan was aware that he was the weakest out of everyone present, so he didn't even dare to approach the altar in the first place, and he had been spared of harm for his foresight.

In contrast with everyone else, Han Li and Qi Mozi were forcing their way through the waves of fire as they continued to rush toward the altar.

Han Li was surrounded by manifestations of his five time-attribute law treasures, which kept the fiery waves at bay as he forged ahead, while Qi Mozi only had his Time Severing Torch hovering before him, but it was giving off even more formidable time law power fluctuations than Han Li's law treasure manifestations.

On top of that, his cultivation base also far surpassed Han Li's, so he was able to reach the altar first.

"The Eon Divine Lamp is mine!" he chortled with glee as he reached for the lamp, grabbing onto it before attempting to pull it off the altar, but it remained completely still, as if it had taken root there.

Qi Mozi's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he released his Great Encompassment Stage in its entirety as he pulled on the lamp with all his might.

The Eon Divine Lamp finally tilted slightly, and a drop of golden lamp oil splashed out from inside before being ignited by the lamp's flame.

An alarmed look appeared on Qi Mozi's face upon seeing this, and his Time Severing Torch instantly vanished into his body at his behest.

At the same time, a layer of golden flames emerged over the length of his entire arm.

As soon as the spark spilled down onto the ground, it immediately reared up as a wave of golden fire that surged toward Qi Mozi's flame-enveloped arm.

The fire on Qi Mozi's arm was only able to resist for a moment before all of it retreated into his body, leaving his arm to be swallowed up by the wave of golden fire, and it was reduced to ashes in the blink of an eye.

Meanwhile, Han Li had also arrived on the altar, and he reached out for the other items on the altar outside of the lamp.

An alarmed look appeared on Qi Mozi's face as his incinerated arm detached itself from his body at his shoulder on its own, while he also reached out his other hand for the other items on the altar.

Han Li was able to capture the golden scroll and two of the crimson tablets, while the triangular, black tablet and the final crimson tablet fell into Qi Mozi's grasp.

Neither of them were willing to settle for this outcome, but it was too dangerous to stay on the altar, so instead of engaging each other in battle, both of them immediately darted back in retreat.

Chapter 1112: Daoist Master Dao Yin

Right at this moment, countless flashing specks of golden light appeared on the walls of the palace.

These specks of light then joined up to form a thick, golden light barrier that encompassed the entire palace, including even the ground and the ceiling.

The light barrier was so dense that it was almost opaque, and it appeared nigh indestructible.

The spatial fluctuations in the palace became more and more condensed, and it was completely isolated from the outside world, becoming a completely independent space.

At the same time, the flame in the Eon Divine Lamp on the altar began to glow far brighter than before, and the time law power fluctuations that it was giving off had also become far more formidable.

Immediately thereafter, nine fiery dragons erupted out of the lamp before pouncing at Han Li and Qi Mozi.

Having already learned the power of the lamp's fire the hard way, Qi Mozi immediately shot back in retreat, not daring to oppose the fiery dragons.

Han Li was retreating even faster than him, covering a distance of several thousand feet in a flash before landing on the ground far away from the altar.

As soon as they landed on the ground, they were immediately swarmed by the nearby Dao Warriors.

Even though the Dao Warriors' five-elemental array had been broken, there were still quite a few of them left, but they were far less powerful than before.

Han Li made a hand seal, and countless streaks of peerlessly sharp golden sword qi erupted out of his body in all directions.

A string of dull thuds rang out as the nearby Dao Warriors were sent flying back through the air to create a large, open area around Han Li, but more Dao Warriors continued to charge at him without any fear for their own safety.

Right at this moment, Wyrm 3's voice rang out.

"Come over here, Fellow Daoist Han!"

Han Li turned to discover Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 standing with their backs against one of the palace's walls, using their immortal treasures to force back all of the Dao Warriors within a radius of several dozen feet.

Han Li immediately flew over to the two of them as a streak of golden light, and Fox 3 turned to him with an intrigued expression as he said, "Impressive as always, Fellow Daoist Han. Which two bonded soul tablets did you manage to acquire?"

Han Li cast his gaze toward the pair of crimson tablets in his hand upon seeing this. In his haste to retreat from the altar, he hadn't yet inspected the tablets.

Each tablet had a tiny image etched onto it, depicting a golden beetle and a white horse.

Fox 3's expression instantly darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he turned his gaze to Qi Mozi.

Wyrm 3 didn't seem to be interested in the three items that Han Li had claimed from the altar, and she also turned her gaze to Qi Mozi, who had already retreated back to join the five devilish beings.

His incinerated arm was still burning, and the golden flame was rapidly making its way toward his shoulder, incinerating all of the flesh and bone along the way.

"Chief Warden, your arm!" Xiong Shan exclaimed.

"Calm down, it's just a minor injury," Qi Mozi harrumphed, then opened his mouth to release a small, golden sword.

The golden sword sliced through his shoulder, severing a small chunk of flesh, following which the wound was immediately shrouded in a layer of golden light to prevent bleeding.

As soon as the chunk of flesh left his body, it immediately erupted into flames and was burned into ashes.

Qi Mozi then promptly devoured a green pill, and he was able to quickly regrow a new arm that was identical to the previous one.

Han Li turned his gaze away from Qi Mozi to assess the battlefield, and in doing so, he discovered that the Lan siblings were locked in battle against some Dao Warriors nearby, but Lei Yuce, Wen Zhong, and Su Anqian were nowhere to be seen.

Han Li was just about to release his spiritual sense to search for the trio when they appeared directly above the altar amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, and they were joined by an elderly man dressed in a daoist robe.

The man was holding a palm-sized golden talisman, upon which was etched the image of a golden lamp that was identical to the Eon Divine Lamp.

The golden talisman was giving off radiant, golden light that contained formidable time law power fluctuations identical to the ones being given off by the Eon Divine Lamp, and the talisman flew through the air as a streak of golden light at the elderly man's behest, vanishing into the Eon Divine Lamp in a flash.

The flame in the lamp instantly shrank down to its original size, while everyone else in the palace looked on with stunned expressions.

"That's Daoist Master Dao Yin, the master of the Almighty Sword Sect!" Wyrm 3 exclaimed.

The five devilish beings shuddered slightly in fear upon hearing this, while Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan also distanced themselves further from Daoist Master Dao Yin with fearful looks on their faces.

Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly upon hearing this. After arriving in the Golden Origin Immortal Region, he had naturally taken it upon himself to learn about this immortal region, and he had certainly looked into a major sect like the Almighty Sword Sect.

Daoist Master Dao Yin of the Almighty Sword Sect was extremely renowned in the Golden Origin Immortal Region, and it was no exaggeration to say that his reputation exceeded even that of Dongfang Bai.

Not only was he a Great Encompassment cultivator, he had an extremely fiery and unyielding personality, and he was renowned for his bitter resentment of all forces of evil.

It was said that he had been in seclusion for a very long time, attempting to sever his first corpse soul, and it was unclear whether he had succeeded in this endeavor.

How did Daoist Master Dao Yin manage to get in here?

The entrance of the palace was already closed, and even a Great Encompassment cultivator wouldn't have been able to sneak in easily. Could it be that this had something to do with that yin yang puppet from earlier?

Before long, the answer was revealed by Lei Yuce, who chanted an incantation before sweeping a sleeve through the air to conjure up a spatial door.

Han Li was very familiar with spatial doors like this as it was the entrance to a spatial treasure.

Three figures, two men and a woman, flew out of the spatial door to join Lei Yuce's group at the top of the altar, and judging from the attire, it was clear that they were all cultivators of the Almighty Sword Sect.

The two men consisted of a yellow-skinned elderly man and a red-haired young man, while the woman was quite youthful in appearance and had a pea-sized green gemstone embedded into her glabella, giving her a sense of exotic allure.

The three of them were all mid-High Zenith cultivators.

"What is the meaning of this, Fellow Daoist Lei?" Wyrm 3 asked in a grim voice.

Lei Yuce remained silent, while Daoist Master Dao Yin swept a resentful gaze over everyone in the palace as he said in a cold voice, "All of you scoundrels have been recklessly taking treasures from this place with no regard for the consequences! This is where you die for your transgressions!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a jade plate roughly the size that was roughly a foot in diameter.

The plate was split up into five sections, each of which was a different color, namely golden, green, blue, red, and yellow, and there were many runes engraved onto each section, giving it the appearance of a profound treasure.

Everyone collectively backed away a few steps with wary looks on their faces upon seeing this.

In contrast with everyone else, a look of bewilderment appeared on Qi Mozi's face at the sight of the five-colored plate, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a virtually identical five-colored plate of his own.

A derisive sneer appeared on Daoist Master Dao Yin's face upon seeing this, and he made a hand seal while chanting a complex incantation.

The five-colored plate before him instantly began to radiate, golden, green, blue, red, and yellow light in an alternating fashion, while Qi Mozi was also attempting to activate his own five-colored plate, but to his surprise, it displayed no reaction.

All of a sudden, the ground near the altar began to rumble violently as five massive jade pillars that were over a thousand feet tall and around forty to fifty feet in diameter rose up from the ground.

Lei Yuce and Su Anqian flew onto the golden and blue pillars, respectively, before sitting down with their legs crossed, while the three Almighty Sword Sect cultivators that had just appeared flew onto the remaining three pillars, leaving only Wen Zhong standing behind Daoist Master Dao Yin.

His gaze fell upon the five people on the jade pillars, particularly lingering on Lei Yuce for a brief moment, and in that moment, a hint of envy and dissatisfaction flashed through his eyes.

After Lei Yuce and the others had sat down, they each made a rapid string of hands seals, injecting dense streams of incantation seals into the jade pillars beneath them.

The spirit patterns on the five pillars instantly lit up, forming five thick pillars of light that erupted into the heavens.

A tremendous aura rose up from within the five pillars of light before sweeping through the air in all directions, causing the nearby space to ripple slightly.

All of the Dao Warriors in the palace were swept up like falling leaves in a fierce storm, crashing heavily into the walls of the palace.

Han Li and the others were also forced to stumble back by the formidable storm, and only when their backs hit the walls behind them were they able to steady themselves.

Qi Mozi was the only one who remained standing on the spot, and he continued to try and activate the five-colored plate before him, but it remained unresponsive.

"Give it up, you fool!" Daoist Master Dao Yin sneered. "That five-elemental plate of yours may have been able to control the array from before, but it can't control the current Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array!"

A look of realization appeared on Qi Mozi's face upon hearing this, and his complexion paled slightly as he exclaimed, "You altered the structure of the array while repairing the array cores!"

"So it seems like you're not a complete idiot. It was clear to us that the Heavenly Court was definitely going to send someone to infiltrate the newly opened Tai Sui Immortal Manor, so we prepared accordingly," Daoist Master Dao Yin gloated as he continued to make hand seals with more urgency, and the five pillars of light grew brighter and brighter while beginning to display signs of fusing together.

Chapter 1113: Trapped

Wyrm 3's expression changed drastically at the mention of the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, and she hurriedly called out in a panic, "We can't let them activate the array!"

The dark red light around her brightened significantly as she spoke, and she began flying toward the five pillars of light while resisting the fierce storm raging in the palace.

Neither Han Li nor Fox 3 had heard of this array before, but Wyrm 3's reaction told them that it was not to be taken lightly, and they immediately followed along behind her.

A cold sneer appeared on Daoist Master Dao Yin's face, and he didn't appear to be concerned in the slightest as he swept his golden talisman through the air.

The flame in the Eon Divine Lamp instantly reared up once again, and nine fiery, golden dragons re-emerged, then swelled rapidly to several dozen times their original size before pouncing at Han Li's trio.

Having already witnessed the power of these fiery dragons, Han Li's trio hurriedly attempted to take evasive measures, but right at this moment, a sly grin appeared on Wyrm 3's face as she swept her right hand through the air, releasing a large, yellow seal.

The seal passed through a gap in between the nine fiery dragons, appearing before the five jade pillars in the blink of an eye.

Wyrm 3 chanted a rapid incantation while pointing a finger at the seal, and a resounding thump rang out as the seal released a burst of astonishing spiritual pressure, coupled with blinding, yellow light that contained layers upon layers of profound and complex yellow runes.

These runes vanished into the seal in a flash, causing it to swell rapidly to the size of a small mountain, taking up close to half of the space in the palace as it crashed toward the five jade pillars with unstoppable might.

Compared with the enormous yellow seal, the five jade pillars were made to appear like mere chopsticks.

"I'm afraid this is not the right place to be using the Vast Earth Seal," Daoist Master Dao Yin remarked in an indifferent manner as he pointed a finger at the yellow jade pillar, and a burst of yellow light instantly split off from it to strike the yellow seal.

As soon as the seal came into contact with this streak of yellow light, it quickly shrank down to its original size, then flew into the pillar of yellow light, where it revolved incessantly above the yellow-faced elderly man's head.

A stunned look appeared on Wyrm 3's face upon seeing this.

"Those five immortal treasures that you took are all a part of the array to begin with. Otherwise, why do you think we allowed you to claim these treasures so easily? It's time for you to cough those treasures back up now!" Daoist Master Dao Yin sneered as he laid a palm down onto the five-colored jade plate, which immediately lit up, as did the five pillars of light.

All of a sudden, the Primordial Ancient Sword in Xiong Shan's hand began to glow radiantly before flying out of his grasp toward the pillar of yellow light in the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, and it refused to return to him despite his frantic efforts to recover it.

The blue pouch in Lan Yan's hand also lit up before flying out of her grasp toward the pillar of blue light, while a green cane that was over two feet in length flew out of Lan Yuanzi's storage treasure without any warning before flying toward the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array as well.

At the same time, the white bead emerged beside Han Li amid a burst of spatial fluctuations before flying through the air, and he immediately reached out to make a grab for it.

A giant, golden hand appeared above the bead before closing itself around it, but the white bead released several pillars of fire that tore through the giant hand before eradicating it with ease.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the white bead flew into the pillar of red light in a flash, while the other three immortal treasures also flew into the golden, blue, and green pillars of light, where they circled around in the air above Lei Yuce and the others.

Bolstered by these five immortal treasures, the five pillars of light lit up even further while giving off astonishing law power fluctuations.

Meanwhile, Daoist Master Dao Yin set down the golden talisman in his hand, then opened his mouth to release several globules of blood essence that fused into the five-colored plate before him.

At the same time, he cast a rapid string of incantation seals into the plate, and Lei Yuce and the others followed his lead, opening their mouths to release their blood essence into the immortal treasures above their heads.

The five-colored light emanating from the five-colored plate flashed erratically for a moment before abruptly fading away, while the five pillars of light intertwined with one another to form a spherical, five-colored light barrier that encompassed the altar alongside Su Anqian and all of the Almighty Sword Sect cultivators.

This sequence of events had unfolded in the span of mere seconds, and Han Li and others were powerless to stop it.

Meanwhile, a drastic change was also taking place outside the Eon Palace.

A resounding boom rang out from each of the five array cores on the giant mountain, and they each released a thick pillar of light that was countless times thicker than the pillars of light in the Eon Palace.

The clouds up above instantly began to churn violently, while the entire seventh level also began to tremble and quake.

All of the world's origin qi in the entire level surged into the five gargantuan pillars of light, and a vast, five-colored, spherical light barrier began to slowly emerge around the five pillars of light, encompassing the entirety of the enormous mountain down below.

A burst of unfathomable power began emanating from the five-colored light barrier, and even a slight ripple in this power was enough to shatter the nearby space.

At this point, all of the unrest taking place in the Eon Palace had already ceased, and all of the spiritual qi inside had fused into the five-colored light barrier.

A series of five-colored spirit patterns appeared on the light barrier, giving off a gentle, five-colored glow that appeared to be completely innocuous.

However, Han Li was struck by an intense sense of foreboding at the sight of the five-colored light barrier.

All of a sudden, the Almighty Sword Diagram in his storage tool began to glow radiantly, as if it were competing against the five-colored light barrier.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, but given the urgency of the situation, there were more pressing concerns for him to worry about.

"Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, you seem to be quite familiar with this Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, what kind of array is it?" he asked through voice transmission so that his voice was audible only to Wyrm 3 and Fox 3.

"The Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array is one of the ten supreme ancient arrays, but it's been lost for countless years, so very few people know of it. This array doesn't appear to be complete, and it's only just barely able to function thanks to the five immortal treasures, but even so, the array is most likely going to be far too powerful for us to resist," Wyrm 3 replied with a grim expression.

"What do we do then?" Fox 3 asked in an urgent manner.

"At this point, all we can do is hold on and hope for the best," Wyrm 3 replied with a heavy heart.

The color slowly drained from Fox 3's face upon hearing this, and a grim look had also appeared on Han Li's face, but he was able to stave off the grips of despair as he swept his gaze over the surrounding palace.

Daoist Master Dao Yin clearly intended to kill everyone in one fell swoop, but there was no way that Qi Mozi and the five devilish beings would simply roll over and allow themselves to be slain.

If all of them could join forces, then they would stand a much better chance at survival, but Daoist Master Dao Yin had clearly already assessed the situation and determined that there was no way that everyone present could work together.

"Fellow Daoist Qi Mozi, didn't you tell us that you can capture the Eon Divine Lamp and control the array in this place? What's going on here?" the White Bone King asked in a cold voice through voice transmission, while the other devilish beings also turned to him with accusatory looks in their eyes.

Qi Mozi had told them that he could control everything in the Eon Palace, and that once they arrived in this place, they would be able to easily kill Han Li and the others, after which Qi Mozi would split half of their treasures with the five devilish beings.

The five devilish beings had accompanied Qi Mozi here as they were extremely confident in their own powers, but things hadn't gone according to plan at all.

Qi Mozi remained silent with a dark look on his face.

Meanwhile, Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan had backed away even further from the altar, arriving near the entrance of the palace, but they chose not to approach Han Li's trio or Qi Mozi's group, clearly not trusting any of them.

At this point, Daoist Master Dao Yin had already stopped what he was doing.

His complexion was rather pale, indicating that he had exerted himself quite severely in activating the array, but there was a fervent look of excitement in his eyes, and he turned to Han Li and the others with a derisive sneer as he swept a sleeve through the air.

The five-colored light barrier around him immediately lit up, following which countless head-sized balls of light flew out from within before hurtling toward everyone in the palace.

These balls of light were flashing with five-colored radiance, and each type of light was giving off law powers corresponding with one of the five elements.

The five types of law powers were conflicting violently with one another, but they didn't completely erupt. Even so, the destructive aura being released by the conflicting law powers still struck fear deep into everyone's hearts, and they hurriedly adopted measures to defend themselves.

The five devilish beings revealed their true, devilish forms while unleashing their spirit domains in unison, and the five spirit domains intertwined with one another to form an ovular black array with five giant, black beastly projections inside, serving as the domain spirits.

The five domain spirits were extremely formidable, blasting arcs of black lightning and torrents of black, devilish flames out of their mouths to significantly bolster the five spirit domains.

This combination of their spirit domains was one of their most powerful trump cards, and in addition to that, the five devilish beings had opened their mouths to release a vast array of close to a hundred devilish treasures, all of which were giving off incredibly formidable devilish qi fluctuations.

The five spirit domains didn't encompass Qi Mozi and Xiong Shan, perhaps because the five devilish beings were resentful of Qi Mozi for his inability to follow through on his promises.

Chapter 1114: Casualties

A cold sneer appeared on Qi Mozi's face upon seeing this, and he didn't appear concerned in the slightest.

A burst of golden light erupted out of his body, forming a golden spirit domain that was over a hundred feet in size to encompass both himself and Xiong Shan.

The spirit domain was extremely dense, making it impossible to see what was happening inside from the outside.

The water law powers cultivated by the Lan siblings excelled in defense, so they had been quite confident in their ability to ward off the attacks of the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array on their own, and that was why they had chosen to act on their own.

However, their expressions instantly changed slightly upon sensing the power of these five-colored balls of light, and they hurriedly released their spirit domains before combining them together.

Plumes of blue law threads flew out of their bodies before intertwining with one another to form a blue vortex around them, and two domain spirits appeared beside the vortex, both of which had humanoid upper bodies paired with serpentine, with each of them wielding a blue trident.

The two domain spirits rapidly revolved around Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan while swinging their tridents through the air to release countless arcs of blue water lightning.

Meanwhile, Han Li's trio had also set up some defenses.

Fox 3 was the first one to spring into action, releasing his spirit domain while also summoning his Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber.

He opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence into the saber, and it immediately began to glow with incandescent crimson light while swelling drastically to several hundred feet in size.

At the same time, he made an urgent string of hand seals, and the giant, crimson saber transformed into a light barrier around the trio.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 had also unfurled her spirit domain, and four streaks of dark red light flew out of her body before landing around the spirit domain, where they revealed themselves to be four dark red archways.

The archways had the characters for north, south, east, and west inscribed upon them, and they were releasing countless rays of dark red light that intertwined to form a protective light barrier.

As for Han Li, he had also released his time spirit domain, and it encompassed an area that was only less than two hundred feet in size, forming the innermost layer of defense.

At the same time, the Profound Heavenly Gourd appeared above his head, following which thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew out from within to form a defensive sword array.

Immediately thereafter, the barrage of five-colored balls of light came crashing down, and they exploded violently as soon as they came into contact with the defenses that everyone had set up.

The entire palace was instantly inundated by dazzling, five-colored radiance, but the golden light barrier around the palace remained completely unmoved.

The crimson saber barrier conjured up by Fox 3 was the first to be destroyed by the balls of five-colored light, and it was barely able to pose any resistance.

The destroyed light barrier reverted back into the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, and it quickly returned to its original size before flying back into Fox 3's grasp with an anguished wail.

The spirit domain around Fox 3 also exploded in the face of the oncoming barrage, and he shuddered violently as he stumbled back while throwing up a mouthful of blood.

The barrage of five-colored light then struck Wyrm 3's spirit domain, and she immediately released a flurry of dark red law threads, which split up into six batches that transformed into six rapidly revolving holes.

The holes were pitch-black and completely devoid of light, looking as if they led straight into the depths of hell.

The balls of five-colored light struck the dark red light barrier, causing it to tremble violently, and the outermost parts of the spirit domain immediately began to disintegrate.

However, Wyrm 3's spirit domain was far more resilient than Fox 3's, and the six black holes were releasing tremendous suction force, devouring much of the destructive five-colored light while also nullifying the explosive five-elemental law powers within them.

However, there were simply too many of these balls of five-colored light, and the six black holes were quickly overwhelmed, following which the entire spirit domain exploded violently.

The wave of five-colored light then struck the light barrier formed by the four archways, which began to flash erratically while giving off law power fluctuations that were far more formidable than those of Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The dark red light barrier was trembling violently, but it was able to keep the five-colored light at bay.

However, it was only able to do so for a few seconds before it also crumbled, causing Wyrm 3 to throw up a mouthful of blood as her aura diminished significantly.

After overwhelming the dark red light barrier, the five-colored light swarmed over the four archways, then continued onward without pause.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and over two hundred time law threads flew out of his body before revolving through the air within his time spirit domain, significantly bolstering it in the process.

At the same time, his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him, then released countless waves of golden ripples that fused as one with his spirit domain.

As soon as the wave of five-colored light surged into his time spirit domain, it was instantly stopped cold in its tracks by the opposing time law powers.

However, the five-colored light was imbued with unfathomable power, and the time spirit domain and Mantra Treasured Axis quickly began to tremble violently, looking as if they could be overwhelmed at any moment.

Han Li had encountered a similar scenario in the Almighty Sword Array, but this Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array was a far more powerful array, and it had almost instantly overwhelmed his Mantra Treasured Axis.

Despite this, Han Li remained unflustered as he quickly made a hand seal, and his four other time-attribute law treasures emerged in unison, then began releasing radiant, golden light that infused itself into the time spirit domain.

The wavering spirit domain was instantly stabilized, completely immobilizing all of the five-colored light that had surged into it.

Immediately thereafter, the sword array formed by the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords sprang into action at his behest, and countless streaks of peerlessly sharp sword qi swept through the spirit domain, eradicating much of the five-colored light.

At the same time, his Profound Heavenly Gourd began to glow radiantly, and it released a burst of green light that swept toward what remained of the five-colored light in the time spirit domain.

All of the remaining five-colored light was instantly sucked into the Profound Heavenly Gourd, and even though more and more five-colored light continued to surge into the time spirit domain, it continued to be immobilized, eradicated, and devoured.

Finally, the five-colored light in the palace faded away, revealing the aftermath of the barrage.

Over at the entrance of the palace, Lan Yan's entire body was drenched in blood, and she was seated on the ground, missing her left hand, left foot, and close to half of her body.

However, she paid no heed to her own injuries as she stared blankly down at a blue jade flower in her right hand with tears streaming down her cheeks.

Lan Yuanzi was nowhere to be seen, and all that was left of him was a pair of destroyed immortal treasures.

The combined spirit domains of the five devilish beings had also been destroyed, and on top of that, the Copper Lion King and the Blood Hand King had also disappeared, while the three remaining devilish beings were all carrying severe injuries and had looks of shock and horror on their faces.

There was a ball of bright, golden light beside them, and it dissipated to reveal Qi Mozi and Xiong Shan, both of whom were completely unscathed.

Inside the five-colored light barrier, Daoist Master Dao Yin's complexion had paled even further, and the same applied to Lei Yuce and the others as well.

Han Li withdrew his time-attribute law treasures, and Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 were a little unsteady on their feet, but they were very relieved to have survived the ordeal.

Daoist Master Dao Yin was clearly rather surprised to see that so many people were still alive, and a hint of killing intent appeared in his eyes as he pointed a finger at the five-colored jade plate before him.

A grim look appeared on Wyrm 3's face upon seeing this, and she turned to Han Li and Fox 3 as she communicated through voice transmission, "At this rate, all of us are going to die here. I have a way to turn the tables, but I'm going to need your help."

Han Li immediately realized what Wyrm 3's intentions were, and he asked, "Are you suggesting that we free that devilish deity?"

"We can't do that! There's a good chance that that devilish deity is a Dao Ancestor, so we'll only be jumping out of the frying pan and into the fire!" Fox 3 exclaimed.

"We have no choice! Also, I'm at least 70% confident that I can keep him from attacking us," Wyrm 3 replied, and Han Li's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this.

For some reason, he had a feeling that freeing the devilish deity here was the best course of action. In fact, he had been struck by this feeling from the instant that he arrived in this place, but he had suppressed it this entire time.

Indeed, just as Wyrm 3 had said, they hardly had a choice in the matter.

The Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array was clearly far too powerful for them to resist, and if everyone else here were killed, he was far from confident in his own ability to oppose the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array and the Almighty Sword Sect cultivators on his own.

As for the consequences of releasing that devilish deity, that was something that he didn't want to think about.

Chapter 1115: Breakthrough

"What do you think, Brother Han?" Fox 3 asked as he turned to Han Li.

"Releasing the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity is going to be very risky, but if Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3 has a way to keep him from attacking us, then I think it's a feasible solution," Han Li replied as an inexplicable sense of urgency welled up in his heart.

Fox 3 was clearly quite surprised that Han Li had chosen to side with Wyrm 3, and he said, "I still think this isn't a sound plan. According to what Lei Yuce said, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity is far more powerful than us, so what happens if we release him, only to be unable to control him? In my opinion, it would be best to break the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, then try to resolve things peacefully with Daoist Master Dao Yin."

"You need to have more confidence in me," Wyrm 3 said as her brows furrowed slightly with displeasure. "Having said that, seeing as you insist on exploring other options first, then let's try and deal with the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array for now. If the situation doesn't take a turn for the better, then we can resort to our backup plan of freeing the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity."

"Alright," Fox 3 acquiesced.

"Regardless of which course of action we choose to take, our top priority right now has to be to break through this light barrier, and that's not going to be an easy task to accomplish," Han Li interjected.

"You can rest assured on that front, Fellow Daoist Han. I've already planted something in the Vast Earth Seal that allows me to disrupt the law powers within the seal for a duration of five seconds at will. Those five fourth-tier immortal treasures are the foundation of the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, so if something goes wrong with the Vast Earth Seal, then the light barrier will definitely be left vulnerable," Wyrm 3 said with a sly gleam in her eyes.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, and only now did he realize that those were five fourth-tier immortal treasures. Given the tremendous power of the immortal treasures, he had thought that they would've been at the third tier.

With that in mind, he couldn't help but heave a forlorn internal sigh. He had been cultivating on his own for all these years, and even though his cultivation base had been progressing smoothly, he was severely lacking in experience when compared with someone like Wyrm 3, who had been nurtured by a major power.

Wyrm 3 had noticed the change in Han Li's expression, and she asked, "Is there something wrong, Fellow Daoist Han?"

"Not at all," Han Li replied with a shake of his head. "Time is of the essence, so let's begin."

Wyrm 3 nodded in response, and the three of them quickly discussed the strategy that they were going to adopt.

Shortly thereafter, the time spirit domain around Han Li expanded rapidly to encompass the entire palace and everyone within it, following which Han Li's trio pounced at the altar from three different directions at once.

The five-colored jade plate in front of Daoist Master Dao Yin had only just lit up again when Han Li's trio launched themselves at the altar.

The three of them were traveling at an astonishing speed, and reaching the five-colored light barrier in the blink of an eye.

A cold sneer appeared on Daoist Master Dao Yin's face upon seeing this, and the five-colored light barrier instantly began to glow radiantly at his behest.

Even though he had been enshrouded in Han Li's time spirit domain, his movements hadn't slowed down at all, and somehow, Han Li's time law powers were also proving to be completely ineffective on the five-colored light barrier as well.

Han Li was rather bewildered to see this, but before he had a chance to ponder the situation, another flurry of balls of five-colored light erupted out of the light barrier.

Perhaps it was because this was a rather rushed barrage from Daoist Master Dao Yin, but the number of balls of light was far fewer than that of the previous wave.

Initially, these balls of light were as fast as ever, but after flying for some distance, they suddenly slowed down to a crawl.

A perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, only to be replaced by a look of realization as his gaze fell upon the Eon Divine Lamp beside Daoist Master Dao Yin.

It seemed that everything within a certain range of the Eon Divine Lamp was able to remain unaffected by his time spirit domain.

With that in mind, it occurred to him that the Eon Divine Lamp was even more profound and powerful than he had anticipated, and he couldn't help but wonder how many time law threads he would be able to attain from refining it.

Even at a conservative estimate, the number surely had to be in excess of a thousand.

All of a sudden, an irrational urge to obtain the Eon Divine Lamp at all costs welled up in his heart, and he was startled by the intensity of this urge.

He hurriedly suppressed this impulsive thought, returning his attention to the crisis at hand.

There was still some agitation in his heart, but he had no time to address that for now.

In the face of the oncoming balls of five-colored light, he continued onward without pause while sweeping a sleeve through the air to release the Almighty Sword Array diagram.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 immediately sprang back in retreat without any hesitation.

They had only pounced forward as a bluff in the first place so that Daoist Master Dao Yin's attention wouldn't be entirely focused on Han Li, and now that they had successfully attracted some of the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array's firepower, they had accomplished their objective.

Even though there were fewer balls of light than in the previous wave, this was still too ferocious a barrage for them to withstand.

Daoist Master Dao Yin's expression changed drastically at the sight of the Almighty Sword Array diagram, and he frantically made a string of hand seals, upon which all of the balls of light shooting out of the five-colored light barrier veered away from Han Li in a desperate attempt to avoid striking the array diagram.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this. Just as he had predicted, the array diagram was of sufficient importance to the Almighty Sword Sect that it could serve as an effective shield for him.

Immediately thereafter, he abruptly accelerated to roughly twice his original speed, instantly flying through the storm of balls of light to arrive before the five-colored light barrier.

He then stowed the array diagram before thrusting his palms forward, and all of his time law threads erupted out of his body, while the time spirit domain around him also began to glow radiantly.

A metallic clang rang out as a giant, golden sword that was around a hundred feet in length and roughly five feet wide appeared in his hands.

The sword was enshrouded in a layer of fiery, golden light that was as bright as the sun, and Han Li swung the sword down with all his might, aiming it at a section of the five-colored light barrier near the yellow jade pillar.

A derisive sneer surfaced in Daoist Master Dao Yin's eyes upon seeing this, and he pointed a finger at the Vast Earth Seal above the yellow jade pillar.

The seal released a thick pillar of yellow light at his behest, and the yellow light surged into the section of the five-colored light barrier in front of Han Li, significantly bolstering it.

All of a sudden, Wyrm 3 abruptly stopped in her retreat, then began making a rapid string of hand seals, and a layer of dark red light suddenly appeared over the surface of the Vast Earth Seal, cutting off the pillar of yellow light that it was releasing.

The yellow-faced elderly man seated on top of the yellow jade pillar was very much taken aback by this, and he hurriedly made a string of hand seals to try and free the Vast Earth Seal from the restrictive layer of dark red light, but to no avail.

At the same time, the section of the five-colored light barrier near the yellow jade pillar began to rapidly thin out, to the point that it had almost disappeared altogether.

The balls of five-colored light hurtling through the air also disintegrated into specks of spiritual light, and before any of the Almighty Sword Sect cultivators had a chance to do anything, Han Li's giant, golden sword had already struck the vulnerable area on the light barrier.

A loud, tearing sound rang out as a rift that was dozens of feet in length was sliced into the light barrier, much to the elation of Wyrm 3.

She began to chant an urgent incantation, and her spirit domain also erupted out of her body to encompass the entire palace.

Immediately thereafter, she launched herself at the rift in the light barrier as a streak of dark red light.

At the same time, Fox 3 summoned his Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, then transformed into a streak of gray light that adhered itself to the saber, which shot forth toward the rift in the light barrier at an even faster speed than Wyrm 3.

The expressions of Qi Mozi, Xiong Shan, and the remaining three devilish beings changed slightly upon seeing this, and the Turtle Back King turned to the Eagle Nose King as he asked through voice transmission, "This is a great opportunity to destroy the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array! Should we help them?"

"There's no need for that. The ideal outcome would be for them to wipe out each other. None of the humans here are to be trusted. While those three are drawing all of the firepower to themselves, we should take this opportunity to find a way out of here," the Eagle Nose King replied.

A hesitant look appeared on the Turtle Back King's face upon hearing this.

"He's right! This place is far too dangerous for us. We should've never believed Qi Mozi's lies! We've already lost two brothers here, it would be foolish to stay any longer!" the White Bone King urged in a grief-stricken manner.

"Alright, in that case, let's see if we can find any weak points in the light barrier around this palace," the Turtle Back King replied.

Right as the three devilish beings were about to depart, a cold voice suddenly rang out beside them.

"You three are not going anywhere!"

Immediately thereafter, a golden spirit domain fell upon them, and Qi Mozi was hovering in the air above them with a mocking sneer on his face.

"What's the meaning of this, Qi Mozi?" the Eagle Nose King yelled as he struggled against the spirit domain with all his might, but to no avail.

Chapter 1116: No Time to Waste

Qi Mozi offered no response to the Eagle Nose King aside from to erupt into laughter, and a vast expanse of golden light rose up within his spirit domain at his behest, then converged above the three devilish beings to form a projection of a golden man that was several hundred feet tall.

The man had a draconic lower body and the upper body of a middle-aged man with a coarse beard and thick, golden chest hair. There was a fiery, golden fan held in the man's hand, and he was giving off an air of unmatched authority.

The man reached out toward the three devilish beings with one hand, and a burst of tremendous pressure instantly crashed down upon them, completely immobilizing them and rendering them unable to utter even a single sound.

"I went out of my way to lure all of you here, and my intention was to claim all of you, but it looks like I'll have to make do with just the three of you," Qi Mozi chuckled as he swept a sleeve through the air, and a crimson cane with a nine-headed demonic dragon engraved onto its head flew out from behind him.

Seven of the draconic heads were giving off bright, crimson light, while the other two were dull and completely devoid of luster.

As soon as the cane appeared, fierce gusts of yin wind instantly rose up around it, and a burst of bone-chilling demonic power began to emanate from the cane, unrestricted even by the surrounding time spirit domain.

Qi Mozi chanted an incantation before pointing a finger at the cane, which released a burst of crimson light that encompassed the three devilish beings.

Bursts of crimson light began to surge out of their bodies and into the cane, and their bodies quickly became dried and withered, while the two demonic dragon heads on the cane began to glow with radiant, crimson light.

......

Meanwhile, Han Li had just flown through the rift in the five-colored light barrier, and he hurled his giant, golden sword through the air, sending it flying toward the yellow jade pillar nearby.

A furious look appeared on Daoist Master Dao Yin's face as he pointed a finger at the golden talisman in his hand, and a thick beam of golden light instantly erupted out of the lamp image on the talisman.

The image of the lamp instantly dimmed significantly, and the time law power fluctuations emanating from it had also become a lot weaker.

The beam of golden light shot into the Eon Divine Lamp, and two bursts of golden flames instantly erupted out of it.

One of them transformed into a fiery, golden dragon with a series of time dao runes all over its body, and it appeared before the yellow jade pillar at an astonishing speed before reaching out with its claws to grab at the giant, golden sword.

As soon as the sword was caught in its grasp, the golden dragon wrapped its own body around the sword light lightning while blasting a jet of golden flames into the sword, causing it to rapidly melt at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

Meanwhile, the other burst of golden flames descended in front of the altar, where it transformed into a fiery, golden barrier.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and he stopped in his tracks.

Daoist Master Dao Yin heaved a faint sigh of relief, then turned his gaze to Han Li with a hint of killing intent in his eyes.

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the to release a streak of dazzling, white light that shot forth at Han Li at an incredible speed.

There wasn't much distance separating the two of them, so the streak of white light was able to reach Han Li as if by instantaneous teleportation.

In response, Han Li conjured up his True Extreme Film while crossing his arms to form a defensive barrier in front of himself.

At the same time, thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew out of his body to form a golden sword barrier.

At the moment, he was in close proximity to the Eon Divine Lamp, which had already displayed its capability of nullifying his time spirit domain, so he wasn't sure if his time-attribute law treasures would be able to function here. Hence, he could only seek out alternative defensive measures.

Before Han Li had a chance to do anything else, the streak of white light struck the golden sword barrier with a resounding boom, and the latter was instantly shattered, while the former continued onward without pause to strike Han Li's arms.

Han Li was instantly sent flying back through the air, only to draw to a shuddering halt as his back struck the five-colored light barrier.

A burst of intense pain shot up his arms, as if the bones inside had been fractured, and he hurriedly channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts to bolster his own physical constitution.

To further compound his woes, the streak of white light came hurtling toward him once again, and it was glowing even brighter than before.

Han Li hurriedly stepped to the side to dodge the attack while sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of green light that captured the streak of white light.

The streak of white light was instantly slowed down drastically as a result, but in the next instant, it released countless needle-like bursts of white light in all directions, which tore the surrounding green light apart, following which it continued to hurtle toward Han Li.

However, Han Li had already bought enough time for himself, and his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords circled around through the air before hurtling toward the streak of white light as arcs of golden lightning.

At the same time, he adopted his Giant Mountain Ape form, transforming into a giant, golden ape in the blink of an eye.

A string of loud, metallic clangs rang out as the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords struck the streak of white light in rapid succession, while the golden ape let loose a thunderous roar before swinging its massive fists down onto the streak of white light with tremendous power.

The streak of white light was finally knocked back, but the golden ape was also sent stumbling back with its fists severely ravaged and bloodied.

At this point, Han Li was able to identify the streak of white light as a small, white sword, but it was several times thicker than the average flying sword, giving it a rather strange, dull appearance.

However, it was giving off astonishing law power fluctuations that were inferior to those of the five immortal treasures in the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, but not by much.

A look of surprise and agitation appeared in Daoist Master Dao Yin's eyes, clearly caught off guard by the fact that Han Li had managed to withstand his attack with only such minor injuries to show for it, and he was just about to urge the white sword to spring into action again when Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 flew through the rift in the five-colored light barrier before pouncing at the altar.

Daoist Master Dao Yin hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air upon seeing this, releasing a golden spirit domain that expanded rapidly toward Han Li's trio.

The spirit domain was giving off metal law powers that were far more formidable than the law powers mastered by Han Li's trio, and even before encompassing them, it was already exerting immense pressure upon them.

Fox 3 immediately stopped in his tracks, then flipped a hand over to summon his Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, and at the same time, a gray spirit domain erupted out of his body.

He let loose a low roar as the gray spirit domain contracted rapidly to form a fist-sized ball of gray light, which vanished into the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber in a flash.

One of the four eyes on the two fox heads etched onto the guard of the saber instantly began to glow with bright, crimson light, following which a burst of tremendous power erupted out of the saber, as if it had finally awakened after a long slumber.

The entire saber began to glow radiantly, illuminating everything within the light barrier a crimson color, and Shi Qinghou emerged within the crimson light, making a rapid string of hand seals while countless crimson runes surged out of the saber.

Fox 3 let loose a loud roar as he swung the saber through the air with both hands, unleashing an all-encompassing wave of crimson light that contained extremely formidable law power fluctuations, ones that weren't inferior in the slightest to those in Daoist Master Dao Yin's spirit domain.

The wave of crimson light struck the golden spirit domain, and the projection of Shi Qinghou swelled to over a thousand feet tall before pressing its hands down onto the golden spirit domain.

The spirit domain's expansion was instantly stopped, unable to spread even an inch further.

After unleashing that saber strike, Fox 3's complexion instantly turned deathly pale, and all of the immortal spiritual power had been drained from his body.

He fell to one knee as his saber-wielding hand trembled uncontrollably, while Daoist Master Dao Yin looked on with a stunned expression.

He hurriedly made a hand seal, and the dull, white sword swelled to several hundred feet in size at his behest, then began sweeping through the air toward Han Li's trio.

Right at this moment, Han Li abruptly appeared before the giant, white sword, having already reverted back to his human form.

All of a sudden, the huge, golden sword that had been ensnared by the fiery, golden dragon exploded violently at his behest, and the force of the explosion was enough to send the fiery dragon flying back through the air.

Over two hundred time law threads shot out of the explosion, then vanished into thin air, only to reappear beside Han Li an instant later.

Han Li began to chant an incantation while making a string of hand seals, and the time law threads intertwined to reform a giant, golden sword to oppose the oncoming white sword.

Chapter 1117: Abrupt Awakening

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the two giant swords clashed, and Han Li was able to keep the white sword at bay, but he was sent flying back through the air from the force of the impact, throwing up a mouthful of blood in the process.

With his time law powers severely suppressed by the Eon Divine Lamp, he was no match for a Great Encompassment cultivator.

However, despite the fact that he had come out on top in that clash, Daoist Master Dao Yin was stunned to see that Han Li managed to survive that attack, and he was also astonished by the seemingly endless bag of tricks that Han Li was able to pull from.

Wyrm 3 paid no heed to the clash taking place between Han Li and Daoist Master Dao Yin as she sped toward the five-colored altar, but at the moment, the altar was enshrouded within a fiery barrier released by the Eon Divine Lamp.

She chanted an incantation as she raised her hands upward, and a series of dark red law threads flew out of her body, while the dark red light in the surrounding spirit domain rapidly converged toward her.

As more and more law threads emerged, her complexion paled further and further, as if all of her strength were being slowly sapped away.

However, there was a determined look of resolve in her eyes as she sped up even further in her chanting.

The surrounding space rumbled violently, and the dark red law threads intertwined to form a red wheel projection the size of a house.

There were six black holes dotted around the wheel, within each of which was a burst of black light that was revolving incessantly, forming a vortex that was giving off a burst of indescribable power, causing the nearby space to rumble violently.

Wyrm 3 thrust her palms forward, and the dark red wheel instantly flew forward while revolving rapidly before crashing into the fiery, golden barrier.

Jets of golden flames erupted out of the fiery barrier as it trembled violently, but those flames were all snuffed out by the layer of black light over the dark red wheel's surface upon contact.

An agitated look appeared on Daoist Master Dao Yin's face as he was forced to turn his attention to Wyrm 3, and he cast a string of incantation seals into the fiery, golden barrier to fortify it.

In response, Wyrm 3 opened her mouth to release several balls of blood essence, following which her aura instantly became extremely feeble and diminished.

The balls of blood essence fused into the dark red wheel as plumes of blood mist, and it instantly began to accelerate in its revolution, releasing a vast expanse of black light that swept toward the fiery barrier.

Before long, the fiery barrier was overwhelmed by the black light released by the wheel, and it exploded into countless specks of golden fire.

Only then did Daoist Master Dao Yin realize that Wyrm 3 was using the laws of reincarnation.

Never had he imagined that these two High Zenith cultivators had both mastered one of the three paramount laws, and their degree of mastery over their respective law powers wasn't inferior to that of the average Great Encompassment cultivator.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and Lei Yuce and the others were also expending a great deal of effort just to maintain the array, so they were unable to assist Daoist Master Dao Yin at all.

"Fellow Daoist Han, now's your chance!" Wyrm 3 yelled.

Her complexion was as pale as a sheet, and she had collapsed to one knee, as if all of the strength had been drained from her body.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already darted through the eradicated barrier of fire as a streak of golden light, but he was rushing toward the Eon Divine Lamp as opposed to the altar.

"Fellow Daoist Han, what are you doing?" Wyrm 3 exclaimed in an alarmed manner.

At this moment, there was a rather dazed look in Han Li's eyes, and it seemed that his attention was entirely fixated on the Eon Divine Lamp, almost in an obsessive manner.

Daoist Master Dao Yin was furious to see this, and he let loose a loud roar as he pointed a finger at the Eon Divine Lamp from afar.

Simultaneously, he bit through the tip of his own tongue before expelling a mouthful of blood essence.

The Eon Divine Lamp shuddered, and the lamp oil within it began to churn violently, raising a vast expanse of scorching, golden flames that swept toward Han Li.

However, Han Li seemed to be completely oblivious to all of this. His desire had already completely overwhelmed his capacity for rational thought, and there was a deranged look on his face as he channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra with all his might.

Manifestations of his five time-attribute law treasures appeared around him, forming a spherical, golden light barrier around his body as he charged into the sea of fire.

The manifestations of the five time-attribute law treasures instantly began to converge toward him, compressed by the surrounding golden flames, and the golden light barrier was also gradually beginning to thin out.

However, Han Li displayed no intention of backing down as he continued to forge ahead with tightly gritted teeth.

After just a few seconds, the five time-attribute law treasures gave out, and the surrounding golden light barrier was eradicated, exposing Han Li's body directly to the flames.

A burst of excruciating, scorching pain surged through his entire body, and an agonized look appeared on his face as a hint of lucidity surfaced in his eyes, but he then gave a cold harrumph as a look of resolve reappeared on his face.

He reached out through the flames to grab onto the Eon Divine Lamp before pulling it toward himself.

The flames on the lamp instantly converged to form a fiery dragon that climbed its way up his arm, instantly devouring his entire arm and close to half of his body.

Han Li could clearly see the skin, flesh, and sinew of his arm slowly melting away to expose the bone underneath, which was gradually becoming charred black by the golden flames.

However, deep within his soul, there was a voice that was constantly consoling and encouraging him.

"Just persevere a little more, and you'll have it... It'll all be worth it once you claim the lamp... You're almost there, don't give up... It's almost yours..."

In a desperate effort to claim the lamp, Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and all of his true spirit bloodlines at once, completely uncaring of the fact that doing so could trigger severe bloodline backlash.

At the moment, the Eon Divine Lamp was the sole object of his fixation, and he was willing to risk everything to obtain it!

A furious look appeared on Daoist Master Dao Yin's face as he sped toward the lamp, leaving a trail of afterimages in his wake.

Right as he did so, Wyrm 3 was somehow able to muster up the strength to strike, and the dark red wheel flew directly toward the five-colored altar at her behest.

An alarmed look appeared on Daoist Master Dao Yin's face upon seeing this, but it was already too late to turn back.

A burst of five-colored light surfaced over the altar in an attempt to ward off the red wheel, but it was completely futile, and a resounding boom rang out as a huge hole was smashed into the altar.

Almost in the exact same instant, Han Li's Spirit Refinement Technique began acting on its own, restoring a hint of clarity to his muddled mind.

Right at this moment, a loud cry rang out beside his ears.

"Fellow Daoist Han!"

Han Li turned with a dazed look in his eyes to discover Lei Yuce roaring at him with all his might.

"Are you really going to release that devilish deity and doom the entire Golden Origin Immortal Region just to satisfy your own selfish desires? The altar has already been broken, if the lamp is also taken, then that devilish deity will surely be freed!"

Han Li shuddered violently upon hearing this, and he suddenly realized the situation that he was in.

He hurriedly released the Eon Divine Lamp as he shot back in retreat, but the golden flames wrapped around his arm refused to let him go.

In response, Han Li removed the Profound Heavenly Gourd from his waist, then thrust his palm into its underside, and a green vortex instantly emerged from the mouth of the gourd to suck in the golden flames clinging to his arm.

As soon as the flames surged into the gourd, its green exterior instantly turned a bright red color, as if it were being scorched from the inside.

Han Li replaced the gourd back to his waist, then looked down at his own incinerated arm, and he couldn't help but shudder as a sheen of cold sweat appeared on his forehead.

What happened to me? Have I fallen under someone's control?

Han Li quickly retraced all of the events that had taken place since he set foot into the Eon Pagoda, and he was able to ascertain with a high degree of confidence that he hadn't fallen under anyone's control.

However, the desire in his heart had been slowly mounting this entire time, but the process had been so subtle and gradual that he hadn't noticed it.

Furthermore, it seemed like everyone who had entered the Eon Pagoda had fallen under the same influence, which slowly magnified their desires over time.

That was why they had destroyed the altars to claim those treasures without any regard for the consequences. It seemed that anyone who had any desire to obtain the Eon Divine Lamp would ultimately be led to it like moths to a flame.

All of a sudden, Han Li's gaze fell upon the huge hole that had been blasted into the altar, where plumes of dense, black mist were rising up before flowing into the palace.

A projection of the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree appeared over Han Li's arm, and it began to quickly regenerate at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye, but it wasn't going to be fully healed anytime soon.

Han Li rose up into the air, then channeled his Infernal Devilish Eyes as he peered into the hole in the altar.

Chapter 1118: Revenge

Deep within the altar was an enormous underground space that was filled with flowing, molten lava.

The lava formed a dark red lake that was giving off plumes of scorching smoke, and hovering at the center of the lake was a huge, black rock with eight black rock pillars standing upon it.

All of the pillars were riddled with cracks that were flashing incessantly, as if there were molten lava flowing through them as well, and attached to each pillar was a golden chain, all of which led toward the center of the rock.

Seated on the ground there was an emaciated man with a head of disheveled hair.

He was completely nude and so thin that it was as if he were literally just a sack of skin and bones, and the eight golden chains were pierced through his chest, abdomen, shoulders, and arms, locking him firmly into place.

On top of that, a series of ancient runes had been engraved onto the ground beneath him, giving off bursts of formidable restrictive power.

Looking into the black hole, Han Li was struck by the feeling that he was peering into a bottomless abyss of desire.

He shook his head to rid himself of these erratic thoughts, following which a perplexed look appeared on his face.

For some reason, he felt like there was something strange about this array, but he couldn't put his finger on exactly what was strange about it.

Right at this moment, the man suddenly raised his head to meet Han Li's gaze, flashing him a wide smile that revealed two rows of gleaming, white teeth.

Han Li hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to protect his own consciousness, but it seemed that his concerns were unwarranted.

Everyone had been startled by the deranged display that Han Li had put on earlier, and as a result, no one had noticed that a plume of black mist that seeped out from the edge of the hole in a stealthy fashion, then vanished after making its way over to Lei Yuce and the others.

At this moment, Daoist Master Dao Yin was glowering at the hole in the altar with a grim expression, and he murmured to himself, "This is going to be troublesome... At this point, it seems like I have no choice but to put an end to this once and for all."

He heaved a faint sigh as he raised a hand to make a beckoning motion, drawing the Vast Earth Seal into his grasp.

He then sliced open his own finger to release a drop of blood essence, which instantly seeped into the seal.

Immediately thereafter, he began chanting an urgent incantation, and the engravings on the underside of the seal flashed with yellow light while releasing bursts of incredibly formidable earth law powers.

After refining the seal with his blood essence to forcibly eradicate the restriction that Wyrm 3 had planted within it, he began channeling the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array with all his might.

The five immortal treasures rose up into the air, and they began to glow with an unprecedented level of brightness, while the law powers of Lei Yuce and the others surged out of their bodies in a frenzy before being absorbed by the array.

At the same time, the five-colored light barrier around the altar began to rapidly contract, and it didn't take long before it was only just barely large enough to encompass the altar.

Immediately thereafter, the altar disintegrated into dust, as if it were a piece of artwork that had already endured countless millennia of decay.

At the same time, the hole in the altar began to expand, and as soon as the black mist flowing out of it entered the area encompassed within the light barrier, it would also disintegrate into dust, just like the altar had.

"This is the true power of the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array. All that is encompassed within it is annihilated into dust," Qi Mozi murmured to himself.

The five-colored light barrier slowly descended into the hole in the altar, encompassing the black rock floating on the surface of the lava lake, as well as the stone pillars and the emaciated man on the rock.

The black rock began to disintegrate, but the man's body remained intact, and there was a derisive sneer on his face.

Han Li was staring intently at the man, and the latter seemed to have detected his gaze as he turned to Han Li before making a funny face, as if he were entertaining a child.

Daoist Master Dao Yin's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and the divine lamp talisman before him suddenly erupted into flames.

The talisman was quickly incinerated into ashes, leaving only a golden flame behind, and the flame fell upon the Eon Divine Lamp to fuse as one with the flame already burning within the lamp.

The Eon Divine Lamp shuddered slightly, following which a burst of incredibly formidable energy fluctuations surged out from within it.

An arc of golden lightning emerged from the flame in the lamp, then shot out of the lamp like a flying dagger before piercing into the five-colored light barrier.

A resounding boom rang out as an explosion of golden light took place within the five-colored light barrier, completely obscuring the space within.

A string of resounding booms rang out within the hole in the altar, and the stone pillars, the golden chains, and the emaciated man were all completely inundated by the blinding, golden light.

A long while later, the commotion within the five-colored light barrier subsided, and it was revealed that everything within it had been utterly annihilated, leaving a void of emptiness behind.

The five-colored light barrier then disintegrated with a dull thump, while Daoist Master Dao Yin heaved a long sigh of relief.

"Ashes to ashes, dust to dust... After sealing you here for so long, I've finally been able to kill you once and for all."

Meanwhile, Lei Yuce and the others slumped to the ground while gasping for air, looking completely drained, and they hurriedly took some pills to speed up their recovery.

Almost all of the law powers and immortal spiritual power in their bodies had been exhausted, but thankfully, they had managed to slay the old devilish deity.

"Now then, it's time for all of you to suffer the same fate," Daoist Master Dao Yin said as he turned a cold gaze to Han Li and the others, all of whom immediately bristled in response.

Daoist Master Dao Yin was a Great Encompassment cultivator, and he controlled the Eon Divine Lamp. If he were to unleash another wave of balls of five-colored light, then the vast majority of the people left in the palace were undoubtedly going to be wiped out.

Right as everyone was trying to think of a way out of this dire situation, a long blade suddenly pierced through Daoist Master Dao Yin's back before emerging from his lower abdomen, and blood immediately began to seep into his robe from the wound.

His eyes widened in shock and fury as he swung around before lashing out at his assailant, but the latter had already sprung back in retreat to preemptively evade his retaliatory attack.

Everyone's attention was immediately drawn to the assailant in question, and an incredulous look appeared on Lei Yuce's face as he yelled, "Wen Zhong, what the hell are you doing?!"

At this moment, Wen Zhong's facial features were twisted with intense resentment, and he had caught everyone completely off guard with his sneak attack.

Daoist Master Dao Yin had just slain the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, and a sense of relief and complacency had inevitably welled up in his heart. That was the opportunity that Wen Zhong had pounced on to make his move.

"What am I doing? I'm going to kill this shameless, biased old bastard!" Wen Zhong roared in a deranged manner.

"Why? Have you gone insane? He's our master! We owe everything to him!" Lei Yuce yelled in a furious and incredulous voice.

"If he's truly our master, as you say, then why is it that he's only passed down the Almighty Sword Array to you? In his eyes, I've never been good enough compared to you. He was never even willing to give me a chance! What did I do to deserve this?" Wen Zhong roared as his eyes seethed with resentment.

Lei Yuce was rendered speechless upon hearing this, while Daoist Master Dao Yin's complexion had turned deathly pale.

Wen Zhong's blade had pierced straight through his dantian, and he couldn't help but throw up a mouthful of blood as he pulled the blade out of his own body.

A concerned look appeared in Lei Yuce's eyes upon seeing this, and he was just about to continue reprimanding Wen Zhong when Daoist Master Dao Yin raised a hand to stop him.

"I am already aware of the resentment Wen Zhong harbors in his heart, and I spoke about it with him in private. I thought I had already resolved the matter, but it seems like he was never able to truly let go of his resentment, and that was what the old devil had taken advantage of," Daoist Master Dao Yin said as he wiped the blood from his lips.

"What are you saying, Master?" Lei Yuce asked with a perplexed expression.

"That old devil has mastered the laws of inner demons, and his forte is to fan the flames of the deepest, darkest desires in one's heart. It looks like Wen Zhong has fallen prey to his power," Daoist Master Dao Yin sighed.

A look of realization appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

"Finally! Finally, I get to exact my revenge!" Wen Zhong cackled as his expression became even more twisted and deranged.

Chapter 1119: The Deranged Devil

Daoist Master Dao Yin quickly took a golden pill to suppress his own injuries, then turned his gaze to Wen Zhong.

To everyone's surprise, despite his fiery personality, at this moment, he was gazing upon Wen Zhong with nothing but sympathy in his eyes.

All of a sudden, he vanished from the spot, only to abruptly reappear behind Wen Zhong.

Wen Zhong immediately swung around, before lashing out in retaliation, only for Daoist Master Dao Yin to grab onto his arm before wrenching it downward.

Wen Zhong felt as if a massive mountain were suddenly weighing down upon his arm, sending him falling forward onto the ground.

Daoist Master Dao Yin took advantage of this opportunity to raise his other hand, following which a streak of needle-like light shot out of his fingertip before piercing into Wen Zhong's glabella.

Wen Zhong's entire body instantly shuddered violently as if he had been struck by lightning, and he fell unconscious on the spot, much to Lei Yuce's relief.

However, his relief soon turned to horror as he cast his gaze toward the edge of the destroyed altar, where a cloud of black mist had emerged, and it was swirling incessantly, forming a stormy, black vortex that was around ten feet in height.

No one was able to pinpoint the moment that the vortex had appeared, as it revolved faster and faster, the black light within it glowed brighter and brighter.

All of a sudden, the vortex fell still, and a slightly hunched-over male figure emerged from the black light within.

The man had skin that was as black as ink, and his eyes were very peculiar in appearance. His left pupil was glowing with bright, purple light, as if there were a purple nebulous cloud swirling around inside, while his right pupil was filled with murky, azure light.

The man's face was very angular, with a tall nose, and sharp, thin lips. He should've been a rather handsome middle-aged man, but with his head of disheveled, gray hair and his thick beard, he appeared more like an unkempt elderly man.

After the man emerged from the vortex, he immediately crouched down before wrapping his arms around his own knees, then began rocking back and forth while mumbling something unintelligible to himself.

Everyone was looking on with perplexed expressions when all of a sudden, a burst of black light emerged over the man's back, forming a black vortex that was roughly a foot in diameter.

Peculiar looks appeared on everyone's faces upon seeing this, and all of a sudden, a translucent, black thread emerged from each of their glabellas, even those of the already deceased devilish beings, following which the black threads drifted directly toward the vortex on the man's back.

In the instant that the black thread flew out of Han Li's glabella, he immediately reached out to try and catch it for a closer examination, but it passed straight through his hand as if it had no substantial form.

Meanwhile, all of the cultivators waiting outside the Eon Pagoda had already split up into groups and factions, waiting for the return of everyone in the pagoda.

It had already been a very long time since Lei Yuce and the others first entered the pagoda, and the people waiting outside had begun to grow rather agitated. Some conflicts had even arisen between hostile factions during this time, but they were ultimately all deescalated without much trouble.

At the moment, it was approaching dusk outside the pagoda, and most of the cultivators were seated in meditation. Right at this moment, a translucent, black thread emerged from all of their glabellas.

All of the black threads converged in the sky, forming a dark cloud that drifted toward the Eon Pagoda before vanishing into it.

Everyone outside the pagoda followed the dark cloud to the pagoda, where they looked on with perplexed expressions as it vanished right before their eyes.

Immediately thereafter, many people began to depart from the pagoda, dispersing in all directions.

Meanwhile, the same translucent, black threads were flying out of the bodies of all of the remaining living beings trapped on all levels of the Eon Pagoda, and all of these black threads traveled toward the same final destination, namely the black vortex behind the disheveled, middle-aged man.

Han Li watched as countless black threads converged toward the man from all directions, and a peculiar feeling suddenly welled up in his heart.

As that black thread was emerging from his glabella, he had suddenly felt a sense of lightness and clarity in his consciousness, as if something had been weighing down on his consciousness this entire time, but it had finally been removed.

However, what was rather unsettling to him was that he had no idea when this black thread had appeared in his consciousness, and it had somehow been able to completely avoid the detection of his Spirit Refinement Technique.

In reality, this was a question that had occurred to everyone else present as well.

None of them received any inkling that anything had been amiss, and it was only after these black threads had emerged from their bodies that they felt a change in their mental state.

All of a sudden, the black vortex behind the middle-aged man faded away, and he rose up from the ground before letting loose a loud yawn while stretching lazily, as if he had just awoken from a long slumber.

At this point, his aura had swelled to the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage, and every single movement of his seemed to be able to affect the space around him.

However, his aura then gradually became more and more restrained until it was completely subdued, giving him the appearance of an innocuous, deranged man dressed in shabby clothes.

Judging from the grim and horrified looks on the faces of Daoist Master Dao Yin and the other Almighty Sword Sect cultivators, this man had to have been none other than the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

"Who're all of you?" the man asked in a perplexed manner, but as soon as his voice trailed off, a golden pillar of fire came crashing down upon him from the heavens, sending him sprawling forward before sinking into the ground.

The pillar of fire seemed to have been holding the weight of a thousand mountains, and the ground was fracturing violently despite the powerful fortification restrictions in the palace.

Han Li turned to discover a bright red thread around the Eon Divine Lamp, indicating that Daoist Master Dao Yin had expended his own blood essence to use the Eon Divine Lamp to unleash that attack upon the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

Only after a long while did the pillar of golden flames fade away, and everyone's attention was focused on the massive crater on the ground, where the man's aura had suddenly become completely undetectable.

Right as everyone was looking on with bated breath, a pained groan suddenly rang out from within the crater, immediately following which a figure drifted out from within in a wraith-like manner, leaving an afterimage behind as they sped over to Daoist Master Dao Yin in the blink of an eye.

Daoist Master Dao Yin had been on his guard this entire time, and he immediately lashed out, sending bursts of golden flames flying out of the Eon Divine Lamp before raining down upon the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

However, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity made no attempt to take evasive measures as he sped directly into the fiery storm, and a layer of dense, black light emerged over his fist as he swung them through the air, unleashing a barrage of countless black fist projections.

The storm of fist projections clashed against the flurry of golden flames, and the former was able to easily eradicate the latter.

However, after the golden flames faded away, a burst of five-colored light came sweeping toward the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, having been unleashed by the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array.

"Piss off!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity grumbled in a displeased voice as he rushed headfirst into the vast expanse of five-colored light, upon which his body instantly exploded into a cloud of black mist.

Before Daoist Master Dao Yin had a chance to react, the cloud of black mist was already upon him, and a hand came reaching out of it before forcefully striking his chest.

Daoist Master Dao Yin let loose a pained cry as he was sent flying back through the air, and only then did the cloud of black mist fully reform into the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

Daoist Master Dao Yin was already carrying very severe injuries, and this palm strike only further compounded his woes. After tumbling to the ground, he threw up several mouthfuls of blood before falling unconscious.

Han Li and the others were all astonished to see this.

Not only did the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity not fear the flames of the Eon Divine Lamp, he was also able to shrug off the attacks of the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation with ease, and that was a feat that even Qi Mozi wasn't confident in his own ability to replicate.

After wounding Daoist Master Dao Yin, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity didn't continue to go after him. Instead, he turned to stare at the Eon Divine Lamp that had trapped him for so many years, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

Lei Yuce wanted to fly over to Daoist Master Dao Yin's side, but he was afraid that doing so would incur the wrath of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's, so he could remain rooted to the spot, while cold sweat flowed down from his forehead.

Chapter 1120: Madman

"I was enjoying a good nap, surely you didn't have to wake me up so unceremoniously," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity yawned as he stretched lazily, while everyone looked on with tense expressions.

All of a sudden, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity turned to spit in the direction of the Eon Divine Lamp, and it seemed as if he had recalled some unpleasant memory as he yelled, "Tai Sui, you old dog! I've been trapped here for far too long because of you! Where is my son right now? Tell me where my son is or prepare to lay down your life, do you hear me?"

Han Li and the others were all flabbergasted to see this, struggling to draw a correlation between this emotionally unstable madman and the almighty devilish deity that had once terrorized an entire immortal region.

"You're not going to tell me? Fine, then I'll just have to make you!"

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity pounced at the Eon Divine Lamp as he spoke.

With Daoist Master Dao Yin unconscious and the altar destroyed, the lamp was left to fend for itself, and it released layers of golden light to oppose the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity continued to curse loudly as he swung his fists at the Eon Divin Lamp, while black mist surged out of his entire body like a volcanic eruption, causing the entire palace to tremble violently.

Han Li could see an enormous figure rising up within the mist, and it seemed to the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's true devilish form, except it seemed to be a projection, rather than an entity of substance.

Even so, the almighty aura erupting out of the cloud of black mist was still more than sufficiently awe-inspiring in its own right.

The projection seemed to have twelve arms, which it was swinging incessantly through the air in a relentless barrage of attacks aimed at the Eon Divine Lamp, causing it to tremble violently.

Large volumes of lamp oil spilled out in all directions, forming a golden sea of fire that swallowed up virtually the entire palace, forcing everyone to frantically retreat to the walls.

The entire palace continued to shudder violently, while the figure in the cloud of black mist maintained its ferocious barrage, and at the same time, bursts of devilish qi were rising up from its body before crashing into the roof of the palace above.

The Eon Divine Lamp remained unscathed, but the palace was beginning to give out.

Finally, the roof of the Eon Palace was blown apart amid a resounding boom, and everyone immediately flew out from within.

Lei Yuce was forced to abandon the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array as he hoisted the unconscious Daoist Master Dao Yin onto his back before fleeing the palace with Su Anqian and the other Almighty Sword Sect cultivators.

However, everyone had only just risen up into the air when an enormous black lotus flower restriction appeared outside the palace, encompassing the entire surrounding area within a radius of several dozen feet.

Every single one of the lotus flower's countless petals was over ten thousand feet tall, and a vast expanse of dark clouds was gathering up above, giving off the same aura as the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

The Almighty Sword Sect cultivators had no choice but to continue to rise up into the heavens, and a burst of radiant swordlight erupted out of their bodies before fusing as one to form a giant, five-colored sword of light that struck the black lotus flower.

A loud clang rang out as the five-colored sword was shattered, while the black lotus flower remained completely unscathed.

"Stop causing a commotion! Just give me some peace and quiet!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity yelled in a disgruntled manner as he looked up from the Eon Divine Lamp, then made a grabbing motion up toward the sky, and a giant hand instantly descended from above, capturing all of the Almighty Sword Sect cultivators.

With a casual toss, the giant hand threw them heavily back down into the palace, following which tendrils of black mist rose up in the air, forming a series of powerful black whips that came crashing down upon the Almighty Sword Sect cultivators with unrivaled power.

"None of you are getting away after rousing me from my slumber!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity yelled, and Han Li and the others all flew back to the Eon Palace before hovering in the air above it.

Han Li raised an eyebrow at the sight of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's strange behavior, and he couldn't help but ask through voice transmission, "Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, why does it feel like this Dark Heavens Devilish Deity isn't quite... all there?"

Wyrm 3 had no response for this.

Right at this moment, the cloud of black mist in the palace began to rapidly shrink, and it didn't take long before the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was revealed again.

"What the hell is wrong with this thing? Why can't I break it?" he grumbled at the Eon Divine Lamp, which remained completely unscathed.

He then turned his gaze to the abandoned Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, and an intrigued look appeared on his face as he murmured to himself, "What's this? It looks rather fun. Maybe I should take it for a spin..."

He then jumped into the array, while everyone else looked on with dazed expressions.

Upon entering the array, a puzzled look appeared on his face as he murmured to himself, "How do I use this thing again? Oh, I've got it!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, five bursts of immortal spiritual power erupted out of his body, forming five pillars of light that fell upon the five immortal treasures in the array.

In the span of no more than twenty seconds, he had completed a process of basic refinement on all five of the fourth-tier immortal treasures.

Immediately thereafter, he began to chant an incantation, and all of the immortal treasures instantly lit up. The Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array was operating again, and it conjured up a five-colored ball of light around the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

Everyone was looking on with perplexed expressions, wondering what the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was doing when he suddenly made a hand seal, and numerous streaks of light burst out of his hand before flying into the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array.

The five-colored ball of light conjured up by the array instantly began glowing even brighter, and a burst of bone-chilling destructive force began to spread through the interior of the light barrier.

An excited look appeared on the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's face, and he only had time to give a yell of exultation before his body disintegrated into a cloud of black dust particles.

Everyone in the palace looked on in deathly silence, unable to comprehend what they had just witnessed.

"Did he just... kill himself?" Fox 3 exclaimed in an incredulous manner.

"No, he's not dead, but he certainly is insane," Han Li sighed.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a cloud of black mist emerged within the ball of five-colored light, then condensed to reform the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, and he was chortling with glee.

"It's been so long since I've taken a bath! Now..."

Before he had a chance to finish his sentence, his body disintegrated once again under another burst of destructive power released by the array, but it didn't take long before he was reformed again.

"I can bathe to my heart's content..." the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity continued where his previous sentence had left off, immediately following which his body exploded for a third time.

"There's definitely a few screws loose up there," Fox 3 communicated to Wyrm 3 and Han Li through voice transmission.

Everyone continued to watch as the cycle of destruction and reformation repeated itself over and over again, and with each rebirth, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's body seemed to become more resilient, making it more and more difficult for the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array to destroy him.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity began to swim through the air in a leisurely fashion, alternating between the backstroke and the doggy paddle, and he was thoroughly enjoying himself, paying no heed to the fact that he had an audience.

As the attacks from the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array became less and less effective, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity began to grow bored, and he made a hand seal before raising his hands to the heavens, injecting another torrent of immortal spiritual power into the five immortal treasures, which glowed radiantly while releasing five bursts of light of different colors into the five-colored light barrier.

A burst of destructive power that was far more formidable than before surged through the light barrier, and the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's body instantly exploded into dust.

At the same time, the five-colored light barrier began trembling incessantly as a series of fist-sized balls of five colored light split off from it before flying through the air in all directions.

The balls of light weren't very large, but all of them contained immense destructive power.

Han Li and the others certainly didn't possess the physical constitution and cultivation base to match the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, and they hurriedly took evasive measures to protect themselves.

A string of resounding booms rang out within the palace as its walls were blasted full of holes, and it didn't appear as if it would be able to stand for much longer.

Han Li had already flown back in retreat to get as far away from the remains of the Eon Palace as possible, but right at this moment, Qi Mozi suddenly appeared beside him with that black ax in his hand, and in the blink of an eye, he swung the ax in Han Li's direction close to twenty times.

A flurry of black ax projections instantly swept directly toward Han Li, forcing him to channel his Reversal True Axis ability before rising up further into the air.

However, as he did so, a ball of five-colored light came hurtling directly toward him on an unavoidable collision path, placing him in a situation of dire peril.

Chapter 1121: Search for Close Family

In this dire situation, Han Li could only channel his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might before swinging a fist at the oncoming ball of five-colored light.

A layer of golden ripples erupted out of his fist, forming layers upon layers of fist projections that swept toward the ball of five-colored light.

The two clashed, and the fist projections exploded one after another, but the time law powers within them weren't able to slow down the ball of five-colored light very much at all, so they hadn't bought him much time.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords combined into one at his behest before falling into his grasp.

There was no time for him to swing the sword, so he could only use it as a protective barrier.

A vast expanse of golden lightning erupted out of the sword in a frenzy, resembling a giant, golden, lightning hand that enveloped the ball of five-colored light to impede its advance.

More and more arcs of golden lightning continued to erupt out of the sword before being destroyed by the ball of five-colored light, and an impasse ensued.

Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 immediately flew over to Han Li's side, protecting him from further attacks from Qi Mozi.

However, instead of harassing Han Li any further, Qi Mozi flew back through the air before landing on a giant pile of rubble roughly ten thousand feet away. At the moment, Xiong Shan was hiding behind the pile of rubble with a horrified look on his face.

Only after several seconds had passed did the eruption of balls of five-colored light finally begin to subside, and Han Li turned to Qi Mozi with a cold look in his eyes.

Right at this moment, a figure abruptly appeared beside Han Li without any warning, stirring up no spatial fluctuations or spiritual qi fluctuations at all as he reached out to grab onto Han Li's sword-wielding arm.

The figure was none other than the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, and Han Li's trio was naturally very much taken aback by his sudden emergence from the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array.

Han Li's throat was feeling a little dry as he turned his gaze to the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, whose aura had become even more condensed and restrained, as if much of the impurities in his body had been eradicated from the repeated baptisms he had undergone within the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array.

"It's been a very long time since I've seen the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra in action. Come, let's have a little spar together," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity said.

"Please don't make jokes at my expense, Senior. I'm clearly no match for you," Han Li hurriedly replied as he attempted to withdraw his arm, but to no avail.

Hence, he could only activate his Infernal Devilish Eyes to try and search for any weak points in the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's body.

"You've also mastered an ocular secret technique of our holy race? You certainly are a rare talent..." the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity remarked, immediately identifying Han Li's Infernal Devilish Eyes.

He then raised an eyebrow as he continued, "Who is your master? How have you mastered even the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts?"

Han Li was astonished to hear this, and he was terrified that the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity would be able to uncover even more of his secrets, so he hurriedly replied, "Your vast wealth of knowledge and experience is truly astounding, Senior. My master is Patriarch Miro of the True Mantra Sect. Have you heard of him?"

"So your master is that fat monk. That makes sense, considering your primary cultivation arts is the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra. I knew it! I'm a genius!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity said with an elated nod, looking much more like a small child who had solved a difficult puzzle than a Great Encompassment cultivator.

"Your wisdom is truly unmatched, Senior," Han Li praised. "May I ask that you release me now?"

Sure enough, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity became even more elated upon receiving praise from Han Li, and he let go of Han Li's arm as he said in a proud manner, "You're not that good to look at, but you're a smart kid. When it comes to knowledge and experience, very few people can compare with me!

“If you have any questions, then I suggest you take full advantage of this opportunity and raise them to me. I'm in a good mood right now, so I'm happy to provide you with the enlightenment that you seek."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he didn't know what to make of this situation, so he said, "I wouldn't dare to trouble you with my trivial questions, Senior."

"Are you trying to make it so that I'm unable to keep a promise? I told you to ask me questions, so you have to ask!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity demanded with an angry look on his face.

Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 were standing beside Han Li, no more than twenty to thirty feet from the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, and they were looking on with flabbergasted expressions, not daring to advance or retreat.

Qi Mozi faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which a sly grin appeared on his face.

Lei Yuce and the others were still unable to get away, so they could only secretly feed Daoist Master Dao Yin some pills while the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was distracted with Han Li.

"In that case, there is a question that I would like to ask. Have you seen a Gold Devouring Immortal here, Senior?" Han Li asked in a respectful manner.

Even though there existed an agreement between him and Qu Lin, he still couldn't help but feel a sense of unease at the fact that Qu Lin had been missing ever since he first entered the seventh level.

"I have," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity replied without any hesitation.

"Where?" Han Li hurriedly.

"I don't remember, it was too long ago. I remember that he made for a really good punching bag, so I gave him a beating to stave off boredom. Come to think of it, I haven't seen him in a very long time," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity mused.

Qu Lin had indeed mentioned being beaten by an old madman during his previous venture into the seventh level, so this corroborated his story.

"Wait, that doesn't make sense! You've been trapped in this altar in the Eon Palace this entire time, how could you possibly have met him before?" Han Li asked.

"You say I've been trapped here? What a joke! I only chose to stay in this place so I can sleep without being interrupted. If I wanted to come out, no one could've stopped me!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity protested in a displeased manner.

"My apologies, Senior, it seems I misunderstood the situation," Han Li hurriedly said.

Back when he had first laid eyes upon the array through the hole that Wyrm 3 had blasted into the altar, he had already noticed that something was a little off about it. Thinking back now, it seemed like the array had already somehow lost the ability to serve its intended purpose.

If the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity really had been trapped in there while slowly having his cultivation base whittled away, then the energy fluctuations in the array definitely wouldn't have been so placid, and that observation was what had struck Han Li as strange at the time.

"What kind of bullshit question is this? You should raise some more difficult questions!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity demanded.

"Like what?" Han Li asked in a perplexed manner.

"Like questions related to cultivation! Come to think of it, those won't be very difficult for me to answer, either..." the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity mused as he scratched his own head.

Han Li raised an eyebrow, and a question really did occur to him.

"The cultivation art for the Infernal Devilish Eyes claims that these eyes will allow me to see through all illusions and restrictions, so why is it that there are many illusory arrays and restrictions in this pagoda that I've been unable to see through?"

"That's not a very difficult question, but I can answer it for you. Have you taken in any devilish qi during your cultivation of the Infernal Devilish Eyes?" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity asked.

"Of course. After all, the foundation of this ocular ability comes from using devilish qi to cleanse one's eyes," Han Li replied.

"I figured as much. You're using a devilish cultivation art, so I'm assuming you drew upon your own devilish qi instead of devilish qi from the outside world. Hence, there should be no issues with the purity of the devilish qi that you've taken in. In that case, the problem must lie in the fact that you've cultivated other spirit eye abilities in the past," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity deduced, and he was suddenly looking much more focused and sane.

"Your deduction is perfect, Senior! I have indeed cultivated another spirit eye ability in the past," Han Li praised, and this time, it came from a much more earnest place.

He had previously cultivated the Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and it seemed that some conflict existed between these two ocular abilities.

"The cultivation methods for different spirit eye abilities are fundamentally different, so they'll inevitably conflict with one another. All you need to do is..."

With that, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity provided a concise solution to Han Li's problem.

With his question answered, Han Li was feeling a bit more reassured, and he said, "Thank you, Senior. I have one more question. May I ask why you've trapped all of us here?"

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was instantly rooted to the spot upon hearing this, and he began pacing back and forth as he fell into deep thought.

"What was I going to do again? I was going to do something, but I can't remember..." he murmured to himself as he sat down onto the ground, while everyone else looked on with exasperated expressions.

After some time, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity seemed to have suddenly recalled something, and a look of urgency appeared on his face as he exclaimed in a frantic voice, "I remember now, I'm looking for my wife and son! Have you seen them? Do you know where they are?"

"I'm afraid not, Senior," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

Chapter 1122: Obtaining the Lamp

"You don't know where they are? How can you not know where they are?!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity yelled in a furious voice.

Right at this moment, Qi Mozi stepped forward with a faint smile as he declared, "I know where they are."

As soon as his voice trailed off, Han Li saw a black shadow flash past his eyes, immediately following which Qi Mozi was lifted up into the air by the shoulders.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity had appeared right beside him in a wraith-like manner, moving so quickly that no one had a chance to react.

A burst of tremendous power descended upon Qi Mozi, instantly immobilizing him despite his Great Encompassment Stage cultivation base, and his smile immediately stiffened slightly.

Everyone reflexively dispersed to open up some distance between themselves and the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, and while Han Li was very relieved to have finally been released, he was also a little concerned about what Qi Mozi was up to.

Qi Mozi was a very cunning and calculating man, so the fact that he had chosen to speak up at a time like this definitely wasn't good news. On top of that, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was not in a sound state of mind, so there was no telling what his reaction would be to what Qi Mozi was about to say.

However, there was nothing that he could do for now aside from watch as the situation unfolded.

"Where are my wife and son? Tell me!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity yelled as he shook Qi Mozi violently by the shoulders.

Qi Mozi felt as if his shoulders were about to be fractured by Qi Mozi's iron grip, and he fought back the pain as he forced a smile onto his own face and asked, "Your name is Shi Kongmo, and your wife is Mistress Jin Ling, is that right?"

Shi Kongmo?

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

"That's right! So you really do know! Take me to them right now!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity exclaimed in an ecstatic voice, and his grip unconsciously tightened slightly from excitement.

A pained look appeared on Qi Mozi's face as he hurriedly said, "Before that, please put me down. I'm afraid I might come apart at the seams if you grip me any tighter."

"Oh, my apologies," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity said as he released Qi Mozi. "Alright, take me to them now."

"I know where Mistress Jin Ling and your son are, but I can't take you to them," Qi Mozi replied with a shake of his head.

"What? Why?" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity asked as a murderous gleam flashed through his eyes, and he reached out to grab Qi Mozi by the throat.

A tangible aura of baleful qi erupted out of his body, causing the nearby space to ripple and tremble violently.

Han Li and the others were also enshrouded in this aura of baleful qi, and they felt as if they were standing in a freezing snowscape in the nude. It was an extremely unpleasant sensation, but they had no choice but to bear it.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Shi. It's not that I'm not willing to take you there," Qi Mozi hurriedly said. "The problem is that your wife and son are currently being held prisoner by Dao Ancestor Chi Rong of the Fused Heavens Immortal Region. You may be near invincible among Great Encompassment cultivators, but I presume that a Dao Ancestor is still too formidable for you to oppose right?"

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's fury instantly abated upon hearing this, and he seemed to have recovered some degree of rationality as he released Qi Mozi.

"They're being held captive by that old hag? She's the Dao Ancestor of essential fire laws, and even among all Dao Ancestors, her powers rank in the top ten, so I'm no match for her for now."

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Shi, I've already established an agreement with Dao Ancestor Chi Rong, and she has agreed to release Mistress Jin Ling and your son in exchange for two items," Qi Mozi said.

An ecstatic look instantly appeared on the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's face upon hearing this, and he hurriedly asked, "What are they? Tell me! I can give her even twenty things if she wants, let alone two!"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as a sense of foreboding welled up in his heart.

"They are the Eon Divine Lamp and the cultivation art for the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra. I came into the Tai Sui Immortal Manor in search of the Eon Divine Lamp, but I've just so happen to run into someone cultivating the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra here as well. It looks like the even the heavens are smiling down upon Mistress Jin Ling and your son!" Qi Mozi said as he turned his gaze to Han Li.

Han Li's expression instantly changed slightly upon hearing this.

"This Eon Divine Lamp is really annoying to look at, and I can't destroy it anyway, so you can have it," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity said, then flew over to the Eon Divine Lamp in a flash.

Even with the five-colored altar destroyed, the Eon Divine Lamp remained hovering in mid-air, giving a golden glow that provided the only light source in what was otherwise a vast expanse of inky darkness.

"You have a way to capture the lamp?" Qi Mozi asked with a surprised expression.

The Eon Divine Lamp had remained completely unmoved in the face of the string of attacks unleashed by the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity just now.

"Of course, and I can do so with ease, just you watch!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity harrumphed as he split up into five identical figures to surround the Eon Divine Lamp.

Immediately thereafter, the five Dark Heavens Devilish Deities each reached out with one hand in unison, and five bursts of black light flew out of the palms of their hands.

The space around the Eon Divine Lamp was torn open like a curtain, forming a circular spatial rift that was hundreds of feet in size.

Turbulence of all types of different colors were surging through the spatial rift, and it was giving off a burst of tremendous suction force that acted upon everything in the nearby vicinity.

Everyone hurriedly retreated even further upon seeing this for fear of being devoured by the spatial rift, but even though the five Dark Heavens Devilish Deities were standing right beside the spatial rift, they remained completely unaffected.

The Eon Divine Lamp also remained completely still, somehow unmoved by the violent spatial turbulence around it.

Deep within the spatial rift, a series of runes in the shape of golden chains intertwined with one another to form an enormous, golden net, which spread out in all directions as far as the eyes could see, and the Eon Divine Lamp was right at the center of the net.

A bewildered look appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of the golden net, and everyone else was also surprised to see that something like this was lurking behind the Eon Divine Lamp.

The five Dark Heavens Devilish Deities each held one hand aloft to stabilize the spatial rift, while swinging their other hand through the air like blades, and five massive, black palm projections were instantly released.

The palm projections were enshrouded in devilish qi, and they were giving off no spiritual qi fluctuations, law powers, or any energy fluctuations of any description, for that matter.

All there was was nothingness, a type of nothingness that could erode everything.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up at the sight of the five black palm projections.

His Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and Infernal Devilish Eyes were both devilish abilities, but he couldn't even hold a candle to the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity when it came to utilization of devilish qi.

If he could utilize devilish qi to the same degree of proficiency as the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, then he would be able to erode the immortal treasures of Qi Mozi and other Heavenly Court cultivators in battle, thereby giving him a large advantage.

The five palm projections swept toward the golden net, eradicating all of the spatial turbulence in their wake.

As soon as the palm projections struck the golden net, the latter immediately began to tremble violently while giving off radiant, golden light.

However, the golden light was no match for the formidable devilish qi released by the palm projections, and it was being quickly whittled away.

The Eon Divine Lamp shuddered as a sea of golden flames erupted out of it before sweeping toward the five palm projections, but it was already too late, and the palm projections were able to overwhelm the golden net before the golden flames had a chance to reach them.

A loud tearing sound rang out as five huge gashes were torn into the golden net, and its connection with the Eon Divine Lamp was completely severed.

The entire net shuddered violently while flashing erratically, then exploded into countless specks of golden spiritual light.

At the same time, a layer of golden radiance appeared in the sky outside the Eon Palace, basking the clouds in a golden sheen, and formidable time law power fluctuations were sweeping through the air, while the world's origin qi was also churning violently.

Countless specks of five-colored light emerged, stretching as far as the eyes could see, and they seemed to fill the entirety of heaven and earth, while the enormous mountain down below also began to tremble violently.

However, it didn't take long before the golden light faded away, and the time law powers that were originally pervasively present throughout the entire seventh level of the Eon Pagoda also vanished in the same instant.

The same applied to the other six levels as well, and from the outside of the Eon Pagoda, one could see the golden flame at the top of the pagoda flash a few times before being abruptly snuffed out.

Inside the ruins of the Eon Palace, the Eon Divine Lamp shuddered violently in the wake of the golden net's destruction, and it began to fly toward the surrounding spatial turbulence.

Right at this moment, one of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deities swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of black light that dragged the Eon Divine Lamp to his side.

Meanwhile, the other four Dark Heavens Devilish Deities drifted back in retreat, and the massive spatial rift was instantly closed, restoring the palace to a state of peace and quiet.

All of this had taken place in the span of just a few seconds, and that was all it took for the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity to obtain the Eon Divine Lamp, putting his peak-Great Encompassment Stage powers on full display.

Han Li and the others were awestruck by his unfathomable powers, while Lei Yuce and the Almighty Sword Sect cultivators were horrified to see that he had captured the Eon Divine Lamp.

The five Dark Heavens Devilish Deities fused back into one, then tossed the Eon Divine Lamp at Qi Mozi, who caught it as a hint of excitement flashed through his eyes, only to be quickly concealed.

Chapter 1123: Beating

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity turned to Han Li, then tossed a purple jade slip at him as he demanded, "Give me a copy of the cultivation art for the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra. Rest assured, Patriarch Miro and I are good friends, so I won't make you give me the cultivation art for nothing.

“Here's a Five Lightning True Mantra that I obtained by chance from a set of ancient ruins. It's one of the most powerful lightning-attribute cultivation arts in this realm, and it's not inferior in value compared with your Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra."

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he caught the jade slip, but his mind was racing as he processed the situation.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was clearly not in a sound state of mind, and he seemed to have placed his trust in Qi Mozi, so Han Li had to proceed with the utmost caution here.

Before he had a chance to say anything, Wyrm 3 suddenly stepped forward, and a Reincarnation Palace mask appeared over her face as she urged, "Don't trust that man, Senior Shi! Not only is he a cultivator from the Heavenly Court, he's the current chief warden of the Immortal Prison, and he's lying to you to try and lure you to the Heavenly Court so all of the Dao Ancestors can target you at once! Fellow Daoist Han and I are both from the Reincarnation Palace, we are your true allies!"

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and it seemed that a hint of rationality had returned to him.

Qi Mozi seemed to have already anticipated this, and he remained calm and collected as he sneered, "I'm a cultivator of the Heavenly Court? What a joke! Given Fellow Daoist Shi's vast wealth of knowledge and experience, would he not be able to tell if I were from the Heavenly Court? Why is your Reincarnation Palace trying to stop me from rescuing Mistress Jin Ling and Young Master Shi? What are your intentions?"

"He seems to be using the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome of the True Mantra Sect, which isn't a Heavenly Court cultivation art," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity mused to himself.

"That's precisely correct, Fellow Daoist Shi," Qi Mozi immediately said, not giving Han Li and Wyrm 3 any chance to interject.

At the same time, he swept a sleeve through the air to release the withered bodies of the three devilish beings from earlier.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, these three were once subordinates of yours, but they betrayed you and doomed you to be imprisoned in this place. I've killed these three, and their two brothers were killed in the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, so you can rest easy now, knowing that they'll never be able to betray you again," Qi Mozi said, clearly sucking up to the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity flew into a rage at the sight of the three bodies, and he yelled, "Those ungrateful bastards! I treated them like my own brothers, yet they betrayed me at the most crucial juncture!"

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and the three bodies exploded into a cloud of gray dust that drifted away with the wind.

Han Li and Wyrm 3 exchanged a concerned glance with each other upon seeing this. Qi Mozi was doing everything in his power to appease the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, and they were unable to match his efforts.

"Give me the cultivation art for the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra right now!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity demanded as he turned back to Han Li.

"I wouldn't dare to not hand over the cultivation art to you, Senior, the problem is that I don't have the complete version. My master only gave me the first half of the cultivation art, so it won't do you any good," Han Li replied, making up an excuse on the spot.

"What? You only have the first half?"

A displeased look instantly appeared on the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's face upon hearing this.

"Rest assured, even though I don't have the complete version of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, I know where the complete version can be found. Right now, the True Mantra Sect has already been destroyed by the Heavenly Court, and in order to prevent the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra from being lost, my master sealed the cultivation art away in a special place that can only be accessed using a powerful time-attribute immortal treasure.

“I came to the Tai Sui Immortal Manor in order to obtain the Eon Divine Lamp so that I can retrieve the second half of the cultivation art. If you trust me, then please lend me the lamp, and I promise to return with the complete version of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra in ten years to help you save your wife and son. You can even accompany me there if you'd like," Han Li replied in a respectful manner.

Qi Mozi's expression darkened significantly upon hearing this, while a contemplative look appeared on the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's face.

Qi Mozi could sense that the tide was beginning to turn against him, and he hurriedly said, "Han Li, how dare you tell such a blatant lie to Fellow Daoist Shi! I saw our master pass down the complete version of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra with my own two eyes! Don't believe him, Fellow Daoist Shi. The cultivation art can be found in his storage tool or his memories, I'm certain of it!"

This was exactly what Han Li wanted, and he pounced on the opportunity, removing a storage tool from his body as he said, "If you want to examine my storage tool, then feel free to do so. However, I want you to offer up your storage tool for Senior Shi's examination as well. I'm sure there will be things inside that will reveal your identity."

Qi Mozi faltered slightly upon hearing this, and he was internally kicking himself for having failed to consider this countermeasure from Han Li.

His storage tools contained many items from the Heavenly Court, including even his chief warden token.

However, he couldn't afford to back down now, and with that in mind, he slipped off the storage ring on his finger as he harrumphed coldly, "Fine, we'll do as you say then!"

He had two storage tools, and this storage ring only contained some items that he used in battle, while all of his more important belongings were in the other storage tool, which was hidden quite well, so he was confident that Han Li wouldn't be able to find it.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's mind was quite muddled to begin with, and he was beginning to grow very frustrated by the bickering between Han Li and Qi Mozi.

However, right at this moment, he suddenly turned to a certain direction, then raised a hand to make a grabbing motion as he yelled, "Who's there?"

The world's origin qi halfway up the giant mountain converged violently to form an enormous, black hand that grabbed onto a certain spot in the air, and Qu Lin was plucked out of thin air.

Before he had a chance to even struggle, the black hand vanished into thin air, then abruptly reappeared in the Eon Palace, having shrunk down significantly.

The black hand then dissipated into thin air, dropping Qu Lin onto the ground, and the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was ecstatic to see him.

"It's you! It's been so long since I've had a good punching bag, my prayers have been answered!"

Immediately thereafter, he appeared directly in front of Qu Lin amid a burst of spatial fluctuations before throwing a punch at him.

A horrified look appeared on Qu Lin's face upon seeing this, and he instantly transformed into a giant, Gold Devouring Beetle that was over a hundred feet in size.

The giant beetle swept its front legs forcefully through the air, releasing countless streaks of translucent, golden light that rained down upon the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

However, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity merely continued onward, taking no evasive measures, and the streaks of golden light merely passed through him in an innocuous fashion, as if there were no substance to his body.

However, in the instant that the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's fist came into contact with the golden beetle's head, his body regained its substantial form, and the giant beetle was sent flying back through the air before crashing into a nearby wall with a resounding thump.

The walls of the Eon Palace were constructed from special materials, so they were very difficult to destroy even without the fortification of any restrictions.

The Almighty Sword Sect cultivators just so happened to have been gathered there, and Lei Yuce and the others hurriedly dispersed while carrying the still unconscious Daoist Master Dao Yin away.

After crashing into the wall, the giant beetle fell down onto the ground with a dazed look in its eyes, seemingly having had its mind scrambled by the force of the punch.

A shallow fist indentation could be seen on its incredibly hard exoskeleton, but it hadn't shattered.

"Your shell has become a lot harder than last time! Looks like I don't have to hold back as much as before!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity remarked as he appeared beside the golden beetle once again, then threw another punch its way.

The golden beetle instantly shrank down to only around the size of a human fist, then flew away at an incredible speed.

However, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was able to somehow get in front of it to intercept it in the blink of an eye as he chuckled, "You're not getting away!"

The golden beetle was sent flying once again by another almighty punch, and it crashed into another wall with a loud thump.

Much of the golden light around the beetle's body was scattered from the force of the blow, and it involuntarily reverted back to its original size.

"It's been a long time since I've gotten some exercise!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity chuckled to himself, then abruptly appeared beside the golden beetle once again before sending it flying with another punch.

This time, the punch had struck the beetle on the body rather than its head, so it remained conscious and lucid, and as soon as it fell to the ground, it immediately laid flat against the ground in a submissive pose.

"Please forgive me, Senior Shi, I shouldn't have tried to spy on your. Please spare me!" the golden beetle implored, knowing that any further attempt to escape would be completely futile.

"What are you rambling on about? I'm only just getting warmed up!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity harrumphed coldly as he flew over to the golden beetle before kicking it away.

His annoyance had been steadily mounting from Han Li and Qi Mozi's bickering, but he had no choice but to tolerate it for the sake of his wife and son, and Qu Lin's arrival had presented him with the perfect opportunity to vent his frustration.

Hence, the golden beetle was transformed into a true punching bag, being kicked and punched back and forth by the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was using only his physical strength without injecting any law powers into his attacks, so even though Qu Lin was being thoroughly bruised and battered, he hadn't sustained any severe injuries.

Chapter 1124: Remnants of Tai Sui's Soul

Never had Han Li and the others witnessed such a farcical sight. A peak-Great Encompassment cultivator was darting around back and forth right before their eyes, chasing around a golden beetle like a mortal chasing after a fly.

Qu Lin wanted to beg for mercy on several occasions, but he was always cut off by the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's blows.

Everyone could only look on with dumbstruck expressions while occasionally dodging to the side to avoid being struck by the flying Qu Lin.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity had forbidden them from leaving, so they didn't dare to stray too far away for fear of incurring his wrath.

Right at this moment, a streak of white light shot forth from afar, then faded to reveal the azure-robed man riding atop Lekima.

Han Li, Fox 3, and Wyrm 3 were ecstatic to see him, while Qi Mozi was clearly less than enthused by his arrival.

"Please have mercy, Fellow Daoist Dark Heavens," the azure-robed man implored as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of gray light, attempting to break Qu Lin's fall.

However, Qu Lin had been struck with such tremendous force that he tore straight through the gray light before crashing into a nearby wall, causing it to collapse.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity seemed to be in a much better mood after taking out his frustrations on Qu Lin, and he turned to the azure-robed man as he asked, "What are you doing here, Liu Zizai? Are you trying to get in my way as well?"

"I came here to congratulate you on regaining your freedom, Fellow Daoist Shi. On top of that, my bonded soul tablet is here, and I've come to retrieve it now that the restriction here has been broken," Liu Zizai replied, only to have his expression instantly stiffen upon catching sight of the destroyed five-colored altar in the palace.

His gaze then quickly turned to Qi Mozi, and his expression instantly darkened slightly.

Meanwhile, Lekima was scouring its gaze over everyone in the palace, unable to detect who was in possession of its bonded soul tablet.

"I have some matters to attend to right now, so your bonded soul tablet will have to wait. Seeing as you're a corpse soul of Liu Qi's, I'll help you look for the tablet later, but for now, stay out of my way!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity harrumphed coldly.

So he's a corpse soul of Patriarch Liu Qi's...

Han Li was instantly struck by a sense of enlightenment upon hearing this.

With that in mind, it was no wonder that he had been reminded of Patriarch Liu Qi back when he first met Liu Zizai, and on top of that, the two of them had also mastered the same type of law powers.

Han Li then shook his head to rid himself of these trivial thoughts, refocusing his attention on the situation at hand.

All of a sudden, a thought seemed to have occurred to him, and he communicated something to Fox 3 through voice transmission.

Fox 3 took a glance at him, then quickly gave a barely perceptible nod.

"You have my thanks then, Fellow Daoist Shi," Liu Zizai replied with a nod.

Right at this moment, Qu Lin's feeble voice rang out.

"Save me, Fellow Daoist Liu..."

His physical body was near indestructible, but the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's physical prowess was even more formidable, and after taking such an extensive beating, his entire body was riddled with wounds, and even all of his orifices were leaking golden blood, presenting a very sorry sight to behold.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, you're a peak-Great Encompassment cultivator with powers far superior to ours, so why go after Qu Lin? He may have been spying on the Eon Palace in secret earlier, but that was only for the sake of his bonded soul tablet, so please forgive him," Liu Zizai implored as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"You can take him away. I feel a lot more loose and limber now that I've had some exercise, so I'll save him for next time," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity replied with a casual wave of his hand.

Qu Lin shuddered slightly at the thought of a "next time", but overall, he was very relieved to have finally been spared.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Shi," Liu Zizai said with an elated expression, then swept a sleeve through the to release a burst of gray light that carried the golden beetle back to his side.

The golden beetle reverted back to Qu Lin's human form, and his face was bruised and battered beyond recognition, presenting a rather comical sight to behold.

With that, Liu Zizai was just about to depart when he suddenly took a glance at Fox 3, and an intrigued look appeared in his eyes as he stopped in his tracks.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, now that the Eon Divine Lamp restriction has been broken, you and I have been freed. Do you have any plans from here onward? Would you be interested in paying our Heavenly Fox Tribe a visit?" Liu Zizai asked.

"I'll pass this time. I've found out where my wife and son are, and I'm going to rescue them so that I can finally be reunited with them. That fox den of yours probably stinks anyway," Dark Heavens Devilish Deity chuckled in response.

"Is that right? That's certainly fantastic news! Please allow me to offer my congratulations. May I ask how you managed to find out the whereabouts of your wife and son?" Liu Zizai asked.

For some reason, a sense of foreboding welled up in Qi Mozi's heart at this line of questioning, and he secretly slid his right hand up his sleeve.

"Fellow Daoist Qi Mozi here told me that he's going to take me to Jin Ling and my son," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity replied as he pointed at Qi Mozi.

"You're going to trust him to take you to your wife and son? Are you not aware that he's the current chief warden of the Immortal Prison?" Liu Zizai asked with a surprised expression.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity seemed to be quite trusting of Liu Zizai, and he immediately turned to Qi Mozi with a cold expression as he asked, "Why is he also saying that you're the chief warden of the Immortal Prison? Is that true?"

"Don't be fooled by their lies, Fellow Daoist Shi!" Qi Mozi hurriedly replied.

"I think this will tell you all that you need to know, Fellow Daoist Shi," Liu Zizai said as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a ball of gray light.

On the surface of the ball of light was an image depicting the scene where Qi Mozi had approached the White Bone King and the Copper Lion King, and their conversation rang out as clear as day, while Qi Mozi presented his chief warden badge to them.

"How dare you lie to me!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity roared as he turned to Qi Mozi with a look of murderous rage in his eyes, but Qi Mozi was already prepared for the worst, and he instantly released his Time Severing Fire Domain, encompassing everyone within it.

Everyone was instantly immobilized within the Time Severing Fire Domain, while Qi Mozi flew away as quickly as he could as a streak of golden light.

"You won't trap me with this flimsy little Time Severing Fire Domain of yours!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity roared as a burst of black light erupted out of his body in all directions, instantly tearing the Time Severing Fire Domain apart.

Immediately thereafter, he reached out with one hand, and an enormous, black hand that took up half of the entire sky instantly emerged before grabbing down onto Qi Mozi.

A burst of overwhelming compressive force converged toward Qi Mozi from all directions, slowing him down significantly, yet right as he was about to be captured by the giant hand, a burst of blinding, golden light erupted out of his body, lighting up the entire sky.

In the next instant, a ball of golden light that was thousands of feet in size appeared, resembling an incandescent, golden sun as it hurtled toward the giant, black hand.

The two clashed with a resounding boom, and the nearby space shuddered violently before shattering into countless pieces.

Qi Mozi fell out of the ball of golden light with blood flowing out of all of his orifices, yet even as he came plummeting toward the ground, he was still clutching the Eon Divine Lamp tightly in his hands.

A burst of golden light emerged over his body, and he was able to stabilize himself before continuing to fly away without so much as a turn of his head.

Even following his departure, the ball of golden light still remained, and it abruptly swelled even further in size as countless thin tendrils of golden flames erupted forth from within, instantly punching countless holes into the giant, black hand.

In the blink of an eye, the giant hand was completely eradicated.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was looking up at the ball of golden light with excitement glowing in his eyes, seemingly having already completely forgotten all about Qi Mozi.

In the next instant, the ball of golden light transformed into a golden figure that was giving off an aura of unmatched authority, but his features were rather blurred and difficult to make out.

Lei Yuce and the Almighty Sword Sect cultivators were ecstatic to see this golden figure.

"It's our patriarch!"

"I knew it! Our patriarch has never left this pagoda all these years!"

All of the Almighty Sword Sect cultivators immediately fell to their knees and began kowtowing to the golden figure in excitement and reverence.

"So that's why the Eon Divine Lamp is still so powerful even with no one controlling it. I should've figured that you had implanted a fragment of your soul within it, Tai Sui!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity harrumphed coldly.

The golden figure looked down at the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity in silence, and in the next instant, black and golden light erupted from their bodies in unison before clashing with tremendous force.

The half-ruined Eon Palace was instantly destroyed, but its ground remained intact, perhaps due to the presence of the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array.

Han Li and the others were sent flying by the shockwaves from the clash, and they took advantage of this opportunity to get far away from the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity and the golden figure.

Chapter 1125: Hunting Qi Mozi

While the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was locked in battle against Tai Sui's soul fragment, bursts of rumbling could be heard ringing out incessantly within the dark clouds in the sky, although there was no lightning to be seen.

Gusts of fierce wind were sweeping through the air, while the ground trembled incessantly, and the entire Eon Pagoda seemed to be shaking.

"Brother Han, we have to recover the Eon Divine Lamp from Qi Mozi," Wyrm 3 said with a serious expression.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face as he said, "Qi Mozi is a very cunning and powerful Great Encompassment cultivator, and his powers will only have been further elevated now that he's in possession of the Eon Divine Lamp, so I don't think it would be wise to go after him."

At this point, he had already been completely freed from the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's influence, so he was nowhere near as enticed by the idea of claiming the Eon Divine Lamp as before.

"Is Qi Mozi not a sworn enemy of yours, Brother Han? Surely you can't back down now," Wyrm 3 hurriedly said.

"That's true, but at the moment, there's a clear power disparity between us. On top of that, with the Eon Divine Lamp displaced, the restrictions in the pagoda have been undone, so it's most likely not a good idea to stay here," Han Li replied.

"Alright, let me come clean to you, Brother Han. Not only has Qi Mozi taken the Eon Divine Lamp, he's also taken an item of great importance to our Reincarnation Palace, and it must be recovered. As a Reincarnation Disciple, you have an obligation to join me in this endeavor," Wyrm 3 insisted as a hint of urgency appeared in her eyes.

"Please don't try to force me into this, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3. I may be a Reincarnation Disciple, but no mission to recover the item in question has been assigned to me by the Reincarnation Palace, so I have no obligation to do anything," Han Li countered.

Wyrm 3's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and after a brief silence, she suddenly switched to voice transmission as she said, "Brother Han, if I recall correctly, you're very close with someone called Jin Tong, right? Right now, they're not in the best of situations."

"What do you mean by that?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"It's a long story, too long for me to tell now, but all you need to know is that taking down Qi Mozi is of great importance to saving your friend as well, so please do not hesitate any longer. Qi Mozi has mastered the laws of time, so without your help, it's going to be very difficult for me to go after him," Wyrm 3 urged as a hint of agitation appeared on her face.

While the two of them were conversing with each other, Fox 3 and Liu Zizai had already set off in pursuit of Qi Mozi. After all, the latter's bonded soul tablet was still in Qi Mozi's possession.

"In that case, I'm willing to help you, but in exchange, I want the Eon Divine Lamp. Is that acceptable to you?" Han Li asked.

Given his bad blood with Qi Mozi, he was also very tempted to take advantage of this opportunity to hunt him down. However, he naturally wasn't going to pass up the opportunity to have Wyrm 3 owe him a favor.

Furthermore, the mention of Jin Tong also had him feeling a little concerned, and that gave him even more of an incentive to go after Qi Mozi.

"Alright, I can agree to that condition, but everything else in Qi Mozi's possession has to be left to me," Wyrm 3 replied without any hesitation.

She was naturally aware that Han Li was taking advantage of the situation to his own benefit, but that didn't matter to her. Her primary objective was to obtain the black tablet, and outside of that, everything was negotiable.

Han Li naturally raised no objections to this, and Wyrm 3 immediately departed.

Right at this moment, a streak of silver light shot forth from the ruins of the Eon Palace. It was the Essence Fire Raven, and clasped in its beak was the white bead that was one of the five immortal treasures in the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array.

Looks like the array is no longer able to function without anyone operating it.

With that in mind, Han Li stowed the fire raven away, then took a glance at the ongoing battle between the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity and the Tai Sui soul fragment, and he was just about to depart when he spotted Qu Lin and Lekima, both of which had adopted their human forms and were searching for something within the wreckage of the Eon Palace.

He flew over to them with a smile as he said, "Come and help us recover the lamp from Qi Mozi, fellow daoists."

"Go away! I'm busy!" Lekima grumbled without even bothering to spare a glance at Han Li.

"How about you, Fellow Daoist Qu? You promised to help me take down a sworn enemy of mine, and he's right over there," Han Li said as he pointed into the distance, where Qi Mozi had been intercepted by Wyrm 3 and the others.

"I have no intention of going back on my promise, but right now I have more important things to do, and it looks like you have more than enough allies to help you deal with that enemy of yours," Qu Lin replied.

"That's a real shame. I guess I'll be keeping these two things to myself then," Han LI said with a smile.

Qu Lin and Lekima immediately turned to him upon hearing this, and they discovered that he was holding a pair of crimson tablets in his hand.

Han Li had originally intended to keep these two bonded soul tablets hidden, particularly Qu Lin's one as having it in his possession would ensure that Qu Lin would be at his mercy in his inevitable future showdown against Jin Tong.

Hence, Han Li had placed a restriction upon them and placed them into the Flower Branch domain so that they couldn't be detected, but he had no choice but to bring them out now in order to convince them to help him.

"So you did get it! Rest assured, I promised you handsome compensation in exchange for my bonded soul tablet, and I fully intend to follow through on that promise!" Lekima said with a wide grin.

"I appreciate it, but all that can wait until we've taken down Qi Mozi," Han Li said as he stowed the pair of tablets away.

"You cunning little bastard! Fine, we'll do as you say," Lekima grumbled with a displeased expression, then instantly vanished from the spot as a white whirlwind, while Han Li and Qu Lin also set off after him.

At this point, the Almighty Sword Sect cultivators had already fled to hundreds of kilometers away, and Daoist Master Dao Yin finally regained consciousness while being carried on Lei Yuce's back.

He turned to discover the chaotic scene behind him, and he asked in a slightly feeble voice, "What happened?"

Lei Yuce was ecstatic to see that Daoist Master Dao Yin had woken up, and he hurriedly set him down before giving him a brief recount of everything that had happened during his stint of unconsciousness.

"This is terrible!" Daoist Master Dao Yin sighed after hearing Lei Yuce's recount. "With the Eon Divine Lamp displaced, all of the restrictions in the Eon Pagoda have been lifted. If those beings imprisoned in the pagoda manage to escape, then countless lives will surely be lost across the entire Golden Origin Immortal Region."

"There's nothing we can do about that, Sect Master. We're extremely fortunate just to still be alive," an elder said.

"No, I have to do something. The reputation of the Almighty Sword Sect cannot be tarnished by my incompetence. Even our patriarch's soul fragment is currently still battling the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, and I have to do my part too. I have to recover the lamp and seal away all of the malicious beings in the pagoda again, even if it costs me my life!" Daoist Master Dao Yin declared in a determined manner.

"Master, the lamp has already been displaced for quite some time, so all of the beings imprisoned in the pagoda have most likely already escaped. The disciples of our sect stationed outside the pagoda should be able to impede those beings for some time, so what we need to do now is leave the Eon Pagoda as soon as possible and activate the backup measures that our patriarch left in place," Lei Yuce hurriedly urged.

"You're saying we should destroy the Eon Pagoda and this entire space?" Daoist Master Dao Yin asked.

"But if we do that, won't all of the cultivators in the secret area be killed as well?" Su Anqian asked.

"I'm afraid that's a sacrifice that must be made. If those forces of evil are allowed to escape into the immortal region, then far more people will lose their lives," Lei Yuce said in a grim manner.

"Given the urgency of the situation, this is the only course of action available to us. These people came into this secret area to satisfy their own greed, so they only have themselves to blame for losing their lives here. The lamp must be recovered to restore the glory of our sect!" Daoist Master Dao Yin declared with a solemn expression.

Su Anqian opened her mouth to say something, but ultimately remained silent.

The group then set off toward the edge of the seventh level. With all of the restrictions undone, they could directly exit the pagoda from there.

Not long after their departure, a nearby black rock suddenly rolled away to the side, following which Xiong Shan emerged from underground.

He removed a golden talisman from his own glabella, then carefully stowed it away as he murmured to himself, "Those bastards are planning to destroy the entire secret area! Looks like I have to get out of this place right away..."

He then swept a sleeve through the air, and a golden longsword and a yellow seal appeared before him. These were none other than the Primordial Ancient Sword and the Vast Earth Seal that he had taken from the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, and a pleased smile appeared on his face at the sight of them.

I may have almost lost my life here, but it's all worth it in the end.

After that, he stowed the two immortal treasures away, then took a glance at the chaotic battlefield in the distance as he murmured to himself, "You guys can keep fooling around over there, I'm getting out of here!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he spotted a streak of blue light flying through the air overhead, and it seemed to be Lan Yan.

His brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, following which he also departed as a streak of golden light

Chapter 1126: Battling Qi Mozi

At the same time, the area outside the Eon Pagoda had already descended into complete chaos.

A series of massive cracks had begun to appear over the entire pagoda, within which silver light was flashing incessantly, giving off bursts of formidable spatial fluctuations.

Before long, a steady stream of living beings of all types of different descriptions began rushing out of the silver light, and their cultivation bases varied drastically as well.

The cultivators stationed outside the pagoda were naturally quite startled by this, and they tried to flee the scene, but many of the living beings that flew out of the Eon Pagoda immediately attacked them on sight, leaving them with no choice but to stand and fight.

Initially, they were able to hold a comfortable upper hand thanks to their numbers advantage, but as more and more of these living beings continued to stream out of the pagoda, the tables gradually began to turn, and a horrific battle ensued in which both sides suffered severe casualties.

......

Meanwhile, Han Li and Qu Lin were flying toward Qi Mozi, and even from afar, they could see Wyrm 3's reincarnation spirit domain, which encompassed an area that was hundreds of kilometers in size.

Inside her dark red spirit domain was another golden spirit domain, and that was none other than Qi Mozi's time spirit domain.

Upon flying into the two spirit domains, Lekima was instantly slowed down significantly.

An alarmed look appeared on its face, and gusts of fierce, white wind began sweeping out of its hooves, stirring up the surrounding space and restoring much of its original speed.

In the instant that Han Li and Qu Lin flew onto the scene, the former immediately released his own time spirit domain to encompass the two of them, and they discovered that Qi Mozi was already locked in a battle against Wyrm 3 and the others.

"Hand over what you obtained from the altar, and we'll let you go," Wyrm 3 yelled.

"What threat do you pose to me now that I have the Eon Divine Lamp?" Qi Mozi harrumphed coldly.

"What if we throw ourselves into the mix as well?" Han Li asked, and Qi Mozi's expression instantly changed slightly at the sight of him, Lekima, and Qu Lin.

Wyrm 3 and the others were already quite troublesome to deal with, so he would certainly struggle immensely to take on Han Li's trio in addition to them.

On top of that, Qu Lin, Liu Zizai, and Lekima were all Great Encompassment cultivators, so even with the Eon Divine Lamp in his possession, this was still clearly a losing battle.

However, instead of displaying any fear or timidity, a sly grin appeared on his face as he flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized, crimson tablet.

"This is your bonded soul tablet, right? If you don't want me to destroy it, then kill him!" Qi Mozi commanded as his gaze fell upon Liu Zizai.

Liu Zizai could see that Qi Mozi was pointing directly at Han Li, and a hesitant look appeared on his face.

"Hurry up or I'll crush this tablet right now!" Qi Mozi threatened in a menacing fashion.

"My apologies..."

A hint of indignation flashed through Liu Zizai's eyes, following which he began to fly toward Han Li, only to be intercepted by Qu Lin.

"I'm afraid I can't let you do that, Old Man Liu."

Lekima hesitated momentarily, then conjured up a massive tornado that swept up Qu Lin and Liu Zizai before sending them flying far away into the distance.

"How about now? With those three gone, do you still dare to challenge me?" Qi Mozi sneered.

Han Li, Fox 3, and Wyrm 3 exchanged a glance and a nod, and the three of them split up to surround Qi Mozi in a triangular formation.

"I admire your courage, but I'm assuming your courage only stands on the basis that you don't know the true power of the Eon Divine Lamp," Qi Mozi sneered, and a hint of foreboding welled up in the hearts of Han Li's trio upon hearing this.

"Let me show you what you're dealing with!" Qi Mozi declared as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing the Eon Divine Lamp, while began to revolve incessantly before him.

His aura instantly began to swell drastically as his robes flapped audibly despite the absence of wind, and a golden torch emerged in front of him.

A fervent look appeared in his eyes as his gaze fell upon the torch and the Eon Divine Lamp, and countless rays of golden light instantly erupted out of the flame at the center of the lamp, making it resemble a dazzling, golden sun that was hanging in the sky, releasing layers upon layers of golden ripples that caused the nearby clouds to churn violently.

The sense of foreboding in Han Li's heart instantly became more pronounced upon seeing this, and he hurriedly yelled, "Stop him!"

At the same time, he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might while sweeping a sleeve through the air to release thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which combined to form a single sword that hurtled directly toward Qi Mozi.

Wyrm 3 immediately followed his lead, releasing an octagonal badge, which, in turn, released a huge cloud of dark red mist that formed an imposing wall before advancing toward Qi Mozi.

At the same time, Fox 3 lashed out with his Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, unleashing a massive, crimson blade projection that was several thousand feet in length, slicing through the very heavens en route to Qi Mozi.

Their attacks were all extremely formidable, and even the average Great Encompassment cultivator definitely wouldn't have dared to disregard them.

However, Qi Mozi seemed to have been completely oblivious to the danger that he was in as he focused the entirety of his attention on bringing his Time Severing Torch and the Eon Divine Lamp together.

Right as the attacks from Han Li's trio were about to fall upon him, the Time Severing Torch and the Eon Divine Lamp finally fused together, and in the same instant, a burst of blinding, golden light was released.

The golden light was countless times brighter than even the light of the sun, forcing Han Li's trio to shield their own eyes.

Han Li heard a resounding boom coming from Qi Mozi's direction, immediately following which he was sent flying back through the air in an involuntary fashion by a burst of tremendous force.

After steadying himself, Han Li immediately made a beckoning motion to drawn his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword back into his grasp, following which he cast his gaze toward Qi Mozi, and he was greeted by the sight of an enormous shadow that resembled a giant pillar.

However, it was only after the smoke cleared that he discovered that the so-called giant pillar was actually none other than the Eon Divine Lamp, which had swelled to over a thousand feet tall!

"Is that... the Eon Divine Lamp?" Wyrm 3 exclaimed.

Han Li turned to her to discover that her hair was a little messy and disheveled, but she was unharmed.

"It looks like he must've used some type of secret technique to completely take control of the Eon Divine Lamp. However, there's no way that he can keep this up for long, so we just have to weather the storm," Han Li said with slightly furrowed brows.

"I don't think it's that simple," Fox 3 said as he flew over to join them, and he was also looking a little disheveled. "Even though he's somehow made the lamp expand to such an enormous size, its aura has remained completely restrained and self-contained, and that's not normal at all."

"You're right," Han Li said as a grim look appeared on his face. "Qi Mozi has somehow managed to fuse the Eon Divine Lamp with his spirit domain, making it resemble a domain spirit of sorts. This could spell trouble for us."

Right at this moment, Qi Mozi appeared on the Eon Divine Lamp, standing on one of its lotus flower petals as he looked down at Han Li's trio with a triumphant smile on his face.

"What do you think of your chances now, Fellow Daoist Han?" he yelled in a goading voice.

Before Han Li had a chance to reply, he cast an incantation seal into the lamp beneath him, and it shuddered violently, as did the flame within it, which then exploded into countless golden fireballs that erupted in all directions.

Han Li's trio hurriedly scattered to take evasive measures upon seeing this.

After the golden fireballs landed on the ground, they refused to dissipate. Instead, they transformed into countless golden lamps, each of which was around ten feet tall, resembling miniature clones of the massive Eon Divine Lamp.

These golden lamps were littered throughout the entire spirit domain, with one present roughly every one hundred or so feet.

Han Li quickly discovered that with the emergence of these miniature lamps, the time law power fluctuations in Qi Mozi's spirit domain had swelled in potency by tenfold, so even though Han Li's trio were sheltered within his time spirit domain, their movements were still severely inhibited.

Right at this moment, Qi Mozi swept both sleeves through the air, and countless specks of red light flew out from within, instantly taking up a large section of the sky above.

"Those are Fire Age Fireflies!" Han Li yelled in an alarmed manner, and as soon as his voice trailed off, the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies split up into three before flying toward Han Li's trio.

Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 hurriedly adopted defensive measures to protect themselves upon hearing this.

A layer of silver light that was riddled with runes emerged over Wyrm 3's robes, giving off a burst of spatial law powers that enveloped her entire body.

Meanwhile, a suit of silver armor emerged over Fox 3's body, covering him from head to toe.

Chapter 1127: Fooled

Han Li didn't dare to take the oncoming Fire Age Fireflies lightly, and his Mantra Treasured Axis instantly appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

As soon as the Fire Age Fireflies drew close to him, they instantly came to a near-standstill, as if they had crashed into an invisible wall.

Han Li felt slightly reassured upon seeing this, and he was just about to pull out his Profound Heavenly Gourd to suck in the Fire Age Fireflies when he noticed something rather unsettling.

A layer of golden flames had appeared over the bodies of all of the Fire Age Fireflies, and the golden flames were constantly whittling away at the golden light released by his Mantra Treasured Axis.

As the rays of golden light were gradually eradicated, the Fire Age Fireflies began to regain their speed of movement, and it was clear that these Fire Age Fireflies were of a far higher caliber than all of the ones that he had encountered in the past.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 had already been completely surrounded by Fire Age Fireflies, and even though the layer of silver light around her body was still intact, it was riddled with holes and clearly on the verge of giving out.

As for Fox 3, he was in an even worse situation. His suit of silver armor offered him barely any protection against the Fire Age Fireflies, so he could only hurriedly take evasive measures, and in the process, he inadvertently crashed into one of the Eon Divine Lamp clones.

A fiery, crimson wyrm instantly erupted out of the lamp before pouncing at Fox 3, who hurriedly retaliated by lashing out with his Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, unleashing a massive, crimson saber projection that swept up hundreds of Fire Age Fireflies before striking the fiery wyrm.

The fiery wyrm was instantly torn to shreds before exploding into a flurry of flames, and Fox 3 had only just had a chance to heave a faint sigh of relief upon seeing this when two other divine lamp clones also lit up, following which two more fiery wyrms pounced out of them from either side of Fox 3, biting down onto his shoulders before he had a chance to react.

As a result, he was instantly locked into place before being overwhelmed by the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies around him.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Inundated by the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies, Fox 3's life force began to rapidly seep away, and his aura also gradually began to wane.

If he wasn't rescued in short order, then he was going to be in a truly dire situation.

With that in mind, Han Li gritted his teeth as he swept a sleeve through the air to release thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which transformed into countless azure sword projections that intertwined with one another to form a huge net before sweeping toward the Fire Age Fireflies.

At the same time, his Mantra Treasured Axis was withdrawn back into his body before revolving in reverse, drastically enhancing his speed as he rushed toward Fox 3.

No longer impeded by the Mantra Treasured Axis, the Fire Age Fireflies instantly reverted back to their original speed, and even though most of them were intercepted by the net of sword projections, some were still able to slip through the cracks to pursue Han Li.

However, this was simply a compromise that Han Li was forced to accept as he flew over to Fox 3's side, then channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts before lashing out with both fists at the two lamp clones on either side of Fox 3.

Two resounding thumps rang out in unison as the pair of lamp clones were destroyed, exploding into countless specks of golden flames, while the fiery wyrms extending out of them were also eradicated.

However, right at this moment, all of the Fire Age Fireflies clinging to Fox 3 suddenly turned back around to target Han Li instead, and as a result, he was sandwiched between two swarms of Fire Age Fireflies.

There was no time for him to take evasive measures, and several hundred Fire Age Fireflies instantly fell upon him.

To compound his woes even further, a burst of formidable time law power fluctuations erupted out of the specks of fire that the pair of eradicated lamp clones had disintegrated into, and Han Li was instantly rooted to the spot.

In the next instant, Qi Mozi abruptly appeared before him amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, then grabbed onto the front of his robe.

"I've got you now!" he sneered.

"Brother Han!" Fox 3 called out in an alarmed voice.

At the same time, a burst of formidable reincarnation law power fluctuations erupted out of Wyrm 3's body, and all of the Fire Age Fireflies around her quickly began dropping to the ground, having entered a state of hibernation.

Wyrm 3's brows furrowed tightly at the sight of the dire situation that Han Li was in, and she immediately began flying in his direction.

However, she had only managed to travel no more than a thousand feet when all of the lamp projections around her began to glow radiantly before releasing a series of fiery wyrms, all of which intertwined with one another to form an obstructive barrier in her path.

Qi Mozi turned his gaze to Wyrm 3, then took a glance at Fox 3 before returning his gaze to Han Li as he sneered, "Looks like no one can save you this time!"

A burst of golden flames erupted out of his hand as he spoke, instantly inundating Han Li's entire body.

"Brother Han!" Fox 3 yelled in a distraught voice as he raised his Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, but before he had a chance to swing it, Qi Mozi casually swept a sleeve in his direction, releasing a ball of golden flames that struck him on the chest to send him flying back through the air.

Wyrm 3 was also looking on with a furious expression, but all she could do was watch helplessly as Han Li was devoured by the golden flames.

Qi Mozi remained holding onto the front of Han Li's robe as if he were holding a torch aloft, watching with immense satisfaction as Han Li's body was slowly incinerated into ashes.

As Han Li's body slowly burned away, black ashes began to fall out of the fire, but no nascent soul emerged.

A cold sneer appeared on Qi Mozi's face upon seeing this, and he raised his other hand, upon which a series of fiery, golden lotus flowers appeared around him, forming a massive cage that completely restricted the entire surrounding space.

A tall figure appeared within the cage of golden lotus flowers, and it was none other than Han Li.

"Did you really think you could fool me again with a substitution puppet?" Qi Mozi sneered as he turned to face Han Li.

At this moment, not only was Han Li completely immobilized within the cage of golden lotus flowers, the flames burning over the lotus flowers were constantly lapping at him, sending bursts of excruciating, burning pain spearing into his body, causing his expression to become twisted with agony.

Qi Mozi had no intention of wasting any time, flying over to Han Li in a flash before grabbing onto his head with a white-knuckled grip.

Han Li instantly felt as if his head were about to explode, and he couldn't help but let loose an agonized cry.

Qi Mozi seemed to be very fond of hearing the sounds of Han Li's suffering, and he tightened his grip even further.

Han Li's face had turned deathly pale, and his eyes were bulging outward, looking as if they were about to explode at any moment.

A frantic look appeared on Wyrm 3's face upon seeing this, and she thrust a palm forward to release a dark red badge, which flew through the air while swelling rapidly in size.

As she injected more and more of her law powers into the badge, it expanded to the size of a city gate while giving off rays of dark red light that proliferated in all directions, causing the surrounding divine lamp clones to disappear one after another.

Fox 3 was also storming back into the fray right behind Wyrm 3, and his Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber was glowing with radiant, crimson light, but Qi Mozi merely turned to look at the two of them with a mocking sneer on his face.

"We won't make it in time..." Wyrm 3 said in a despairing voice.

All of a sudden, Han Li's head exploded like an overripe watermelon under Qi Mozi's vice-like grip, and looks of grief and despair instantly appeared in the eyes of Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 at this horrific sight.

Qi Mozi paid no heed to the two of them as he plucked Han Li's nascent soul out of his headless body, and a cold smile of satisfaction appeared on his face as he chuckled, "Looks like the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra is going to be mine, after all."

The nascent soul was struggling with all its might, but had no chance of breaking free.

A layer of black light appeared over Qi Mozi's eyes, following which two thin threads of black light shot out of his pupils before wrapping themselves around Han Li's nascent soul.

Using this secret method, he could successfully search any nascent soul as long as it belonged to a cultivator of an inferior cultivation base to himself, even if there were restrictions placed upon said nascent soul. Furthermore, most of the power of the nascent soul in question would also be absorbed by him, so very little of it would go to waste.

However, as soon as the black threads of light shot out of his eyes, his expression instantly changed drastically as a look of chilling realization appeared on his face, but it was already too late.

All of a sudden, Han Li's headless body vanished into thin air amid a burst of law power fluctuations, as did his nascent soul.

At the same time, the azure-robed Liu Zizai appeared beside Wyrm 3 with a faint smile on his face.

Thanks to the seamless collaborative effort between his illusory law powers and Wyrm 3's reincarnation law powers, they had managed to completely fool Qi Mozi at the cost of a substitution puppet.

Chapter 1128: Obtaining the Divine Lamp

Right at this moment, a white whirlwind swept onto the scene from afar, and it was none other than Lekima.

Han Li sprang down from Lekima's back, and bursts of radiant, golden light surged out of his body as manifestations of all five of his time-attribute law treasures appeared in rapid succession to form an encirclement around Qi Mozi.

The five time-attribute law treasure manifestations lit up in unison, and a flurry of time law threads flew out of them before fusing together, following which they began to glow with dazzling, five-colored light, as if they had been set alight by a five-colored flame.

A look of shock and horror appeared on Qi Mozi's face before instantly stiffening as the five-colored light washed over him.

Immediately thereafter, layers upon layers of projections of himself appeared over his body before fading away one after another.

Meanwhile, everyone else was looking on with stunned expressions from thousands of feet away, and no one dared to approach Han Li as they could all sense that Qi Mozi's cultivation base was gradually receding, all the way until he reverted back into a High Zenith cultivator.

However, at the same time, the five-colored light was also rapidly dimming, looking as if it could fade away at any moment.

Right as the five-colored light completely vanished, Han Li let loose a thunderous roar as he channeled his true spirit bloodlines and Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts in unison, instantly transforming into a devilish deity with three heads and six arms before reaching out with two of his hands at once, one aimed at Qi Mozi's dantian, and the other at his heart.

Two dull thumps rang out as Han Li's hand was able to tear through Qi Mozi's chest before crushing his heart, but his other hand was not able to pierce into Qi Mozi's dantian.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he pulled back his hand in preparation to deal a finishing blow, but right at this moment, hundreds of Fire Age Fireflies erupted out of Qi Mozi's dantian alongside a burst of scorching heat before swarming toward Han Li.

Han Li's arm instantly turned charred black and withered as the Fire Age Fireflies crawled over his body.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, but the fiery, silver figure then sprang out of his shoulder before transforming into a wave of silver flames that inundated his arm along with the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies.

Right at this moment, a clump of golden law threads flew out of Qi Mozi's dantian. Enveloped within it was Qi Mozi's nascent soul with a look of burning resentment on its face, and it vanished from the spot in a flash before reappearing hundreds of kilometers just an instant later.

Fox 3 immediately took a step forward to set off in pursuit, only to be stopped by Liu Zizai.

"Don't bother. He's wrapped his own nascent soul in all of his time law threads, even Lekima won't be able to chase him down," Liu Zizai said in an indifferent manner.

Even before the Fire Age Fireflies clinging to his arm had been fully eradicated, Han Li had already reached out with his other hand to claim Qi Mozi's storage ring and storage bracelet, while the Eon Divine Lamp fell into Wyrm 3's grasp.

Everyone gathered together, and Wyrm 3 said, "Brother Han, we had an agreement..."

"Don't worry, I haven't forgotten. I told you I only want the Eon Divine Lamp, and that still stands," Han Li replied with a nod before tossing the pair of storage tools at Wyrm 3, who smiled as she tossed the Eon Divine Lamp at him in return.

After the items were examined to ensure that nothing was amiss about them, they were promptly stowed away.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I've already fulfilled my end of our agreement, so it's time for you to return my bonded soul tablet to me, right?" Lekima asked as he approached Han Li, who was just about to respond when the entire space abruptly shuddered violently.

Everyone immediately turned in the direction where the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was still locked in battle against Tai Sui's soul fragment, where they saw a streak of black light and a streak of golden light clashing over and over again with tremendous force.

Most of the enormous mountain below had already collapsed, while countless enormous rifts had been torn into the surrounding space, and the entire seventh level was trembling violently.

Thankfully, these spatial rifts were constantly being sucked away by the shockwaves from their clashes. Otherwise, the entire seventh level would've already collapsed.

The spatial rifts seemed to have no effect on the pair of combatants, and after yet another earth-shattering clash, the two streaks of light separated to reveal the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity and the golden soul fragment.

"It's been a long time since I've been able to fight to my heart's content like this!" the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity chortled as a burst of black light erupted out of his body before rapidly expanding to take up most of the entire sky.

Radiant, golden light was also emanating from the soul fragment's body to contend against the black light, but at the moment, the soul fragment was looking far frailer than before, and the golden light around it was completely enveloped within the all-encompassing black light, which was only continuing to spread.

Even though Han Li and the others were situated quite far away, it didn't take long for the black light to reach them, and the immortal spiritual power in their bodies was instantly thrown into a state of complete disarray, while their hearts began to thump violently as if they could explode at any moment.

On top of that, the scenery around them was rapidly changing, as if they had fallen into a boundless nightmare.

These were all precursors of imminent inner demon backlash!

Han Li's expression changed drastically as he hurriedly channeled all of the remaining time law powers in his body to protect himself while flying away into the distance.

However, due to the chaotic state of his immortal spiritual power, his speed was significantly hampered, and his time law powers were also failing to protect him as his inner demons continued to rear their ugly heads.

Liu Zizai, Wyrm 3 and the others were also frantically flying away while channeling their own law powers for protection, but it seemed like they were in a similar situation.

Thankfully, the black light didn't spread any further beyond this point, and even though everyone was flying very slowly, they were still eventually able to emerge from the black light, upon which all of the debilitating effects that they were experiencing quickly subsided.

Even so, they continued to fly away for some time before turning around to look at the vast expanse of black light behind them with stunned looks on their faces, and in particular, Liu Zizai, Qu Lin, and Lekima were clearly feeling a little depressed.

They were already aware that a massive disparity in power existed between them and the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, but they were still Great Encompassment cultivators, nonetheless, so they had thought that they would be able to fare much better in the face of his power, but that was clearly not the case.

If a true battle of life and death were to take place between them, even if the three of them were to join forces, they would still undoubtedly be easily crushed.

Meanwhile, Han Li was peering into the black light in the distance with a contemplative look in his eyes, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

Within the suffocating black light, the golden light around the soul fragment had been compressed significantly, shrinking down to a radiant ball of golden light that was several thousand feet in size, and it was only continuing to be compressed further and further.

"It's a real pity that all that remains of you is this soul fragment. There's no point in continuing this battle any longer," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity sighed as he swept a sleeve through the air, and nine giant, black hands, each of which was around an acre in size, abruptly appeared around the ball of golden light surrounding the soul fragment.

Every single one of the giant hands was giving off unmatched destructive power, staining the nearby space black while also causing it to crumble away.

The nine giant hands pressed forward in unison to strike the ball of golden light, which was instantly shattered into pieces, while the soul fragment was sent stumbling back through the air.

The nine giant hands were only stopped in their tracks for a split-second before continuing to crash down upon the soul fragment, but right at this moment, ten streaks of fiery, golden light erupted out of the soul fragment's body, all of which were imbued with immense time law powers.

After unleashing those ten streaks of light, the golden soul fragment's already dim body became even dimmer, and it had turned almost fully transparent.

Nine of the streaks of light struck the black hands to stop them cold in their tracks, while the final one tore through the surrounding black light before hurtling directly toward Han Li and the others, all of whom hurriedly scattered in an alarmed manner.

Han Li was also flying back in retreat, but the Eon Divine Lamp suddenly began to glow radiantly, and it became completely rooted to the spot in mid-air, refusing to budge even as Han Li tugged on it forcefully.

Countless golden flames emerged within the Eon Divine Lamp, and each one transformed into a fiery lotus flower, which then converged to form a bright sea of golden flames.

Han Li hurriedly released the lamp in an alarmed manner upon seeing this, then vanished from spot before reappearing several thousand feet away with his brows tightly furrowed.

He had finally managed to obtain the Eon Divine Lamp after so much painstaking effort, was he about to lose it again?

Chapter 1129: Oneness Tier

The final streak of golden light was incredibly fast, and it reached the Eon Divine Lamp in the blink of an eye before flying into the sea of golden flames within it.

A burst of tremendous time law powers surged out of the sea of golden flames before being injected into the streak of golden light, and the golden soul fragment in the distance instantly lit up as it quickly began to take on a more substantial form.

At the same time, it threw a punch forward, and over a hundred streams of golden fire erupted out of its fist in all directions like flowing, golden rivers.

Each stream of fire was tens of thousands of feet long, and they were giving off the same aura of inevitability and decay as the passage of time itself.

It could be said that the most fearsome thing under the heavens was the passage of time. Any life form, even cultivators who had attained so-called immortality, were still susceptible to the inevitable harvester of lives that was time.

The streams of golden fire were able to easily eradicate all of the nearby black light and then nine giant hands before hurtling toward the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

The nearby space was instantly enshrouded within a burst of tremendous time law powers that immobilized everything, including even the spatial rifts in the area and all of the spatial raging spatial turbulence within them.

Han Li and the others had thought that they had already retreated to a safe distance away, but they were still encompassed within this burst of time law powers, which instantly rooted them to the spot.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's eyes lit up with excitement as he chortled, "Brilliant! I didn't think that a mere soul fragment of yours would still have so much power!"

Radiant, black light emanated from his body as he spoke, plunging the entire surrounding area in a radius of several thousand feet into complete darkness.

At the same time, a black longsword appeared in his grasp, and it was enshrouded within a layer of black light that was constantly fluctuating in brightness, giving the sword an illusory appearance, as if it could vanish at any moment.

With a swing of the sword, over a hundred almighty, black sword projections were unleashed, and all types of horrific voices could be heard ringing out from the sword projections, including ghastly howls, agonized wails, deranged laughter, and enraged roars, culminating in a maddening cacophony that was enough to drive the listener insane.

Each of the sword projections struck one of the streams of golden flames with unerring accuracy, easily tearing huge rifts into the space in their path.

A string of earth-shattering booms rang out as an impasse ensued between the sword projections and golden flames, with neither side able to get the better of the other.

Two gargantuan bursts of law powers were clashing against each other, tearing the restrictive force in the nearby space to shreds, and as a result, Han Li and the others had their mobility restored.

"We have to get out of here! A battle between two peak-Great Encompassment cultivators could kill us at any moment!" Liu Zizai yelled as released a burst of gray light to sweep up Fox 3 before flying away into the distance.

Meanwhile, Han Li was observing the rivers of golden flames from afar while sensing the time law powers emanating from them, and the more he observed, the more inspired he felt.

However, this was not the time to be dwelling on inspiration, and he took one final glance at the radiant Eon Divine Lamp, then tore his gaze away with gritted teeth before also flying away into the distance.

Wyrm 3, Lekima, and Qu Lin had naturally all fled the scene as well.

Right at this moment, the golden soul fragment made a hand seal, and the golden light radiating from its body instantly increased in brightness by over tenfold.

A surprised look appeared on the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's face upon seeing this. The golden soul fragment was elevating its own power without considering the costs at all.

Before he had a chance to do anything, dazzling rays of golden light erupted out of the streams of golden flames, destroying all of the black sword projections before sweeping toward the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity from all directions.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, but he remained calm and composed as he rapidly maneuvered himself through the air while lashing out with his black sword in all directions.

Countless black sword projections fanned out around him like a blooming, black lotus flower, which was able to keep the oncoming rays of golden light at bay with ease.

Despite this, the golden soul fragment didn't appear disheartened, and it continued to make a rapid string of hand seals.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out as its body exploded into a vast expanse of blinding golden light, forming a golden world that encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers.

For the first time, a look of alarm appeared on the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's face.

All of the sudden, all of the rays of golden light in the air doubled back before converging to form an ovular body of golden light with a diameter of thousands of kilometers, hanging in the sky like a giant star.

All of the nearby golden and black light completely faded away, and everything descended into peace and quiet in an eerie fashion.

Is that a spirit domain?

Han Li couldn't help but turn around with an intrigued expression upon sensing what was happening behind him.

It seemed that the massive, golden star was indeed a spirit domain.

"That's a Oneness Tier spirit domain! Oneness Tier spirit domains possess a substantial form and are far more powerful than Spiritform and Creation Tier spirit domains! I didn't think that a mere soul fragment would be able to conjure up a spirit domain of this caliber. We have to get out of here right now!

“Its intention is most likely to detonate its own spirit domain to take down the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity with it!" Lekima yelled in a frantic voice, following which a large cloud emerged from its body to encompass both Han Li and Wyrm 3.

At the same time, a cloud also emerged from each of its four hooves, and its speed was instantly enhanced by severalfold as it darted away into the distance as a white shadow.

Qu Lin and Liu Zizai's expressions also changed drastically as they arrived at the same conclusion as Lekima, and Qu Lin took on his Gold Devouring Beetle form before racing away as a streak of golden light, vanishing into the distant sky in the blink of an eye.

Meanwhile, Liu Zizai opened his mouth to release a ball of gray light, which transformed into a door of gray light that was around ten feet tall and was giving off bursts of spatial power.

He immediately stepped into the door of light with Fox 3, and the two of them instantly vanished into thin air, while the door of gray light also faded away.

Immediately thereafter, the giant, golden star in the distance began to glow with blinding, golden light, and countless fiery patterns had also appeared over its surface.

On top of that, it was giving off a terrifying aura of annihilation, and even though it still hadn't been detonated, the nearby space was already trembling violently.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the golden star exploded into a vast, unfathomable expanse of golden light, which proliferated through the air in all directions, tearing through the nearby space with ridiculous ease.

All of the spatial fragments and spatial turbulence was then completely devoured by the golden light, and countless vortexes of different sizes that seemed to be capable of swallowing up all things had also appeared within the golden light.

What remained of the enormous mountain down below was quickly swallowed up by the golden light, and it was erased from existence without being able to offer up any resistance.

The golden light continued to spread rapidly, and the entire seventh level was trembling violently as massive spatial rifts appeared everywhere.

At this point, Han Li's trio had already flown to a considerable distance away, but they were being outsped by the expanding golden light, and it was quickly catching up to them.

Lekima let loose an urgent neigh as a pair of huge, white wings appeared on its back, and there were countless white symbols of winds and clouds flashing on their surface.

With its speed further enhanced by the pair of white wings, it had become faster than expanding golden light, but the entire seventh level was beginning to collapse, and spatial rifts were constantly appearing up ahead, forcing Lekima to duck and weave from side to side.

As a result, it was being slowed down significantly, preventing it from outrunning the expanding golden light.

Amid all the chaos, it was unclear where Qu Lin and Liu Zizai had gone.

"This isn't going to work, Fellow Daoist Lekima. I'm going to use a spatial teleportation technique to get us to the sixth level!" Han Li said as he made a hand seal, and arcs of golden lightning erupted out of his body to form a lightning array that encompassed all three of them.

As the lightning array took shape, more and more lightning array patterns appeared on its surface, but due to the fact that three people had to be teleported at once, including a Great Encompassment cultivator in the form of Lekima, some more preparations had to be made before teleportation could be initiated.

Lekima continued to flee from the expanding golden light while observing the surrounding lightning array, and its eyes instantly lit up upon sensing the exquisite integration of lightning and spatial powers within the array.

Finally, the lightning array fully took shape, and at this point, the expanding golden light was still some distance away.

An elated look appeared on Han Li's face as he prepared to activate the teleportation array, but right at this moment, the nearby space completely collapsed amid an earth-shattering commotion.

Han Li's trio instantly fell into a boundless expanse of spatial turbulence, which tore the lightning array apart with ease.

The lightning array was only a teleportation array, so it wasn't particularly resilient or defensively stalwart.

Han Li was involuntarily torn off Lekima's back before being swept up by the boundless spatial turbulence, while Lekima and Wyrm 3 were also swept away, vanishing out of sight in an instant.

Han Li felt as if the entire world were spinning around him, and countless bursts of spatial turbulence were sweeping toward him from all directions, filling his ears with deafening rumbling.

The spatial turbulence was incredibly powerful, and even with his immense powers, he was only just barely able to stabilize himself. Furthermore, due to the fact that the surrounding space had completely collapsed, there were also spatial fragments interspersed throughout the spatial turbulence.

Chapter 1130: Escape

Right at this moment, a burst of five-colored light appeared over Han Li's body, and a loud cry rang out as he transformed into a five-colored phoenix that was around a thousand feet in size.

It was Han Li's Heavenly Phoenix form, and it spread its wings as it began soaring through the air in an extremely cautious manner.

The spatial turbulence didn't pose much of a threat, but those spatial shards were extremely sharp and would slice even a Great Encompassment cultivator to ribbons, if given the chance.

In the wake of his battle against Qi Mozi, he had exhausted all of his time law powers, so he had to proceed with extreme caution in order to avoid those lethal spatial shards.

Right at this moment, a burst of thunderous rumbling rang out from behind him, and he turned to discover that the golden light was sweeping toward him once again.

An alarmed look appeared on his face as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts to transform into a devilish deity with three heads and six arms, and this time, the three heads were those of the Azure Luan Bird, the Lightning Bird, and the Heavenly Phoenix.

Gusts of azure wind, arcs of silver lightning, and streaks of five-colored light surged out of his body in unison as he flew back in retreat, traveling at an extraordinary speed that was far faster than even the top speed that Lekima had displayed earlier.

Flying at such an incredible speed, Han Li's ability to avoid the spatial shards in his path was severely compromised, and several gashes were soon sliced into his body.

Thankfully, his physical constitution was extremely formidable in this form, and he also had the protection of his True Extreme Film, so none of the gashes had cut very deep.

Before long, he was able to open up some distance between himself and the golden light, and to his immense relief, the golden light was beginning to slow down, as if it had finally exhausted all of its power.

An elated look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, but right at this moment, a burst of dull rumbling suddenly rang out from behind him, and the golden light abruptly exploded into countless waves of golden radiance that spread through the air far faster than before.

The waves of golden light instantly caught up to Han Li before he even had a chance to react, and he immediately summoned a whole host of defensive immortal treasures in a blind panic to protect himself.

However, it then quickly dawned on him that his concerns were unnecessary. The waves of golden light didn't have much destructive power within them, and they were merely propelling him rapidly through the air.

All of the surrounding spatial shards were also being propelled forward, so they didn't inflict much harm upon him.

The waves of golden light propelled Han Li through the air for some time before fading away, much to his relief and elation.

Right as he was about to continue onward, his gaze was suddenly drawn to a certain direction, and after a brief hesitation, he decided to fly in that direction.

A few seconds later, a struggling, blue figure appeared in his field of view up ahead, and it was none other than Lan Yan.

At this moment, she was trapped in a swirling vortex of spatial turbulence, and her entire body was riddled with wounds. Her left arm had been completely sliced off at the shoulder, and her hair was completely disheveled, while her complexion was deathly pale.

Most damning of all, the layer of protective spiritual light around her body had already become very dim, and it was only just barely able to ward off the surrounding spatial turbulence, indicating that her immortal spiritual power reserves were running dry.

Right at this moment, a huge spatial shard was hurled Lan Yan's way, and an alarmed look appeared on her face as she hurriedly dodged to the side.

However, in her current, terrible condition, her movements were far slower than normal, and she wasn't able to completely evade the spatial shard.

Right as she was about to be struck by the projectile, a streak of black light sped past in a flash, and Lan Yan instantly vanished into thin air, evading the spatial shard by the skin of her teeth.

A black figure emerged amid a burst of spatial fluctuations several thousand feet away, and it was none other than Han Li, gripping Lan Yan in one of his six giant, devilish hands.

"Are you... Fellow Daoist Han?" Lan Yan asked in a hesitant manner.

Han Li nodded in response with an indifferent direction, and a burst of green light surged out of one of his other hands before seeping into Lan Yan's body.

A layer of green light instantly appeared over her body, and her wounds began to rapidly heal, while the layer of protective spiritual light around her also brightened significantly.

A relieved look appeared on her face as Han Li released her, and she promptly took a pill, upon which her pale complexion quickly began to improve.

"Thank you for saving me, Fellow Daoist Han," she said with a look of mixed emotions in her eyes.

"No need to thank me. Now that you've recovered somewhat, I'll leave you to your own devices," Han Li replied, then promptly departed.

Even though they had initially been enemies, Han Li had a rather positive impression of the Lan siblings, and that was why he had decided to save Lan Yan in her time of need.

On top of that, he could feel that some darkness had taken root in his heart during the period of time in which he had been under the influence of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's inner demon law powers, so he decided that it was best to do some good deeds where possible in order to cleanse the darkness in his heart.

However, that didn't mean that he would go as far as to take Lan Yan with her. He had already saved her life here, and that was more than enough in his eyes.

Lan Yan looked on with a hesitant expression for a moment as Han Li flew away into the distance, then seemed to make up her mind as she set off after him.

After flying for a short while, Han Li arrived in an area filled with particularly powerful bursts of spatial turbulence that were interspersed with a huge number of spatial shards.

There was a massive spatial rift that was several dozen kilometers in length up ahead, through which the outside world could be seen, and that spatial rift was where all of the spatial shards were coming from.

An elated look appeared on Han Li's face as a layer of inky black light surfaced over his body, and he quickly took on an alternative devilish deity form, this one with the heads of the True Dragon, the Giant Mountain Ape, and the Kun Peng.

Additionally, this devilish deity form was also more physically imposing than the previous one, and all of his injuries were healed almost instantly.

At the same time, over nine hundred profound acupoints lit up over his body, and a burst of tremendous power erupted out his devilish body, scattering all of the nearby spatial turbulence to open up a large safe zone around him.

However, he didn't choose to immediately fly toward the white spatial rift as there were far too many spatial shards around it. Instead, he lashed out with his six fists in rapid succession, unleashing countless fist projections to strike at the dense clusters of spatial shards in front of the white spatial rift.

Bursts of thunderous rumbling rang out as waves upon waves of black fist projections struck the spatial shards before exploding into the balls of black light, and the spatial shards were quickly being scattered to open up a path of safe passage.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up slightly as he slowly flew forward while continuing to unleash a sustained barrage of fist projections to clear the way ahead, and it didn't take long before he arrived in front of the spatial rift.

Right at this moment, a layer of black light surfaced over each of his six fists, and he lashed out with his six fists in unison to release a black fist projection the size of a house.

The fist projection struck the white spatial rift before exploding into an enormous ball of black light that proliferated outward in all directions, clearing away all of the spatial shards near the white rift.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li let loose a thunderous roar as he lashed out with his six fists in unison once again to strike the spatial rift, and an earth-shattering boom rang out as the spatial rift shuddered violently.

A large hole that was several dozen in feet in size was blown into the spatial rift where it was struck by Han Li's fists, and an ecstatic look appeared on his face as he immediately reverted back to his human form before flying through the hole.

Outside the hole was a vast canyon that was filled with dense mist, while a blanket of dark clouds were hanging up above.

The Eon Pagoda was situated behind Han Li, but at this point, its seventh level had already been completely destroyed, reduced to a chaotic mass of spatial turbulence that was tearing the surrounding space to shreds.

All of the cultivators situated outside the Eon Pagoda were already nowhere to be seen, and only a few people who had been freed from the pagoda were still hanging around nearby, but none of them dared to approach the pagoda as they observed the structure in a fearful manner from afar.

Right as Han Li was assessing his surroundings, he suddenly turned around and raised an eyebrow while casting his gaze toward the large spatial hole that he had just emerged from.

A blue figure flew out from within before descending to the ground nearby, and it was none other than Lan Yan.

Several new wounds had appeared on her body, and the protective blue light around him had dimmed significantly once again.

She was gasping for air as she summoned a pair of blue talismans, which fused into her body as two balls of blue light, and her complexion instantly improved slightly.

"I didn't get a chance to thank you for setting aside our past differences and saving my life, Fellow Daoist Han. I'll be sure to repay you for your kindness," she promised with a serious expression.

"It's fine, don't worry about it," Han Li replied in an indifferent manner.

"You saved my life, Fellow Daoist Han. This is not something that I can simply forget," Lan Yan said in an insistent manner.

"Suit yourself then," Han Li shrugged as he took a pill while scouring his surroundings for Wyrm 3 and the others.

Lan Yan took a long glance at Han Li, then descended into the canyon and sat down to rest and recuperate.

Han Li paid no heed to her as he scanned the surrounding area with his spiritual sense, and his brows furrowed slightly in concern as he discovered that he couldn't detect any of their auras.

Chapter 1131: Sacrifice and Compromise

Surely they should all be fine, Han Li thought to himself.

Right at this moment, a huge spatial hole appeared near the Eon Pagoda, and Wyrm 3, Lekima, and Qu Lin flew out from within.

The three of them were all carrying substantial injuries, particularly Wyrm 3, half of whose body was soaked in blood, but thankfully, none of them were in any life-threatening danger.

"I'm glad to see you made it out safely, Fellow Daoist Han. I was worried about you after we became separated, but it looks my concerns were unnecessary," Wyrm 3 said with a mixture of elation and relief in her voice.

"I was very fortunate to have made it out alive. You should take some time to rest and recuperate so we can get out of here as soon as possible," Han Li replied.

Lekima and Qu Lin were also quite relieved to see that Han Li was unharmed, and they immediately sat down with their legs crossed to tend to their own injuries.

......

In the Azure Silk Col of the Golden Origin Mountain Range.

It was nighttime, and all of the households in the ancient village were busy making supper.

Plumes of smoke were rising up from the chimneys of the houses in the village, and the village chief was seated at the table in his own front yard along with a few old friends, sipping on some home-brewed wine while his wife prepared food in the kitchen.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out, and the entire Azure Silk Col shuddered violently. The table jumped up slightly into the air, and much of the wine in the bowls on the table came spilling out.

"When is this going to end?" the village chief grumbled as he hurriedly reached out to steady his bowl and the wine flagon.

"I just don't understand! What in our village could possibly be of such interest to those high and mighty immortals?" a dark-skinned elderly man sitting across from the village chief complained.

"I heard that some treasure had appeared in the Azure Silk Col, and many immortals came to visit the col before disappearing without any explanation. The remaining people have sealed up the col, so no one can access it now," a middle-aged man said.

"I don't care what they're doing as long as they don't ruin our spring," the village chief said in a concerned manner.

Another resounding boom rang out as they spoke, and unbeknownst to them, these were about to their final moments.

......

Inside White Head Valley, the ground was trembling violently amid bursts of thunderous rumbling.

Deep within the valley, many cultivators dressed in Almighty Sword Sect attire were gathered around the stone archway, and all of them were staring intently at the space beneath the archway, not daring to relax for even a single instant.

Right at this moment, a group of five or six figures emerged from the space there amid a flash of silver light, and looks of immense relief instantly appeared on the faces of the nearby Almighty Sword Sect cultivators at the sight of them.

It was none other than Lei Yuce's group that had emerged from the silver light.

Daoist Master Dao Yin's complexion was still looking rather pale, and there was an urgent look on his face, while Lei Yuce and the others were also looking far from pleased, so it was clear that something had gone wrong.

"Chen Chuan, have you completed the task I assigned to you?" Daoist Master Dao Yin asked.

A tall, male figure with a long, black beard stepped forward as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute and replied, "Yes, Master. I finished setting up everything close to a month ago, and I examined everything twice to ensure that there's nothing amiss."

"Give me the Dragon Tooth Key, then get out of here right now!" Daoist Master Dao Yin instructed in an urgent voice.

Chen Chuan's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he wanted to raise some questions, but didn't dare to do so. In the end, he could only flip a hand over to produce a crimson, crescent-shaped jade pendant, which he offered to Daoist Master Dao Yin with both hands.

"Let me do it in your stead, Master. Your injuries are too severe," Lei Yuce said with a grim expression.

"Do we really have to resort to that, Brother Lei?" Chen Chuan asked.

"We were unable to kill the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity or recover the Eon Divine Lamp, and the Eon Pagoda's defenses have already been breached. It won't be long before the people imprisoned in the pagoda come out of the secret area, and that'll spell disaster for the entire Golden Origin Immortal Region, so we have to act now," Lei Yuce replied in a grim voice.

"In order to activate the Dragon Tooth Destruction Array, someone has to stay in the array, and ten seconds following its activation, a string of explosions will take place. The majority of the power will be released into the secret area, but the residual power will still be enough to wipe out a good portion of the Golden Origin Mountain Range. Will you be able to make it out safely in your current condition?" Daoist Master Dao Yin asked in a concerned manner.

"Rest assured, Master, I'll be fine on my own," Lei Yuce assured with a smile.

"Senior Dao Yin, is there no other way? The foundations of our Heavenly Water Sect and your Almighty Sword Sect are both built upon the Golden Origin Mountain Range, so this will surely negatively impact both of our sects. On top of that, what about the countless innocent lives that will be lost? What have they done to deserve such a terrible fate?" Su Anqian asked with tightly furrowed brows.

Everyone fell silent upon hearing this, and it was clear that they echoed her concerns.

A hesitant look appeared on Daoist Master Dao Yin's face upon hearing, following which he heaved a forlorn sigh as he said, "I'm afraid we have no choice in the matter..."

"Allow me to explain," Lei Yuce interjected. "The Dragon Tooth Destruction Array was set up under direct orders from the Heavenly Court. They instructed us to blow up the entire secret area, but we didn't want to inflict such mass destruction upon the Golden Origin Mountain Range, so we ventured into the secret area with the objectives of killing the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity and recovering the Eon Divine Lamp.

“However, now that we've failed on both accounts, we have no choice but to execute the Heavenly Court's orders."

Su Anqian's expression changed slightly upon seeing this. She was aware of the weight of official orders from the Heavenly Court.

"If we had succeeded in our original plan, then we would've been able to seal away all of the beings imprisoned in the Eon Pagoda with the help of the Eon Divine Lamp, but now, we have no choice but to use the Dragon Tooth Destruction Array," Lei Yuce continued.

"If those beings previously imprisoned inside the pagoda manage to escape, then the Heavenly Court will be sure to intervene, and the consequences will be far more dire. Our Almighty Sword Sect will most likely be wiped out, and there's a good chance that your Heavenly Water Sect will also be held partly responsible. Hence, some sacrifices must be made," Daoist Master Dao Yin sighed.

As soon as his voice trailed off, another resounding boom rang out within the valley, and the ground began to tremble even more violently than before.

"The Eon Pagoda won't be able to hold itself together for much longer! We have to act now!" Daoist Master Dao Yin said in an urgent manner.

"Please leave this place at once, everyone. I'll activate the array on my own," Lei Yuce urged.

"Alright, I'll leave everything here to you, but make sure you return safely," Daoist Master Dao Yin replied after a brief hesitation, then handed the crescent-shaped jade pendant to Lei Yuce.

The pendant was riddled with complex patterns and slightly warm to the touch, and a solemn look appeared on Lei Yuce's face upon being entrusted with it.

"Be safe," Su Anqian said as she turned to depart, and Lei Yuce responded with a smile and a nod.

After that, everyone flew out of White Head Valley, leaving only Lei Yuce behind.

Su Anqian heaved a faint sigh as she flew over the serene little village in the Azure Silk Col.

Following everyone's departure, Lei Yuce rose up into the air, then joined his palms in front of his own chest with the Dragon Tooth Key clasped between them.

He then began to chant an incantation, and the entire White Head Valley began to tremble as a series of crescent-shaped stone pillars began rising up from the ground and the mountain faces surrounding the valley.

Before long, hundreds of black stone pillars that resembled sharp bones had emerged from the entire valley.

These stone pillars were etched with dense clusters of strange-looking runes that were dark red in color, giving off bursts of scorching heat and formidable spiritual power fluctuations.

Lei Yuce was feeling a little anxious as he held the jade pendant in his hand, but there was no time for him to hesitate as he tossed the Dragon Tooth Key forward.

The key ascended further into the heavens, hanging above the valley like a crimson moon.

Bursts of flashing light began emanating from the crimson moon, and the runes on the stone pillars below also began to flash in tandem.

All of a sudden, Lei Yuce brought his palms apart as he let loose a thunderous roar, and the crimson moon exploded into countless rays of crimson light that descended upon the stone pillars in the valley.

As these rays of light shone down onto the stone pillars, the runes engraved upon them brightened even further.

Meanwhile, Lei Yuce was already flying out of the valley as quickly as he could while commencing an internal countdown of ten seconds.

Immediately thereafter, another streak of light flew out of the valley before racing away in another direction.

It was none other than Xiong Shan standing atop the Primordial Ancient Sword, and his speed wasn't inferior to Lei Yuce's in the slightest.

As soon as the ten-second countdown concluded, countless pillars of light in the shape of wolves' fangs erupted out of the earth in the Azure Silk Col, and the entire surrounding area within hundreds of kilometers completely erupted, as if a gargantuan creature had risen up after a long slumber.

Immediately thereafter, a layer of red light swept through the entire area, instantly vaporizing everything that it came into contact with.

The entirety of Spare Food Village was torn apart by gusts of ferocious wind even before the red light arrived, and all signs that the village had ever existed were erased in the blink of an eye.

Close to half of the entire Golden Origin Mountain Range began to collapse amid bursts of violent rumbling, resulting in the destruction of countless settlements and the loss of countless lives.

Chapter 1132: Another Type of Compensation

Near the Eon Pagoda.

After taking a brief rest, Lekima and Qu Lin's complexions were looking much better than before.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I've followed through on my promise to you, so it's time for you to give me my bonded soul tablet, is it not?" Qu Lin asked as he rose to his feet.

"Of course," Han Li replied as he tossed over Qu Lin's bonded soul tablet.

A disgruntled look appeared on Lekima's face upon seeing this, and he protested, "Hey, don't forget about me! Isn't it about time that you returned my bonded soul tablet as well?"

"Have you forgotten that you promised me compensation in exchange for your bonded soul tablet, Fellow Daoist Lekima?" Han Li asked as he pulled out Lekima's bonded soul tablet, but didn't return it to him.

"I really did forget about that, but of course you didn't!" Lekima chuckled. "I suppose it's for the best. This way, I won't have to owe you any favors."

A streak of white light then came flying out of his mouth, containing a large, white flag that was riddled with designs of wind and clouds and giving off extremely formidable wind law power fluctuations.

Even without any injection of immortal spiritual power, the sheer presence of the flag alone was enough to stir up violent air currents within a radius of several hundred feet, forming an enormous, swirling vortex.

There was a reluctant look in Lekima's eyes as he gazed upon the flag, but he still offered it to Han Li as he said, "This Windbringer Flag is a prized fifth tier immortal treasure of mine that can be used to greatly enhance one's speed. I'm now gifting it to you as compensation for retrieving my bonded soul tablet."

"This is indeed a fine immortal treasure, but in order to fully tap into its power, one has to have mastery over the laws of wind, and that does not apply to me, so I'm afraid that I must refuse it. Instead, may I ask for something else as compensation?" Han Li asked as he swept a sleeve through the air, sending the flag drifting back to Lekima.

"What else would you like from me, Fellow Daoist Han?" Lekima asked with a surprised expression.

"I don't want any of your treasures. Instead, I want you to agree to a condition of mine," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"What is it?" Lekima asked.

"I can see that you are a true spirit, so I'm sure you've heard of the true spirits, the Baxia and the Zhuyan, right?" Han Li asked as he switched to voice transmission.

"I am indeed aware of them. They are extremely rare and powerful true spirits. What does that have to do with our discussion here?" Lekima asked with a perplexed expression.

"As compensation, I would like to secure you a batch of blood essence from each of those two true spirits," Han Li replied.

At the moment, he already possessed ten true spirit bloodlines, and he was only missing two bloodlines from his Twelve Awakening Transformation were those of the Baxia and the Zhuyan.

Given that the Heavenly Court was currently hot on his tail, he wasn't going to have much spare time to search for these two types of blood essence, so it was much better to assign the task to Lekima, who was a true spirit himself.

"You make it sound so simple, Fellow Daoist Han! How am I supposed to find these types of true spirits when they're virtually extinct in the True Immortal Realm? On top of that, both of these true spirits are extremely formidable, so even if I do manage to find them, extracting their blood essence is going to be an exceedingly difficult task," Lekima said in a solemn manner.

"I am aware that this is a very difficult task, so all that I ask is that you do your best. If you encounter any difficulties, you can contact me for help at any time," Han Li said as he flipped a hand over to produce a communication array plate, then handed it over to Lekima along with his bonded soul tablet.

Lekima accepted the two items from him, then raised an eyebrow as he asked, "You're giving me my bonded soul tablet just like that? Are you not worried that I'll take it without fulfilling my end of the agreement?"

"I think I'm a decent judge of character. I may not have known you for all that long, but I can tell that you're not one to go back on your promises," Han Li said with a faint smile.

Finding the last two types of true spirit bloodlines wasn't exactly a high-ranking priority anyway, so even if Lekima didn't follow through on his promise, it wouldn't have mattered much to Han Li. If worse came to worst, he would just have to offer a reward for the bloodlines in the Reincarnation Palace.

"I assure you that your trust in me is not misplaced, Fellow Daoist Han," Lekima promised with a serious expression, then stowed the communication array plate and his bonded soul tablet away, along with the Windbringer Flag.

Right at this moment, the nearby space tore open once again amid another resounding boom, and Liu Zizai and Fox 3 flew out from within.

The two of them were also carrying some injuries, but none of them were very severe, and they immediately flew over to Han Li's group upon catching sight of them.

Right at this moment, a burst of loud rumbling rang out from up ahead, and the sixth level of the Eon Pagoda collapsed violently, releasing a spatial storm that erupted in all directions to send Han Li and the others flying back through the air.

On top of that, the spatial storm was interspersed with spatial rifts that were capable of slicing through everything in their path.

Everyone hurriedly took evasive measures, but there was a huge number of these spatial rifts, and Fox 3 was unable to evade them all as his right arm was severed by a spatial rift before exploding into a misty cloud of blood.

Everyone hurriedly retreated even faster upon seeing this, and Lan Yan was also awoken from her meditation by the commotion.

She hurriedly rose to her feet, then flew out of the canyon to join everyone as they fled into the distance.

No one displayed any surprise at the sudden emergence of Lan Yan, and thankfully, the spatial storm didn't spread very far, so no one sustained any injuries aside from Fox 3.

However, before they even had a chance to catch their breaths, another resounding boom rang out as the fifth level of the Eon Pagoda exploded violently as well.

This was followed by the fourth level, then the third level, then the second, and finally, the first level.

Before long, the entire Eon Pagoda had vanished, replaced by an explosive spatial storm that was tearing everything around it to shreds.

The spatial storm contained devastating bursts of spatial power that were far more formidable than the spatial turbulence that Han Li had to contend with earlier, and he had a feeling that even if his time law powers and immortal spiritual power were both in peak condition, he would still be doomed if he were to be swept up in the spatial storm.

The entire space was trembling and swaying violently in the face of the terrifying spatial storm, and there was a look of lingering fear in Qu Lin's eyes as he remarked, "Thank heavens we managed to make it out in time. Otherwise, we would've surely died in there."

Even with his incredibly formidable physical constitution, he was certain that power of the spatial storm would be too much for him to bear.

"Each of the Eon Pagoda's levels is an independent space, so it can be said that the entire pagoda is a spatial treasure of an extremely high caliber. Hence, its self-detonation is naturally sure to unleash unfathomable power," Liu Zizai said.

"Fellow Daoist Shi is still inside. He was forced to withstand the detonation of Tai Sui's Oneness Tier spirit domain, and now, he's been swept up in such a terrifying spatial storm. I'm afraid the chances of him surviving all of this are extremely slim," Lekima sighed.

"The detonation of a time-attribute Oneness Tier spirit domain is already powerful enough to threaten any Great Encompassment cultivator, and Fellow Daoist Shi has only recently been freed, so he most likely hasn't recovered all of his power. I'm afraid you may be right..." Liu Zizai sighed.

Wyrm 3's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and a hint of concern surfaced in her eyes.

"Good riddance, I say! I'm glad that old madman is dead!" Qu Lin harrumphed coldly.

Right at this moment, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's voice suddenly rang out nearby.

"Oh? Is that right?"

Qu Lin shuddered as he frantically looked around in a panicked manner, and his complexion instantly turned deathly pale.

Right at this moment, a burst of black light flew out of everyone's bodies before converging to a single spot.

Everyone hurriedly examined their own internal conditions upon seeing this, but didn't discover anything amiss.

The same bursts of black light had also emerged from the bodies of all of the distant bystanders, and they fused together to form none other than the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

Qu Lin's complexion paled even further upon seeing this, and he was rooted to the spot in fear.

"I've heard that when inner demon law powers are cultivated to a certain degree, one would be able to resurrect themselves in the inner demons of others at any time even if their physical body and soul were to both be slain. I always thought that was nothing more than hyperbole, but you've proven me wrong, Fellow Daoist Shi," Liu Zizai mused with an incredulous expression.

"I may have been sealed in this place by Tai Sui for all these years, but during this time, I was able to make some advancements in my inner demon law powers," the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity said in a smug manner.

"We cannot even begin to fathom your boundless powers, Senior Shi," Wyrm 3 said, and everyone else also quickly chimed in with words of praise.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was extremely pleased by this, and he burst into hearty laughter.

However, as Han Li observed the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, he suddenly noticed that even though the latter had managed to successfully resurrect himself, his aura was far inferior to before, indicating that a price had to be paid for this form of resurrection.

Qu Lin was very relieved to see that the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's attention had been diverted away by everyone else, and he silently ducked behind everyone, hoping to stay out of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's line of sight.

All of a sudden, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity turned a cold gaze toward Qu Lin as he harrumphed coldly, "Where do you think you're going?"

Immediately thereafter, he abruptly vanished from the spot, and Qu Lin's expression changed drastically upon seeing this as he instantly adopted his Gold Devouring Beetle form.

He had only just completed his transformation when the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity appeared right in front of him before sending him flying with an almighty punch, and that was only the beginning of a ferocious barrage that had Qu Lin howling for mercy.

However, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's powers had diminished significantly following his resurrection, so the beating wasn't anywhere near as difficult to endure as last time for Qu Lin.

On top of that, Qu Lin fully deserved what was coming to him for his big mouth, so no one stepped in to plead for mercy for him.

Chapter 1133: Mass Destruction

The spatial storm raged for some time before finally beginning to dissipate, and in the span of just a few seconds, it had completely vanished.

Peace and quiet was restored, and it was as if nothing had happened, with only the gargantuan crater in the ground serving as a reminder of the havoc that had just been wrought.

All of a sudden, Han Li's eyes lit up as if he had spotted something, and he flew straight into the crater before re-emerging from its depths shortly thereafter with the Eon Divine Lamp held in his hand.

After enduring the spatial storm, the lamp was completely unharmed, but its flame had been snuffed out, and the time law power fluctuations emanating from it were also far weaker than before.

"Congratulations on recovering the Eon Divine Lamp, Fellow Daoist Han, although it seems to have sustained some damage," Wyrm 3 remarked.

"I'm already very content just to be able to recover the lamp," Han Li said as he stowed the lamp away.

At this point, the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity had finally had his fill of beating Qu Lin, and he flew back with a satisfied expression, while Qu Lin trailed along behind him with a glum look on his bruised and battered face.

"We may have made it out of the Eon Pagoda, but we're still in the Tai Sui Immortal Manor, and it doesn't look like this secret area is going to be around much longer. If the entire immortal manor collapses, the destructive power released will most likely be even more formidable than the collapse of the Eon Pagoda, so I think we should get out of here right away," Wyrm 3 proposed, and everyone nodded in agreement.

"We've already been trapped here for countless years, so of course I'm more than happy to leave this place, but how can we do that? Perhaps you can't sense it at your current cultivation base, but right now, the entire immortal manor is encompassed within a tremendous burst of spatial power, and it won't be easy to force our way out," Liu Zizai said.

A faint smile appeared on Wyrm 3's face, and she was just about to respond when the group of bystanders in the distance suddenly flew onto the scene.

It was a group of only twenty to thirty living beings, and it was unclear whether the rest had already perished or had gone somewhere else.

It was a very diverse group consisting of humans, demons, and devils, and most of them were completely emaciated, presenting a rather pitiable sight to behold.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he noticed that all of them possessed immense, High Zenith Stage auras, but for some reason, none of them possessed any law powers.

Even so, this was still a group of twenty to thirty High Zenith cultivators, and everyone looked on with wary expressions as they approached.

"You must've all been previously sealed in the Eon Pagoda, right? What business do you have with us?" Wyrm 3 asked in a composed manner.

"If you have a way to leave this place, then please take us with you. We've been trapped in here for countless years, and we've finally been freed, we don't want to die here," a red-haired, male human implored, and everyone else also began begging Wyrm 3 to take them with her.

"Rest assured, everyone, we were fated to meet here, so I won't leave you behind," Wyrm 3 declared.

"Thank you so much!" the red-haired man said, and his voice was brimming with gratitude.

Everyone else also hurriedly extended grateful salutes to Wyrm 3.

"Do you have a way to get out of here, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3?" Liu Zizai asked.

"I came here to carry out a mission for the Reincarnation Palace, so of course I have a way to get out of here. However, I'm going to need some time to prepare," Wyrm 3 replied as she flipped a hand over to produce a stack of silver array plates and array flags, all of which were giving off formidable spatial power fluctuations.

"That's a Great Spatial Transference Array! The Reincarnation Palace truly is an organization of remarkable wealth," Liu Zizai praised.

A faint smile appeared on Wyrm 3's face, and she was just about to begin setting up the array when the entire immortal manor began to tremble and sway violently.

The spatial rifts in the sky were rapidly expanding, and rays of blinding golden light were erupting out of them.

The earth had also begun to tremble violently, and a series of enormous trenches emerged before widening into vast canyons.

Everyone's expressions changed drastically upon seeing this, and they hurriedly flew up into the air.

"How could this be? The secret area has begun to collapse, but it should've been able to last at least a few more days. Could it be that someone's doing something to accelerate its collapse?" Wyrm 3 exclaimed.

"Now's not the time to be thinking about that! You focus on setting up the array, we'll keep you sheltered in the process!" Liu Zizai yelled in an urgent voice, and Wyrm 3 immediately sprang into action as the array plates and array flags in her hands flew into the nearby space to form a silver array.

Bursts of silver light erupted out of the array tools, forming a thick pillar of silver light that erupted into the heavens, while everyone hurriedly gathered around Wyrm 3.

Meanwhile, three figures were standing in the distance, seemingly completely unaffected by the surrounding spatial turbulence as they looked on at Han Li's group from afar.

......

Close to half a day later.

The commotion in the Golden Origin Mountain Range finally began to gradually subside, and at this moment, Daoist Master Dao Yin's group was standing in mid-air hundreds of thousands of kilometers away, looking on with pained expressions.

To the left, the Golden Origin Mountain Range remained as majestic and exuberant as ever, but to the right, the mountain range had been completely decimated, resulting in the annihilation of countless landmarks and the loss of countless lives.

"We've caused a horrific tragedy of unimaginable proportions!" Daoist Master Dao Yin sighed with a guilt-ridden expression.

"We're not to blame for this, Master. We did everything in our power to not have to do this, but ultimately, we have no choice but to obey the orders of the Heavenly Court," Chen Chuan consoled.

Right at this moment, everyone spotted a figure flying through the dense smoke in the distance, and a hint of elation surfaced in Chen Chuan's eyes as he exclaimed, "It's Senior Martial Brother Lei!"

Indeed, it was none other than Lei Yuce, and at the moment, there was a dazed and haunted look on his face.

Everyone knew the reason for this, and Su Anqian strode over to his side, standing beside him in a silent act of moral support and solidarity.

......

Right at this moment, a spatial rift suddenly appeared in the sky above what was once the Azure Silk Col, and over forty figures stumbled out from within in quick succession of one another.

The first person to emerge from the spatial rift was none other than the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, and a soon as he appeared, he immediately yelled, "Sheesh! What have they done with this place?"

Han Li and the others quickly emerged behind him, followed by all of the High Zenith cultivators that had been previously held captive in the Eon Pagoda.

"We're free... After all these years, we're finally free!"

All of the High Zenith cultivators had erupted into sobs from excitement and elation.

"Thank you for saving us!" someone yelled, and all of the High Zenith cultivators immediately fell to their knees to kowtow to Wyrm 3.

"There's no need to be so grateful to me, everyone," Wyrm 3 said with a dismissive wave. "What are your plans from here onward?"

"After being trapped in there for so long, we have no idea what the outside world is like anymore and whether our past sects even still exist. I can't speak for everyone, but at the very least, I don't have anywhere to go," the red-haired man replied with a wry smile, and dejected looks appeared on everyone else's faces as well.

"If you have somewhere you can go, then feel free to leave now. If not, you can come with me, and I'll arrange a place for you to go," Wyrm 3 said.

Seven eight of the freed cultivators immediately bade farewell to Wyrm 3 upon hearing this, while the rest, of which there were over twenty, chose to stay.

Han Li paid no heed to the conversation taking place between them and Wyrm 3.

At this moment, he was hanging high up in the sky, observing the landscape below with a grim expression. There was nothing but scorched earth as far as the eyes could see, and it was completely unlike the lush mountain range from before.

The former White Head Valley had already been completely destroyed, transformed into a giant crater that was hundreds of kilometers in diameter, and not a single living being could be seen in the entire decimated area.

The massive mountain range previously standing down below had also almost been completely razed to the ground, leaving behind only a small ridge that was no more than several hundred feet tall. Even now, the ridge was still giving off plumes of thick smoke and an acrid, charred odor.

Lan Yan was standing beside him with all of the color drained from her face, and her hand was clasped over her mouth in an astonished silence.

"Not only was the secret area detonated, this entire stretch of the mountain range was also destroyed. Who could've done this?" Wyrm 3 asked as she flew over to Han Li's side.

"Judging from the current circumstances, I'm guessing the Almighty Sword Sect must've had something to do with this, but what I don't understand is why they had to go so far," Han Li replied in a perplexed manner.

"That doesn't seem plausible to me. The Almighty Sword Sect is situated in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, and even though their sect isn't here, there are some powerful sects in the area that are allies of theirs, so surely they wouldn't have resorted to such extreme measures," Fox 3 countered.

"That's not necessarily true. While the Almighty Sword Sect and Heavenly Water Sect are powerful sects in their own right, one of the main reasons why they've been able to become premier forces in the Golden Origin Immortal Region is because of their loyalty to the Heavenly Court.

“Otherwise, a peak-High Zenith cultivator like Dongfang Bai wouldn't have been assigned to preside over a medium-sized immortal region like the Golden Origin Immortal Region," Wyrm 3 mused.

"That makes sense. If the Almighty Sword Sect really is behind this, then there's a very good chance that there was involvement from the Heavenly Court," Han Li speculated.

Chapter 1134: Jin Tong Captured

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity naturally wasn't interested in the conversation taking place between Han Li's trio.

At the moment, he was inspecting his surroundings in an excited manner, and all of a sudden, he crouched down in front of the crater as a contemplative look appeared on his face, then swooped down into the center of the crater.

There was a series of molten fireballs the size of houses situated on the ground there, and the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity seemed to be very interested in them, circling around them while reaching out as if to warm his hands.

Right at this moment, a burst of spatial fluctuations erupted out of the nearby space, and three more figures stumbled out of thin air.

Having just endured a grueling battle, Han Li and the others were still quite tense and alert, and they immediately prepared for battle at the sight of this unfamiliar trio.

The three of them seemed to be very apprehensive as well, and they were led by an elderly man with azure scales all over his body, giving off bursts of bone-chilling glacial qi.

He was accompanied by a tall man with dark green skin that was withered like tree bark, and he hurriedly darted away to the side, seemingly very fearful of this glacial qi. At the same time, countless green roots emerged from his body in the blink of an eye before plunging into the charred soil below.

The final figure to round out the trio was a gray-robed elderly man who was far closer to a normal human in appearance compared with his two companions. He stood on the spot with one hand clasped behind his back, and waves of golden ripples were surging out of his robes.

Right as a battle was about to commence, Liu Zizai suddenly called out, "Huai Yangzi! Is that you, Fellow Daoist Huai Yangzi?"

Everyone faltered slightly upon hearing this, and the gray-robed elderly man's brows furrowed slightly as he directed his gaze to Liu Zizai, upon which a surprised look appeared on his face as exclaimed, "Fellow Daoist Liu!"

"That's right, it's me! I didn't think we would be reunited here after all this time," Liu Zizai said with a wry smile.

"Indeed, fate is truly a cruel mistress," Huai Yangzi sighed with a shake of his head.

"Don't be alarmed, everyone. Fellow Daoist Huai Yangzi is an acquaintance of mine, not an enemy," Liu Zizai reassured, and Huai Yangzi also gestured for his two companions to stand down.

With that, the tension in the air was lifted, and everyone gathered together in a loose circle.

"Back when you went missing in the Ink Sea Immortal Region, I went there to search for you, but even after several centuries of searching, the only lead that I could dig up was that you had gone to explore a deepsea secret region in the Forgotten Sea. After that, no one heard from you again. What happened all those years ago?" Liu Zizai asked.

"Back then, I was invited by an old friend from the Ink Sea Immortal Palace to explore a secret area deep within the Crimson Wyrm Trench. However, that scoundrel betrayed me, and I was ambushed and captured by Immortal Palace cultivators under a whole host of arbitrary crimes.

“After that, I was thrown into the Immortal Prison, then ended up sealed in the Eon Pagoda, and only after all these years have I finally been freed," Huai Yangzi explained.

"You were also trapped in the Eon Pagoda? How did we not see each other in there after all this time?" Liu Zizai exclaimed.

"You were trapped in the pagoda as well?" Huai Yangzi asked with a skeptical expression.

"Do you not believe me?" Liu Zizai asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"No, it's just that a cultivator of your caliber shouldn't have been able to preserve your cultivation base after being captured by the Heavenly Court. Did they not rob you of your law powers?" Huai Yangzi asked with a perplexed expression, and the same expression was also mirrored on the faces of his two companions.

"Are you saying the Heavenly Court robbed you of your law powers? No wonder your cultivation base hasn't regressed, but it seems a little unstable," Liu Zizai mused.

"Not only were my law powers taken from me, many cultivators in the Immortal Prison suffered the same fate as well. We were stripped of all of our law threads before being thrown into the Eon Pagoda," Huai Yangzi said in a resentful manner.

"Come to think of it, even though you didn't join the Heavenly Court, you've always remained on good terms with them as an itinerant immortal, so why did they decide to target you? Could it be that your law threads were special in some way?" Liu Zizai asked.

"Law powers are derived from each person's unique understanding of the Great Dao of heaven and earth, so strictly speaking, everyone's law threads are special in some way. However, I don't think the Heavenly Court cared about that at all. They captured many cultivators of all tribes and races, including even plant spirits, and no patterns can be gleaned in the law powers mastered by the captured cultivators, so the whole thing is very suspicious," Huai Yangzi replied.

"What did the Heavenly Court do with those extracted law threads, Senior Huai Yangzi?" Wyrm 3 asked, and Han Li was also very curious to hear the answer to this question.

"I don't know. We were never able to find out why they wanted so many law threads. I'm more curious about why your law threads weren't extracted, Fellow Daoist Liu," Huai Yangzi replied.

"I'm not sure. All I recall is that I wasn't in the Immortal Prison for very long before I was coaxed by Tai Sui into the Eon Pagoda. By the way, where were you imprisoned in the Eon Pagoda?" Liu Zizai asked.

"I was imprisoned in the seventh level of the Eon Pagoda along with many other cultivators, but we were all sealed away underground in a state of semi-hibernation. I can't recall exactly when it was, but some number of years ago, the restrictive forces in the pagoda suddenly began to loosen, and we attempted to slowly recover our law powers, but we were unable to move freely," Huai Yangzi replied.

"I see. I was imprisoned on the fifth level, so it's no wonder that we never saw each other in the pagoda. If we hadn't been freed, we would've never known that we were so close to each other," Liu Zizai mused.

Han Li's expression remained largely unchanged as he listened to the ongoing conversation, but internally, his mind was racing.

The Heavenly Court was the most authoritative power in the entire True Immortal Realm, and its primary objective was to maintain peace and order across the realm, so it shouldn't have been doing anything too out of line. However, if Huai Yangzi were telling the truth, then the Heavenly Court had to have been planning something massive and potentially sinister.

Unfortunately, there were too few leads for him to make any good guesses on what they were attempting to do.

After some contemplation, Han Li proposed, "Pardon my interjection, but I think we should focus on leaving this place as soon as possible. Everything else can be discussed after that."

"I agree. Given what's just happened here, I'm sure the Heavenly Court will be sending people to clean up the mess very soon, so we should leave this place right away," Wyrm 3 seconded with a nod.

"Do you have any future plans, Fellow Daoist?" Liu Zizai asked as he turned to Huai Yangzi.

"At this point, there's nothing that I'm too afraid to say anymore. Before my incarceration, the Reincarnation Palace tried to recruit me, but I refused for fear of pitting myself against the Heavenly Court. Right now, I have nowhere to go, and I wonder if the Reincarnation Palace is still willing to take me, or if the Reincarnation Palace still even exists, for that matter," Huai Yangzi sighed.

"If you want to join the Reincarnation Palace, I can perhaps have that arranged, Senior," Wyrm 3 said with a smile.

All of the High Zenith cultivators who were originally planning to follow Wyrm 3 were slightly alarmed to hear this, with some of them displaying some concern at her implied affiliation with the Reincarnation Palace.

"Does that mean you're a member of the Reincarnation Palace?" Huai Yangzi asked in a surprised manner.

Wyrm 3 merely smiled and offered no response, but the implication was clear.

"If it wasn't for them, we would still be imprisoned in the Eon Pagoda right now," Liu Zizai said.

Huai Yangzi was rather taken aback to hear this, and he said, "In that case, it looks like I owe my freedom to you. I'm willing to go to the Reincarnation Palace with you."

He then turned to his two companions as he asked, "What are your plans, fellow daoists?"

"We're in a similar situation to you. Even though we've managed to escape from the Eon Pagoda, I'm sure the Heavenly Court won't be willing to let us off the hook, so we may as well join the Reincarnation Palace too," the azure-skinned elderly man replied with a smile, while the tree-like man merely nodded in agreement, seemingly a man of few words.

"What are your plans, Brother Han? Would you like to return to the Reincarnation Palace with me?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"At this point, I'm only accumulating more and more bad blood with the Heavenly Court, so the sooner I go to the Reincarnation Palace, the sooner I'll have some allies and backers for my protection. Having said that, I hope that I won't be given another hollow Reincarnation Disciple status like last time," Han Li replied.

"Perhaps it's destiny, but your fate seems to be intertwined with that of our Reincarnation Palace, Brother Han. On top of that, you made a significant contribution to the completion of my mission, so I can assure you that you'll become a core member once you come back to the Reincarnation Palace with me this time. Our palace master also has a very high opinion of you, and perhaps he'll want to see you," Wyrm 3 said with a smile.

"That's all well and good, but I'm still waiting on an explanation about the situation surrounding Jin Tong that you brought up earlier," Han Li said as he switched to voice transmission.

"I can't elaborate too much on the matter for now, all I can tell you is that Jin Tong is currently being held captive in the Nine Origins Temple," Wyrm 3 replied after a brief hesitation.

"Why has Jin Tong been captured by the Nine Origins Temple? Surely you can answer me that question at least," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

Chapter 1135: Distinctions Between Immortal Regions

"From what I heard, Jin Tong used herself as bait to lure out a Gold Devouring Immortal kept by the Nine Origins Temple, and she was able to successfully devour that Gold Devouring Immortal, but in the process, she was discovered by the Nine Origins Temple and captured under the combined efforts of several Great Encompassment cultivators," Wyrm 3 explained.

A grim look appeared on Han LI's face upon hearing this.

"There's no need to be overly concerned, Brother Han. Gold Devouring Immortals are extremely precious, so not only will the Nine Origins Temple not do anything to harm her, they'll most likely do everything in their power to nurture her. The only downside is that her freedom will be compromised for now," Wyrm 3 consoled.

There was a clear implication that Jin Tong would only be granted freedom again once she was tamed by the Nine Origins Temple.

He wasn't overly concerned about that as Jin Tong certainly wasn't going to be easy to tame. What he was more concerned about was that given her personality, she was most likely going to put herself through a great deal of suffering.

As a Gold Devouring Immortal, she had a near indestructible body, but there were still things that could hurt her, and given the vast wealth possessed by an almighty power like the Nine Origins Temple, there was no telling what resources they could have up their sleeve to target her.

Jin Tong had been with him for the majority of his cultivation journey, so he couldn't just leave her in harm's way.

"It just so happens that there's going to be an upcoming mission from our Reincarnation Palace concerning the Nine Origins Temple. If you're willing to take on the mission, then you can take the opportunity to rescue Jin Tong," Wyrm 3 continued.

"What's the mission?" Han Li asked.

"You know the rules, Brother Han, there are some things that I can't tell you for now. On top of that, there's still a very long time until the mission is set to commence, so you can take this time to make some further advancements in your cultivation base," Wyrm 3 replied.

"Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, do you have a map of the Golden Origin Immortal Region?" Han Li asked through voice transmission after some contemplation.

"Why do you want a map? Are you planning to travel to the Nine Origins Temple?" Wyrm 3 asked as her brows furrowed slightly.

"Seeing as the Nine Origins Temple is in the Golden Origin Immortal Region, I may as well go and scout for some information. Rest assured, I won't do anything reckless," Han Li replied.

"I'm afraid there's a misunderstanding here, Brother Han. This Golden Origin Immortal Region isn't that Golden Origin Immortal Region," Wyrm 3 said with a smile.

"What do you mean by that?" Han Li asked.

"There are countless immortal regions in the Immortal Realm, but there aren't actually all that many with shared names. Most of them are small and secluded immortal regions that are completely unaware of one another's existence. However, the case of the two Golden Origin Immortal Regions is rather special in that the name is shared by a small immortal region and a much larger one," Wyrm 3 explained.

"There are much larger immortal regions out there?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"You've only been in small immortal regions like the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so it's no surprise that you're unaware of this. Then again, this is something that the vast majority of cultivators in the True Immortal Realm are also oblivious to.

“After all, for cultivators below the Golden Immortal Stage, they could easily spend their entire lives in just a single immortal region. In total, there are thirty-six large immortal regions, five hundred medium regions, and three thousand small regions. The number of three thousand is really just one that was arbitrarily assigned. No one knows exactly how many there are, and no one can be bothered to find out," Wyrm 3 explained.

"There are thirty-six large immortal regions? I've heard of the Middle Earth Immortal Region, I'm assuming that must be one of them, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The Middle Earth Immortal Region ranks at the very top of the thirty-six large regions, and the Golden Origin Immortal Region that the Nine Origins Temple is situated in is also vastly renowned. The Golden Origin Immortal Region that we're in right now has been able to keep its name despite the overlap because it was once part of the larger Golden Origin Immortal Region and only broke off from it during a bout of major unrest," Wyrm 3 explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

Right at this moment, Wyrm 3's gaze suddenly flicked to Lan Yan, and a look of killing intent surfaced in her eyes as she abruptly lashed out like lightning, thrusting a palm toward Lan Yan's chest.

Having just survived that massive ordeal, Lan Yan was feeling a little drained and complacent, and she was caught completely off guard by this turn of events. Before she had a chance to react, she was struck in the chest, and she felt a burst of peculiar power seep into her body from the palm of Wyrm 3's hand, sending her flying back through the air as she threw up a mouthful of blood.

Everyone was initially rather startled by this, but they then quickly realized why Wyrm 3 had suddenly lashed out.

Lan Yan struggled up into a seated position with blood still flowing from the corner of her lips and a look of alarm and fear on her face.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he stepped in between Wyrm 3 and Lan Yan before the former could attack the latter any further.

"We can't let her live, Brother Han, she's a disciple of the Nine Origins Temple," Wyrm 3 said with tightly furrowed brows.

"Even if she is a disciple of the Nine Origins Temple, she doesn't deserve to die," Han Li countered.

"Given how long she's been with us, there's no telling what important information she could report back to her sect. She cannot be allowed to return to the Nine Origins Temple alive!" Wyrm 3 insisted.

"She and her brother made a peace agreement with me earlier, and she didn’t go back on the agreement even when I was being attacked by She Chan, so it's clear that she's a woman of integrity. I think we should spare her on the condition that she doesn't reveal anything about us to her sect. As an additional layer of security, I can plant a restriction on her soul," Han Li said.

"Why go to all that trouble? It would be far easier just to kill her!" Wyrm 3 objected in a cold voice.

"Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3, if you truly regard me as an ally, then please do me this favor," Han Li implored with a serious expression.

A look of realization appeared on Wyrm 3's eyes upon hearing this, and she finally acquiesced, nodding in agreement to Han Li's request.

Han Li knew that she had definitely misunderstood, but he couldn't be bothered to explain himself to her, so he merely cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

He then turned to Lan Yan as he said, "Fellow Daoist Lan, I'm going to be planting a restriction in your consciousness to ensure that you don't reveal any information about us. I'm afraid you have no choice but to accept this arrangement."

Lan Yan remained silent as she pursed her lips and nodded in response, putting on a pitiable display.

With that, Han Li plucked a strand of translucent light out of his own glabella, then slowly extended it toward Lan Yan's glabella.

The strand of translucent light slithered out of his glabella like a spirit snake, then vanished into Lan Yan's glabella in a flash.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 had already descended into the massive crater in the ground.

The Dark Heavens Devilish Deity was thoroughly enjoying himself, playing with the balls of molten fire, and he was far from happy to have been interrupted by Wyrm 3, immediately raising a hand in preparation to lash out at her.

"Please don't attack me, Senior Shi! I have something to discuss with you," Wyrm 3 hurriedly yelled in an alarmed manner.

"What is it?" Shi Kongmo snapped in an impatient manner.

"You've been searching for your wife and son this entire time, haven't you? Perhaps I can help you," Wyrm 3 said.

An urgent look immediately appeared on Shi Kongmo's face upon hearing this, and he hurriedly asked in a frantic voice, "Do you know where they are right now?"

"No, but I can help you find them," Wyrm 3 replied.

All hints of derangement faded from Shi Kongmo's eyes as a look of cold killing intent appeared on Shi Kongmo's face, instantly making Wyrm 3 feel as if she had been plunged into a glacial pit.

"That's exactly what Tai Sui said to coax me into his Eon Pagoda. If you dare to trick me like he did, I'll make you wish you had never been born!" Shi Kongmo threatened with a chilling gaze.

"I wouldn't dare, Senior," Wyrm 3 hurriedly replied with cold sweat beading up on her forehead.

"Good," Shi Kongmo said as a smile returned to his face, and it didn't take long before he reverted back to his deranged demeanor.

"Would you like to return to the Reincarnation Palace with me, Senior?" Wyrm 3 asked in a hopeful manner.

"Yes, yes, take me to my wife and son," Shi Kongmo replied with a smile.

The two of them returned to the surface together, where they were approached by Liu Zizai, who said to Wyrm 3, "I would love to also return to the Reincarnation Palace, but before that, I'm afraid there are some matters that I must attend to."

"Are you returning to the primordial land with Fox 3?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"That's right," Liu Zizai replied with a nod.

"That's not a problem then. The palace master has already told me about this," Wyrm 3 said.

A hint of surprise flashed through Liu Zizai's eyes upon hearing this, but he didn't ask any questions.

"How about you, Fellow Daoist Han? Will you return to the Reincarnation Palace with me?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"I'll pass for now as I still have some other matters to attend to. However, as I stated earlier, I'm willing to join the Reincarnation Palace and take part in the mission that you mentioned earlier," Han Li replied with a smile.

Wyrm 3's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but she quickly accepted this outcome as she said, "In that case, I wish you the best of luck, Fellow Daoist Han. I'm sure we'll meet again soon."

After everyone had a chance to say their goodbyes, Wyrm 3 departed with the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, Huai Yangzi, and the others.

Liu Zizai seemed to be discussing something with Fox 3 and Lekima, while Han Li turned to Qu LIn as he asked, "What are your plans, Fellow Daoist Qu? Are you planning to accompany me?"

"That was my original plan, but I may have to change my mind now," Qu Lin replied with a smile.

"Oh? Why is that?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Given what's happened here and your previous exploits in the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, you must be an extremely renowned figure in the Heavenly Court by now, so it would be unwise for me to accompany you on your travels," Qu Lin explained.

"I suppose that makes sense," Han Li replied with a nod.

In reality, Han Li also had his reservations about Qu Lin, so parting ways here suited him just fine.

"In that case, let's part ways here, Fellow Daoist Qu. May we meet again," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

Qu Lin returned the salute, then flew away as a streak of golden light.

Following his departure, Han Li turned to Lan Yan as he asked through voice transmission, "Fellow Daoist Lan, you're going to return to the Nine Origins Temple, right?"

Lan Yan nodded in response.

"In that case, I'll have to trouble you to serve as my guide. I'm also planning to travel to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region," Han Li said.

Chapter 1136: Reincarnation Palace Master

"Why are you traveling to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, Fellow Daoist Han? Are you not aware that you're being hunted by the Heavenly Court right now?" Lan Yan asked with a puzzled expression.

"That's precisely why I'm going. There's no way that the Heavenly Court could possibly anticipate this. Isn't it always said that the most dangerous is often the safest place to be?" Han Li replied with a smile.

Lan Yan knew that Han Li was only saying this to placate her in order to hide his true objective, but she knew not to pry into his private matters.

Right at this moment, Lekima suddenly trotted over to Han Li, then said, "I've been quite impressed with you, kid. Would you like to consider returning to the primordial land with me?"

"I'm honored that you think so highly of me, but I still have some matters to attend to, so I'll have to turn down your kind offer," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Alright, you can have this then. If you need anything from me, feel free to come find me in the primordial land," Lekima said as he released a streak of white light with a raise of his hoof.

Han Li caught the streak of white light to discover that it was a palm-sized scale with layers of rippling patterns over its surface, giving off a fierce, primordial aura.

"You have my thanks," Han Li said as he stowed the scale away, following which he bade farewell to Fox 3 and the others before departing with Lan Yan.

After Han Li and Lan Yan had completely vanished into the distant sky, Lekima suddenly rose up onto his hind legs, following which countless white air currents were conjured up around his entire body.

Fox 3 looked on with an intrigued and puzzled expression as Lekima gradually took on a human form, and the white air currents faded away to reveal a handsome and refined middle-aged man dressed in a white robe.

Liu Zizai extended a respectful bow as he cupped his fist in a salute and said, "Please pardon me for my earlier transgressions, Young Master."

Lekima hurriedly strode over to Liu Zizai to help him into an upright position as he replied, "What transgressions do you speak of, Uncle Liu? I was the one who instructed you to do so all of this."

"What's going on?" Fox 3 asked with a dazed expression.

"Let's go, I'll explain to you on the way," Lekima said with a smile, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a white, three-story louchuan that displayed exceptional craftsmanship and extravagant opulence.

The three of them flew onto the louchuan, and gusts of white wind rose up beneath it, carrying it up into the air before propeling it into the distant sky, where it quickly vanished out of sight.

......

Over three years flew by in a flash.

On this day, a dark red spirit boat was flying through the air over a vast river running along the northern border of the Golden Origin Mountain Range.

While it was technically a spirit boat, it was a very large one that had two levels, and at this moment, Wyrm 3 was standing behind the railing on the second level of the boat in an azure dress, looking out into the distance.

After peering into the distance for some time, Wyrm 3 said, "Senior Huai Yangzi, now that we've left the Golden Origin Mountain Range, I'll be going into seclusion for some time, so I'm going to need you to pilot the spirit boat from now."

"You can count on me, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," Huai Yangzi immediately replied, and Wyrm 3 cupped her fist in a grateful salute before making her way into the pavilion on the second level.

From there, she made a hand seal before pointing a finger upward, and a streak of dark red light immediately shot out of her fingertip before fusing into a dark red badge that was hovering above her head.

The badge instantly began to revolve on the spot, releasing a light barrier that gradually encompassed the entire pavilion, isolating all of the auras within.

Wyrm 3 sat down with her legs crossed, then made a peculiar hand seal as she began to chant an incantation.

Immediately thereafter, a series of complex runes lit up over her body before roaming through the surrounding air like red silk ribbons, and at the same time, a layer of hazy light emerged around her.

It was as if layers upon layers of illusory shadows had appeared around her body, giving her an indistinct appearance.

Right at this moment, a burst of red light flashed through her eyes, which then instantly became completely empty and glazed over, as if the soul had been sucked out of her body, leaving her as nothing more than an empty husk.

Her eyelids then slid shut as her vision faded into black.

As she reopened her eyes, she found herself in a murky, gray space that was completely empty aside from a series of long, winding rivers.

She was hovering in mid-air as if she possessed an illusory body, and she was able to propel herself forward by stroking her hands through the air like oars, casually traveling over a dark red river in the upstream direction.

There were a total of five rivers neighboring this one, all of which were different in color and appearance. Some contained turbulent, rushing water, while others were much more slow and placid.

One of them, a silver river, was flowing in a slow and stable manner, and there were countless water-droplet-shaped balls of light flowing through it, all of which seemed to have images flashing inside.

Wyrm 3 didn't dare to allow her gaze to linger on any of those balls of light. Otherwise, she would be sucked into that river against her will.

After flying upstream for an indeterminate period of time, all of the rivers finally began to gradually taper down to a single point of origin in the form of a river that acted as the source for all of the others.

It was unclear where this river originated from, and its water was a murky yellow color, while a dark red stone arch bridge had been constructed over it.

The surface of the bridge was smooth and seamless, giving it the appearance of a crystalline platform, and as the river flowed past under the bridge, it automatically split up into six different streams that extended in different directions.

All of a sudden, Wyrm 3's brows furrowed slightly as she took a glance under the bridge.

She had unwittingly discovered a woman in black seated on the riverbank under the bridge with her fair and delicate feet submerged in the dark red river that had only just split off from the original, yellow river.

The woman had her back facing Wyrm 3, so she wasn't able to see her face.

Wyrm 3 didn't dare to observe the woman for too long as there was another figure nearby, this one hovering in mid-air above the stone arch bridge.

It was a slightly hunched over figure with a large, veiled hat on their head and a heavy bamboo fiber cloak draped over their body. The figure had their back facing the six branching rivers, looking out at the murky, yellow river.

The figure was also holding an azure bamboo pole that was riddled with white spots, and attached to the head of the pole was a translucent, dark red line that trailed down into the water like a fishing line.

Wyrm 3 flew over to the bridge, but was unable to descend onto it and continued to hover in mid-air.

"Gan Jiuzhen pays her respects to the palace master," Wyrm 3 greeted as she extended a respectful salute.

The cloaked figure was none other than the palace master of the Reincarnation Palace.

"Has everything already been taken care of? That went a lot quicker than I expected. Tell me what happened," the palace master said as he continued to look out over the yellow river.

With that, Wyrm 3 delivered a recount of her journey through the Eon Pagoda.

After hearing her story, the palace was silent for a moment, then said, "Make sure to keep a close eye on Shi Kongmo."

"Are you of the opinion that he's feigning his insanity, Palace Master?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"That doesn't matter as long as he doesn't turn on us. Make sure to follow through on your promise of helping him find his wife and son, and for that purpose, you can draw upon all of the resources of our Reincarnation Palace," the palace master replied, and Wyrm 3 gave an affirmative response.

"Seeing as you've recovered that thing, we can set many of our plans into motion now. This should be enough to keep the Heavenly Court busy for quite some time," the palace master continued.

"I'll get started on that once I'm back," Wyrm 3 said.

After that, both of them were silent for a long while before the palace master suddenly asked, "What do you think of Han Li? I don't want to hear an objective assessment, I want to hear what you think about him."

"I've worked with him on several occasions now, and I think he possesses exceptional powers, potential, and mental qualities. He will surely be of great use to our Reincarnation Palace, and I hope that he can be included in the upcoming mission," Wyrm 3 replied.

"I'll leave that to you," the palace master said, and Wyrm 3 gave an affirmative response.

"You must've expended quite a few law threads to come and see me, so you can have these as compensation," the palace master said as he flicked his fishing rod upward, and the dark red line instantly flew up into the air with a ball of dark red light attached to its end.

The palace master grabbed onto the ball of light, then massaged it into a dark red bead before flicking it toward Wyrm 3, sending it flying straight into her glabella.

Wyrm 3 was instantly sent flying back like a falling leaf in a fierce gust of wind, and her vision also turned dark.

In the second-floor pavilion of the spirit boat, Wyrm 3's eyes abruptly sprang open, and her entire body was drenched in sweat as she began gasping for air.

After taking a moment to compose herself, she raised a hand to massage her own glabella, which was feeling a little swollen and sore.

However, there was also a cool and refreshing sensation emanating from there alongside traces of reincarnation law power fluctuations, much to her elation.

At the same time, she couldn't help but think back to the woman seated on the riverbank.

Who was that, and how is she related to the palace master?

Chapter 1137: Glimpse of the Heavenly Court

Meanwhile, a dark green flying boat was racing through the air elsewhere in the Golden Origin Immortal Region.

The flying boat resembled a dark green dragon that was soaring through the heavens, and it was incredibly fast, covering tens of thousands of kilometers in the blink of an eye.

Han Li and Lan Yan were seated in the flying boat, but both of them had adopted disguises.

This Ink Dragon Flying Boat was something that Han Li had found from She Chan's storage treasure. She Chan had detonated her own Toad Moon Jewel back in the Eon Pagoda, but Han Li was able to claim her storage treasure just in the nick of time.

The flying boat was a sixth tier wood and wind dual-attribute immortal treasure, and not only was it incredibly fast, it was also far better at concealing itself than all of Han Li's previous flying boats.

Lan Yan was piloting the flying boat, and Han Li had restrictions planted in her body that allowed him to detect her every move, so he wasn't concerned about any foul play on her part.

At this moment, he was seated with his legs crossed at the rear end of the boat, and time law powers were surging over his body alongside a layer of rippling, golden light.

After three years of recuperation, he had recovered close to half of his time law powers, and that instilled him with a great deal of reassurance.

At this moment, he was holding several jade slips, the contents of which he was inspecting with his spiritual sense, and some time later, he withdrew his spiritual sense from them as a grim look appeared on his face.

These jade slips contained information pertaining to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region and the Nine Origins Temple, and he had obtained them through the Reincarnation Palace.

He had managed to gather a lot of information about the Golden Origin Immortal Region, but the Nine Origins Temple was extremely secretive, so despite his best efforts, he was only able to find some trivial information about the organization.

"Can I ask you some questions, Fellow Daoist Lan Yan?" Han Li called out.

Lan Yan immediately strode over to him in an obedient manner as she asked, "What would you like to know, Fellow Daoist Han?"

Along this entire journey, Lan Yan had been extremely obedient, following Han Li's instructions to a tee.

"I want to ask you some questions about the Nine Origins Temple," Han Li declared in a direct and straightforward manner.

Lan Yan's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, following which she said, "Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Han, I'll tell you everything that I know."

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this.

"According to my knowledge, members of the Nine Origins Temple who reveal its secrets to outsiders are severely punished if caught. Is that not something you're afraid of?"

"You're far more powerful than I am, so even if I refuse to tell you anything, I'm sure you can find out what you want from me by force anyway. Hence, I may as well cooperate. All that I ask is that you don't tell anyone where you received this information from," Lan Yan replied.

"You and your senior martial brother really do think alike. Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Lan, I won't expose you as long as you answer my questions to the best of your abilities," Han Li promised.

A hint of sorrow flashed through Lan Yan's eyes at the mention of Lan Yuanzi, but she then immediately concealed it as she gave Han Li a grateful nod.

"How many Dao Ancestors are there in your Nine Origins Temple?" Han Li asked.

"Dao Ancestors are extremely rare. Our Nine Origins Temple may be a very powerful sect, but it only has a single Dao Ancestor, and that's our founder," Lan Yan replied.

"What about Great Encompassment cultivators?" Han Li asked.

"To tell you the truth, despite my cultivation base, I'm only a fringe cultivator responsible solely for carrying out secret missions for the temple, so I'm pretty low down in the pecking order, and I don't know much about the temple's inner workings.

“According to my knowledge, there are fifteen Great Encompassment cultivators in the Nine Origins Temple, consisting of the abbot, the two assistant abbots, the four holy envoys, and the eight saints. However, there are many secrets in the Nine Origins Temple, so there are most likely other Great Encompassment cultivators that I don't know of," Lan Yan replied.

Han Li couldn't help but be alarmed upon hearing this.

With so many Great Encompassment cultivators in the Nine Origins Temple, it was no wonder that Wyrm 3 had encouraged him to make some advancements in his cultivation base. Given his current powers, venturing into the Nine Origins Temple to try and rescue Jin Tong would be a complete suicide mission.

"You were sent after me by Immortal Lord Miao Fa, right? What is her cultivation base and status in the temple?" Han Li asked.

"Immortal Lord Miao Fa is one of our temple's four holy envoys, and she's a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator," Lan Yan replied.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon hearing this.

After reaching the Great Encompassment Stage, each successive cultivation rank attained amounted to an unfathomable advancement in power. With all of the trump cards up his sleeve, Han Li was confident in his ability to oppose an early-Great Encompassment cultivator, but he was most definitely no match for a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator.

After that, he asked Lan Yan some more questions, all of which she answered in great detail, giving him a rough understanding of the Nine Origins Temple, and the more he learned, the more deflated he felt.

The Nine Origins Temple was far more powerful than he had imagined. It was a true monolith that completely dwarfed all of the Immortal Palaces that he had come into contact with in the past, and rescuing Jin Tong on his own was going to be an impossible task.

However, he was determined to save her no matter what.

After asking all of the questions that he could think of, Han Li dismissed Lan Yan, then continued to cultivate.

......

Middle Earth Immortal Region, Heavenly Court.

There were countless, enormous, immortal mountains dotting the landscape, stretching as far as the eyes could see, and almost every single one of them was home to one or several heavenly palaces.

The mountains were connected by rainbow-like immortal bridges, and ethereal clouds of different colors were hovering in the air between the palaces.

Radiant light of all types of different colors were emanating from these mountains and palaces, completely outshining the natural light in the sky, and it was as if this was the only place under the heavens that was completely devoid of darkness.

Somewhere in the Heavenly Court, there was a blanket of dense, white clouds in the sky that were constantly morphing into different forms. At times, it would take on the form of a flight of majestic dragons, and at other times, it would shapeshift into a mighty stampede of horses, or a vast and turbulent white sea.

Perched on top of the clouds was an enormous palace the size of a city.

The palace was a pristine, white color, and it was etched with countless large runes, while more runes were drifting through the air around the palace.

There were many guards clad in suits of white armor stationed in the surrounding area, and the bodies of all of these guards were also formed by white clouds.

Every single one of them was giving off formidable auras comparable to High Zenith cultivators, and the weapons that they were wielding were all graded immortal treasures.

The gates of the palace were thousands of feet tall, and hanging above it was a golden plaque that carried the words "White Cloud Dao Palace" in spritely and ethereal characters that looked as if they could fly out from the plaque at any moment.

The main seat on an elevated platform in the palace was occupied by a white figure with a rather indistinct body that made them appear as if they were situated deep within a boundless expanse of ethereal space.

A burst of almighty pressure close to that of the Heavenly Dao was emanating from the white figure's body, and it felt as if everything in the palace, including even time and space, were completely under their control.

Standing in the palace before the white figure was another figure formed by golden flames, and it was none other than Qi Mozi.

"... In the end, I heard that the Almighty Sword Sect detonated the entire Tai Sui Immortal Manor, so there shouldn't have been any survivors. However, Han Li, Liu Zizai, and the others are quite powerful in their own right, and they also had a peak-Great Encompassment cultivator like Shi Kongmo on their side, so perhaps they were somehow able to escape alive.

“Hence, I implore you to send people to the Golden Origin Immortal Region right away to verify whether Han Li and the others are dead or alive," Qi Mozi said in a respectful manner.

"I've already received a report from the Almighty Sword Sect, but you've provided some useful details that weren't very clearly elaborated on in their report. You were saying that you were swept into the Tai Sui Immortal Manor by chance, is that right?" the white figure asked.

"That's right. I was pursuing Han Li in order to retrieve the Heaven Controlling Vial, and in the process, I just so happened to stumble upon the Tai Sui Immortal Manor. As for why the Tai Sui Immortal Manor appeared in the lesser Golden Origin Immortal Region and why there were so many prisoners inside, I'm afraid I do not know. Regarding Tai Sui..."

"Don't go asking questions about Tai Sui!" the white figure suddenly interjected to cut Qi Mozi off.

"My sincerest apologies!" Qi Mozi hurriedly apologized in a fearful manner.

"You just said that Han Li is only at the late-High Zenith Stage right now, so why is it that you were unable to recover the Heaven Controlling Vial from him?" the white figure asked.

"Han Li may only be at the late-High Zenith Stage at the moment, but he's cultivating the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, which completely dominates the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome.

“On top of that, he's also mastered the Five-Elemental Illusory World ability, and he had the assistance of several other powerful cultivators who were also in the Eon Pagoda at the time. Not only was I not able to recover the Heaven Controlling Vial, my physical body was destroyed in the process," Qi Mozi explained with a pained expression.

"Were they really too powerful, or did you miss the best opportunity to strike because your own selfish desires got in the way? According to my knowledge, you've been searching for the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra for a very long time, and you even sent out your own disciple some time ago for this purpose," the white figure said, and the air temperature in the palace abruptly plummeted as they spoke.

Qi Mozi's expression changed drastically upon hearing this, and he fell to his knees with a horrified expression as he implored, "Please forgive me! I'll admit that I did indeed want to obtain the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra from Han Li, but I wouldn't dare to let that get in the way of carrying out your orders! I really did only fail in my mission because the enemy was too powerful!"

The white figure remained silent, allowing the pressure in the palace to steadily build, and Qi Mozi was becoming more and more fearful by the second as his fiery body began to tremble.

Chapter 1138: Brewing Unrest

After a long silence, the pressure in the palace gradually began to dissipate as the white figure relented, "I suppose it was always going to be difficult for you, given Shi Kongmo was also there. However, the Heaven Controlling Vial is an item of the utmost importance, and it must be recovered. At the moment, the Heavenly Court can't spare many people to the cause as we're preparing for the Bodhi Banquet.

“On top of that, the Golden Origin Immortal Region is the territory of the Nine Origins Temple, so it'll be inappropriate to send other people there. Hence, we must continue to count on your Immortal Prison to recover the Heaven Controlling Vial, but failure will not be acceptable a second time, do you understand?"

Qi Mozi was ecstatic to hear this. As long as he was still assigned with the task of hunting for Han Li, there would still be a chance for him to claim the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

With that in mind, he hurriedly replied, "Yes, I understand! I'll send out all of our immortal envoys to the Golden Origin Immortal Region right away to search for Han Li, and I'll be sure to recover the Heaven Controlling Vial this time!"

"There's no need to make such a big fuss about it. I'll send someone to deliver a Heavenly Fire Holy Lotus Flower to you so you can reforge a new body," the white figure said.

"Words cannot express my gratitude!" Qi Mozi said as he extended a deep bow.

"You can go now," the white figure said as they waved a dismissive hand, and Qi Mozi extended another respectful bow before turning to depart.

Right at this moment, a red cloud flew over from afar, then entered the palace without any forewarning before transforming into a red-haired woman.

The woman appeared to be around twenty years of age, with incredibly fair and delicate skin and facial features that looked as if they had been pulled straight out of a piece of artwork. Her proportionate, yet curvaceous body was perfectly accentuated by her tight-fitting red dress, and she was truly a stunning sight to behold.

However, in spite of her breathtaking beauty, there was a completely undisguised look of arrogance on her face, giving her the appearance of an unapproachable, thorny rose.

"Fancy meeting you here, Chief Warden Qi Mozi. I heard that you had suffered such a terrible defeat in your latest outing that even your physical body was destroyed, and I had thought that that was nothing more than an unsubstantiated rumor, but it appears that I was mistaken," the red-haired woman giggled with more than a hint of mockery in her voice.

An enraged look flashed through Qi Mozi's eyes, but he immediately suppressed his own fury.

"I pay my respects to Master Bai Yun," the red-haired woman greeted as she turned to the white figure before extending a casual salute that was far more relaxed and carefree than the fearful display put on by Qi Mozi.

"No need for formalities, Chi Meng. How was your trip to the Green Forest Immortal Region?" the white figure asked, and his demeanor had warmed up significantly.

"Everything went very well, and I've purchased all of the immortal fruits that you requested," the woman by the name of Chi Meng replied.

"Good. Those fruits are going to be served up during the Bodhi Banquet, so they must be of the highest possible quality," the white figure said.

"Rest assured, Master Bai Yun, I've examined every single one of them personally to ensure their quality," Chi Meng replied.

"I trust you. You must be tired from your journey to the Green Forest Immortal Region, go and have a good rest," the white figure said.

"It was a fairly relaxed outing, so I'm not all that tired. While I was coming in, I heard you discussing a Heaven Controlling Vial with Qi Mozi. Is that the treasure that was stolen from the Nine Origins Temple all those years ago?" Chi Meng asked.

Qi Mozi and Chi Meng were not on good terms with one another, so the latter was just about to leave, but he instantly stopped in his tracks upon hearing this.

"That's right. Are you interested in this matter as well?" the white figure asked.

"Of course! On my way back, I received a message from my grandmother, telling me to ask about this," Chi Meng replied with a faint smile.

"Fellow Daoist Chi Rong has already come out of seclusion?" the white figure asked in a surprised manner, while Qi Mozi shuddered involuntarily, seemingly very fearful of the woman in question.

Chi Meng took a disdainful glance at Qi Mozi, then replied, "My grandmother only just came out of seclusion a few years ago, and she told me to pass on her greetings to you."

"I've been presiding over the official matters of the Heavenly Court in her absence, but my incompetence has led to many undesirable outcomes. Now that Fellow Daoist Chi Rong has come out of seclusion, I can finally shed this burdensome role," the white figure said with a smile.

"You're far too modest, Master Bai Yun. The Heavenly Court has thrived under your capable leadership, and I'm certain that no other Dao Ancestor would've been able to do anywhere near as good a job as you have. My grandmother often says that you may not be the most powerful Dao Ancestor, but you're certainly the most capable ruler among all of the Dao Ancestors," Chi Meng said with a bright smile.

"Fellow Daoist Chi Rong is far too kind in her appraisal of me!" Dao Ancestor Bai Yun chuckled.

"Qi Mozi, why don't you tell Chi Meng about the current situation surrounding the Heaven Controlling Vial?" Dao Ancestor Bai Yun instructed.

Qi Mozi was a little hesitant to oblige, but ultimately had no choice but to acquiesce and provide Chi Meng with a detailed rundown of the situation.

"This Han Li sounds like a very interesting character. He only ascended from to the True Immortal Realm less than thirty thousand years ago, yet he's already reached the late-High Zenith Stage. This is an unprecedented rate of progress!" Chi Meng said with an intrigued expression.

"There's no need to be surprised, Chi Meng. The Heaven Controlling Vial is an unfathomably powerful treasure, so it really isn't out of the ordinary at all for him to have made such rapid progress with the vial in his possession," Dao Ancestor Bai Yun said.

"I see. Master Bai Yun, Qi Mozi's body has already been destroyed, and he won't be able to forge a new one in a short time. On top of that, if even he's been defeated by Han Li, then I'm assuming no one else in the Immortal Prison will be able to fare any better. Hence, why not assign the task of capturing Han Li to me? I'll be sure to bring back both Han Li and the Heaven Controlling Vial," Chi Meng promised.

"There's no need for that, Fellow Daoist Chi Meng," Qi Mozi hurriedly interjected. "I failed to capture Han Li this time because I was too complacent, but I won't make the same mistake again."

"How are you going to complete the mission when you don't even have a physical body right now? Who knows how long it's going to take for you to reforge a body? Are you going to wait until after that before you go after Han Li again? Given how alert and cunning he is, who knows where he'll be by then?" Chi Meng scoffed.

Before Qi Mozi had a chance to argue any further, Dao Ancestor raised a hand to stop him.

"Chi Meng is right, Qi Mozi. You should stay in the Heavenly Court to rest and recuperate while you reforge a new body for yourself."

Qi Mozi was clearly very reluctant to accept this outcome, but he had no choice but to do so.

"Chi Meng, I'll be assigning the task of capturing Han Li to you then. Qi Mozi has already failed once, so you must make sure that you succeed in his stead," Dao Ancestor Bai Yun said in a solemn manner.

"You can count on me, Master Bai Yun!" Chi Meng promised with a wide smile, then flew out of the palace as a red cloud, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Qi Mozi quickly departed as well, and before long, Dao Ancestor Bai Yun was the only one left in the palace.

"You certainly are getting nosier by the day, Fellow Daoist Chi Rong," he chuckled coldly to himself as he remained seated in his chair.

......

Meanwhile, in a pink, semi-transparent, crystalline palace elsewhere in the Heavenly Court.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa was seated in front of a dark red jade tablet with a dark expression, and an image of a yellow toad could be seen on the tablet.

However, the tablet had already shattered into pieces, and there were two maidservants standing nearby, both of whom had fearful looks on their faces.

"How are Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan's bonded tablets?" Immortal Lord Miao Fa asked.

"Lan Yuanzi's bonded tablet has cracked open, but not fully shattered. Lan Yan's bonded tablet is completely unscathed, but we haven't been able to contact her, so she's most likely been captured by someone," one of the maidservants hurriedly answered.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa's eyes narrowed slightly in silence upon hearing this.

"The abbott has also been made aware of this, and he's very displeased by the failure to recover the Heaven Controlling Vial," the other maidservant reported in a timid voice.

"Alright, you two can go now," Immortal Lord Miao Fa dismissed as her brows furrowed slightly, and the two maidservants immediately departed.

Looks like I really underestimated you, Han Li. No matter, I'll just have to come after you myself.

......

The northwestern border of the lesser Golden Origin Immortal Region was an area with flat terrain and fertile soil, so there was far higher population density here than in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, and there were also many sects situated here as well.

Beyond the northwestern border was a boundless sea that was very abundant with spiritual qi, but also extremely violent, often generating extremely destructive windstorms, and that was why this region of the sea had been named the Windstorm Sea.

There was a vast abundance of all types of resources in the Windstorm Sea, which attracted countless treasure hunters, no less so than the Golden Origin Mountain Range.

There was a massive city right next to the Windstorm Sea called Golden Void City, and it was the largest and most illustrious city in the entirety of the lesser Golden Origin Immortal Region.

The city was thriving thanks to the countless treasure hunters who were attracted there by the Windstorm Sea, as well its interregion teleportation, which was connected to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region.

Outside the city was a huge plaza that was several dozen kilometers in size, and it was teeming with masses of people, presenting an extremely lively and bustling sight to behold.

There were streaks of light constantly flying to and away from the plaza, and right at this moment, a streak of dark green light flew over from afar, then drew to a halt above the plaza to reveal a dark green flying boat, whose passengers were none other than Han Li and Lan Yan.

"What a majestic view! As expected of the largest city in the lesser Golden Origin Immortal Region," Han Li praised as he cast his gaze toward the almost boundless Golden Void City.

"It's not bad. Once we reach Nine Origins City in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, you'll get to see what a true large city looks like," Lan Yan said with a faint smile.

"Is that right? I'm looking forward to it," Han Li replied in an indifferent manner, then stowed the Ink Dragon Flying Boat away before flying toward Golden Void City.

Chapter 1139: Racing Up the Ranks

There was a huge number of people entering and exiting Golden Void City every single day, and not only could they enter the city through the gates, many entrances had also been opened up in the city protection restriction above for cultivators to pass through.

Han Li and Lan Yan flew into the city through one of those entrances, and the city down below was teeming with pedestrians that included both cultivators and mortals.

The streets in the city were wide and tidy, and they were lined with large and opulent shops that were constructed like a series of majestic palaces, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

Some of the larger shops had even been constructed in mid-air to resemble celestial palaces, placing them above the shops on the ground both in terms of altitude and prestige.

All of these aerial shops belonged to large trading houses that were renowned across the entire Immortal Realm, including Hundred Creations Mountain and the Vast Origin House.

Under normal circumstances, perhaps Han Li would've been interested in visiting those shops to see if he could find anything that caught his eye, but given the perilous situation that Jin Tong was in, he paid no heed to the shops as he flew directly toward the central region of the city.

Before long, a golden pagoda that was hovering in mid-air appeared up ahead, and it was home to the interregion teleportation array that led to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region.

The gates of the pagoda were tightly shut, and in front of it was a white jade plaza that was mostly deserted.

Han Li and Lan Yan descended onto the plaza, and the latter looked around with a perplexed expression as she mused, "How strange. When my senior martial brother and I first arrived in the lesser Golden Origin Immortal Region, this place had been very lively and bustling, so why is it suddenly so quiet?"

Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly, but not for the same reason as Lan Yan. Instead, it was because as soon as the two of them descended onto the plaza, several burst of spiritual sense had immediately swept over their bodies.

Those bursts of spiritual sense were all extremely secretive, clearly having been masked using some type of secret technique, and he wouldn't have been able to detect them at all if not for his immense spiritual sense.

Lan Yan was also a peak-High Zenith cultivator, but her spiritual sense wasn't all that powerful, so she had failed to detect anything amiss.

Han Li was just about to attempt to follow the bursts of spiritual sense to see who the people that were spying on him were when he suddenly stopped what he was doing and strode over to the golden pagoda up ahead.

Standing on either side of the shut gates was an armorclad guard dressed in Heavenly Court attire.

Of course, the interregion teleportation array was also under the Heavenly Court's jurisdiction, and the two guards were both at the Golden Immortal Stage, yet they had been assigned with such a menial task, and that was a clear indication of just how much more powerful the lesser Golden Origin Immortal Region was compared with the immortal regions that he had previously been to.

"Can I help you, fellow daoists?" one of the guards asked in an expressionless manner.

In order to avoid drawing attention to themselves, both Han Li and Lan Yan had suppressed their cultivation bases to the Golden Immortal Stage.

"Greetings, fellow daoists. We would like to take the interregion teleportation array to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region," Han Li replied as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"I'm afraid you've come at a bad time. The interregion teleportation is temporarily closed as it's currently suffering from some problems, so you'll have to come back later," the guard said.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "May I ask when the problem is going to be fixed?"

"We're not sure at the moment. A public notice will be released once the teleportation array has been repaired, so make sure to keep up to date with the news released in the Immortal Outlet," the guard replied as he pointed to another floating building not far away from the golden pagoda, and it was none other than the Immortal Outlet in the city.

"Thank you, fellow daoists," Han Li said with a grateful salute, then flew toward the Immortal Outlet, while Lan Yan trailed along behind him.

At this moment, there were four golden-robed cultivators seated in a large hall at the top of the golden pagoda. Judging from their attire, they were also Heavenly Court cultivators, and hovering in front of each of them was a fist-sized white ball, all of which were displaying an image of Han Li and Lan Yan.

There were many people in the Immortal Outlet, and the two of them were quickly concealed in the crowd.

"The target's spiritual sense is extremely powerful, so there's no way that he would've failed to detect this level of sensory fluctuations. Hence, the fact that the two of them haven't detected anything shows that they're not the people that we're looking for," a man with a hooked nose said.

The other people in the room nodded in agreement, and they began observing the other cultivators in front of the golden pagoda.

"It's already been close to twenty years, yet we haven't found any signs of Han Li at all. Is it possible that he's already left the lesser Golden Origin Immortal Region through some other avenue?" a round-faced, middle-aged man asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"Have more patience, Fellow Daoist Liang. Like you said, it's only been less than twenty years," a gray-haired elderly man said.

"Normally, this wouldn't be a problem, but Fellow Daoist Liang's dao partner recently birthed a son for him, only for him to be sent to the lesser the Golden Origin Immortal Region before he even had a chance to spend any time with his son, so he's naturally in a hurry to get back to them," a middle-aged woman explained with an amused smile.

"Is that right? I must offer you my congratulations then, Fellow Daoist Liang," the gray-haired elderly man said with a faint smile, and the round-faced man hurriedly thanked him for his kind words.

"That's enough chit-chat! Palace Master Chi sent us here to search for Han Li, not for you to chat among yourselves. Focus on the task at hand, and if you want to chat, then do so after you're off your shift," the hook-nosed man scolded in a stern manner.

The other three cultivators in the room hurriedly gave a collective, affirmative response before returning their attention to the task at hand.

Right at this moment, the round-faced man's brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and the image on the white bead before him suddenly began to flicker erratically.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Liang?" the hook-nosed man asked.

"Some years ago, my spiritual sense was damaged during a battle against a formidable foe while I was out on a mission, so I'm struggling a little to keep up with the spiritual sense demands of operating the True Cycle Bead," the round-faced man replied in an embarrassed manner.

The hook-nosed man's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he could sense that the round-faced man's spiritual sense really was fluctuating in an unsteady fashion.

"In that case, you should go and rest, Fellow Daoist Liang. There's only half a day left of our shift anyway, so just leave the rest of the shift to the three of us," the gray-haired elderly man said.

"It doesn't make much difference whether there are three or four of us keeping an eye on the proceedings anyway," the middle-aged woman said.

The round-faced man gave the two of them a grateful glance, then turned his gaze to the hook-nosed man, who said, "Go and rest, Fellow Daoist Liang. Try to recuperate as much as possible so this doesn't happen again."

The round-faced man immediately gave an affirmative response, then stowed his white bead away before departing.

......

Meanwhile, Han Li and Lan Yan had already made their way into the Immortal Outlet.

Unbeknownst to him, his careful and cautious nature had just saved him once again.

This Immortal Outlet was far larger than the ones in the other immortal regions that he had visited, but the layout was roughly the same.

On either side of the Immortal Outlet were shops that sold all types of pills, immortal treasures, and spirit materials, while at its center stood a huge, stone wall that was over ten thousand feet tall and laden with missions.

Beyond the stone wall was a raised platform that was roughly the same height as the missions wall, and that was the Immortal Slaying List, containing all of the Heavenly Court's most wanted fugitives.

At the moment, the missions wall and the Immortal Slaying List were completely surrounded by people, all of whom seemed to be very excited about something.

Han Li was rather intrigued to see this, and he scanned his gaze over the missions wall and the Immortal Slaying List.

All of a sudden, his expression changed slightly as he noticed that his name had climbed into the top ten on the Immortal Slaying List.

There was a long list of crimes attached to his name, and the full description read: Han Li, member of the Reincarnation Palace, cultivator of forbidden techniques, main perpetrator in the deaths of Northern Glacial Immortal Palace Master Xiao Jinhan and Golden Origin Immortal Palace Master Dongfang Bai, collaborator with the Devil Realm, perpetrator in the destruction of close to half of the Golden Origin Mountain Range. Wanted dead or alive for fifty million Immortal Origin Stones.

There was also a mission on the missions wall released by the Heavenly Court for his capture, and attached to the mission was a detailed account of many pieces of information pertaining to him, including things like this lightning-attribute Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, as well as his proficiency in Infernal Devilish Eyes, the Heavenly Purgatory Baleful Arts, and the laws of time.

It was also stated in the mission that Han Li was currently still in the Golden Origin Immortal Region, and that even those who were able to provide any useful leads on him would be given handsome compensation.

Even though Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 had also been present in the Tai Sui Immortal Manor, their rankings on the Immortal Slaying List hadn't changed much at all, and it seemed like the Heavenly Court was focusing all of its efforts on capturing Han Li.

"Who exactly is this Han Li? It's been a very long time since such a huge reward has been offered on the Immortal Slayin List!"

"If I had fifty million Immortal Origin Stones, I would go into seclusion and refuse to come out until I reached the High Zenith Stage!"

"You're far too short-sighted! With so many Immortal Origin Stones, there's no need to arduously cultivate, just start your own sect so you can be revered as a founder!"

"All those on the Immortal Slaying List are completely out of reach as far as us Golden Immortals are concerned, so I suggest all of you snap out of your fantasies."

"Indeed. As alluring as a reward of fifty million Immortal Origin Stones is, it won't do you any good if you're dead!"

"Risk and reward have always come hand in hand. If you don't even have the courage to dare to dream, then why even come here at all?"

"So not only is he a member of the Reincarnation Palace, the collapse of the Golden Origin Mountain Range was also brought about by him in collaboration with the Devil Realm!"

"I've heard about the collapse of the Golden Origin Mountain Range. Countless settlements were destroyed during that disaster. What a heinous scoundrel this Han Li is!"

Everyone was discussing Han Li's new ranking on the Immortal Slaying List, and many of them were contacting their respective sects to keep an eye out for him.

There were even some who had begun secretly scouring through those around them in the Immortal Outlet with their spiritual sense. After all, a reward of fifty million Immortal Origin Stones was simply far too alluring.

Chapter 1140: Exposed

"The situation isn't looking good here, Fellow Daoist Han, I think we should get out of here righ away," Lan Yan urged through voice transmission.

Han Li had planted an extremely powerful restriction in her consciousness, so if he were killed, then she would also meet her demise.

Han Li was also struck by the urge to leave Golden Void City right away upon seeing all of this, but after taking a moment to assess the situation, he immediately regained his composure, and he quickly decided on a course of action.

"There's no need to panic, just act natural," he replied through voice transmission, and he began to look up at the missions wall while feigning the same look of excitement as what was displayed on the faces of everyone around him.

Lan Yan faltered slightly upon seeing this, and she was also instilled with a sense of calmness and reassurance, as if there were some type of soothing quality to Han Li's words.

Han Li began walking back and forth in front of the missions wall and the Immortal Slaying List, just like many people around him were doing.

Both he and Lan Yan had adopted disguises using Reincarnation Palace masks, so even a Great Encompassment cultivator wouldn't be able to see through them unless they were paying particularly close attention.

Furthermore, they had only displayed a fleeting instant of alarm upon seeing Han Li's new position on the Immortal Slaying List, so no one would've been able to notice their reaction unless they had been looking closely at the two of them at the exact right instant.

They had only just arrived in Golden Void City, and they hadn't done anything to draw attention to themselves, so there shouldn't have been anyone keeping an eye on them.

What Han Li had failed to anticipate was that there really was someone intently scrutinizing him and Lan Yan from deep within the Immortal Outlet, and it was none other than the round-faced man from the golden pagoda.

I'm certain that those two are suspicious! That man didn't display any reaction earlier, but there was a momentary ripple in his spiritual sense. No one else noticed that, but it was as clear as day to my Soul Searching Eyes! It's a pity that I wasn't able to arrive in time to see their initial reaction to the Immortal Slaying List. Otherwise, I would be able to confirm my suspicions with a greater degree of certainty.

At this moment, the round-faced man was intently observing Han Li and Lan Yan with a film of peculiar light over his eyes.

Han Li walked around in the Immortal Outlet for a while longer, then called out to Lan Yan before departing, and after leaving the Immortal Outlet, the two of them immediately began flying toward an exit in the distance.

The round-faced man tailed the two of them out of the Immortal Outlet with a contemplative look on his face.

It looks like the two of them are planning to leave the city right away. I knew they were suspicious! Should I alert everyone else? No, the compensation for finding a suspicious individual is far too little.

Lin'er's immortal acupoints are naturally feeble, and it'll take an enormous amount of Immortal Origin Stones to cure his condition. I have to confirm that man's identity first before and only report him once I'm absolutely certain that he's Han Li!

With that in mind, the round-faced man set off in pursuit of Han Li's duo as an indistinct black shadow.

It didn't take long before Han Li and Lan Yan flew out of Golden Void City through one of the many exits, and Han Li immediately swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of azure light that encompassed both himself and Lan Yan before flying away into the distance.

Even though the chance of She Chan's Ink Dragon Flying Boat being recognized were very slim, he didn't dare to risk bringing it out so close to Golden Void City.

At his current speed, he was able to travel millions of kilometers in the blink of an eye, and only then did he slowly draw to a halt.

"Why did you stop, Fellow Daoist Han? We're still not completely safe here," Lan Yan asked with a perplexed expression.

"We'll have to keep going from here, but before that, I have to take care of something," Han Li replied with a faint smile, then suddenly made a grabbing motion toward a nearby hill.

A giant, golden hand the size of a small mountain instantly appeared above the hill before grabbing down onto it, and the hill was pulverized in the blink of an eye, leaving a massive crater that was thousands of feet in size in its wake.

Immediately thereafter, the round-faced man flew out of the crater before fleeing in a panic, and his aura was exposed, revealing him to be an early-High Zenith cultivator.

"Did you really think that I hadn't noticed you following us all this time?" Han Li harrumphed coldly, and the giant, golden hand abruptly vanished at his behest, then appeared directly in front of the round-faced man before closing itself forcefully around his body.

The round-faced man's body instantly exploded, but instead of blood and flesh splattering in all directions, his body split up into hundreds of streaks of black light that erupted forth in all directions.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he discovered that he couldn't detect the round-faced man's true body, as if he really had split himself up into hundreds of parts, with each of them concealed within one of the streaks of black light.

However, he remained calm and composed as he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which instantly released a wave of golden ripples that encompassed all of the streaks of black light within them, immobilizing them on the spot.

At this point, his time law powers had already completely recovered, and it had become even more formidable than his former peak.

He swept a sleeve through the air to release countless arcs of golden lightning, which formed a lightning cage around all of the streaks of black light, then exploded violently to instantly eradicate all of the streaks of black light trapped inside.

An anguished howl rang out from within the lightning before instantly fading away into silence, while Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief.

The round-faced man appeared to have mastered the laws of shadows, which were weak to the laws of lightning, and with the Mantra Treasured Axis on Han Li's side as well, there was no way that he would've allowed the man to get away.

Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis, and the surrounding golden ripples and golden lightning quickly dissipated.

"Who was that, Fellow Daoist Han? Was it a Heavenly Court spy? Could it be that they're already onto us?" Lan Yan asked in a fearful manner.

"He most likely was a Heavenly Court spy, but rest assured, he won't be around to tell anyone about us," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

He could tell that the round-faced man was a living cultivator, rather than something like a clone, and given how quickly he had killed the man, there should've been no time for him to transmit any information to anyone.

However, as a safety precaution, they still had to leave this place right away.

With that in mind, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to summon the Ink Dragon Flying Boat, which flew away into the distance with himself and Lan Yan onboard.

Meanwhile, Immortal Lord Miao Fa was standing in a peaceful courtyard in Golden Void City, tending to a floral garden.

Right at this moment, she was approached by a maidservant in a green dress, who reported, "We've received news about Han Li, esteemed holy envoy."

"Is this piece of news worthy of my attention, or is it going to be a false alarm, just like all of the other times?" Immortal Lord Miao Fa asked as she brought a pink flower to her nose.

"This piece of news was personally brought to us by a spy that was planted in the Heavenly Court, and he claims to have a recording of his battle against Han Li, so it should be a reliable lead. However, he insists on showing the recording only to you," the maidservant replied.

"Alright, get him to come and see me," Immortal Lord Miao Fa instructed as she tossed the pink flower away.

The maidservant gave an affirmative response, and it didn't take long before she returned with the round-faced man.

At this moment, he was looking very pale, as if he had suffered some severe injuries, but there was an excited look on his face.

"Immortal Lord Miao Fa," the round-faced man greeted with a respectful salute.

"You have information on Han Li, is that right?" Immortal Lord Miao Fa asked.

"That's right," the round-faced man replied, then delivered a detailed recount of his initial encounter with Han Li, followed by their subsequent battle.

"Here's a recording of our battle," he concluded as he flipped a hand over to produce a black bead, which was displaying a recording of the battle.

"That's definitely him! His physical appearance is different, but I'm certain that's Han Li!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa declared as her eyes lit up with excitement, and the round-faced man heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this.

He had paid a heavy price in order to verify Han Li's identity, and he was glad that the sacrifice had been worth it.

"Where is he right now?" Immortal Lord Miao Fa asked.

"I used a soul-splitting technique to keep an avatar here, while I pursued and fought him outside the city with my true body. He should be under the impression that he's managed to kill me before I could alert anyone, so he most likely won't have employed any extreme measures to try and get away.

“On top of that, only a few minutes have passed since the conclusion of our battle, so I'm sure you'll be able to track him down with your unmatched powers," the round-faced man replied as he pulled out a map of the area near Golden Void City, and there was a spot marked out on the map, denoting the site of his battle against Han Li.

"You've done very well. Lü Xin, take him away for his reward," Immortal Lord Miao Fa instructed with a pleased expression.

The round-faced man was ecstatic to hear this, and he thanked Immortal Lord Miao Fa before departing from the courtyard with the maidservant.

Immediately following his departure, two more maidservants appeared beside Immortal Lord Miao Fa without any warning.

It was a pair of identical twins, and a cold look flashed through the eyes of one of them as she asked, "Now that we've already learned Han Li's whereabouts, should we dispose of that man to ensure that no news gets out?"

"There's no need for that, just keep him detained here for a few days. If it becomes known that we've been killing our informants rather than rewarding them, then no one would be willing to come to our Nine Origins Temple with information in the future," Immortal Lord Miao Fa replied.

"Your foresight is truly unmatched, esteemed holy envoy," the maidservant replied.

"There's no need to pay attention to these trivial matters. Right now, our top priority is to capture Han Li," Immortal Lord Miao Fa said as she swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of blue light that swept up the pair of maidservants before she set off into the distance.

Chapter 1141: Fleeing from the City

Not far away from Immortal Lord Miao Fa's little courtyard was a restaurant, and seated in one of its booths was none other than the red-haired woman by the name of Chi Meng.

There were around a dozen flagons on the table before her, most of which were already empty.

Looks like she's finally found him!

A faint smile appeared on her face as she looked out the window at the streak of blue light racing through the air.

The hook-nosed man from the golden pagoda was also standing in the booth, and he praised, "Your wisdom is truly unmatched, Mistress Chi Meng. Could it be that you had already guessed that Liang Fang was a Nine Origins Temple spy?"

"I didn't know, but the Golden Origin Immortal Region is the Nine Origins Temple's territory, so no matter how vigilant we are, infiltration from the Nine Origins Temple is all but inevitable. As opposed to worrying about something that I won't be able to prevent anyway, it's much better to keep a close eye on Miao Fa, and she'll eventually find Han Li for us," Chi Meng replied.

"But won't that allow Miao Fa to seize the initiative? What if she manages to capture Han Li before we can get there?" the hook-nosed man asked in a concerned manner.

"That's not a concern. Han Li was able to evade capture from the Heavenly Court for so long, and he even managed to destroy Qi Mozi's physical body, so he definitely won't be captured so easily," Chi Meng replied with an assured smile.

The hook-nosed man was still rather concerned, but he didn't say anything further.

"Miao Fa's already gone far enough, let's go after her now," Chi Meng said as she swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of red light to encompass both herself and the hook-nosed man before setting off after Immortal Lord Miao Fa.

......

A golden lightning array appeared in the air above a lush mountain range in the Golden Origin Immortal Region, and the array contained none other than Han Li and Lan Yan.

After leaving Golden Void City, they had traveled using the Ink Dragon Flying Boat for some time, following which Han Li stowed the flying boat away, then concealed his own aura using the Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique before traveling on foot for a while.

Given his current physical constitution, traveling on foot wasn't much slower than traveling by flight.

After that, Han Li had teleported close to twenty times in succession using his lightning teleportation array to reach this point.

They were now an immeasurable distance away from Golden Void City, and he had done everything in his power to cover his tracks, so he was fairly confident that they were safe.

From there, Han Li turned back to look in the direction of Golden Void City with a contemplative look on his face.

Given how closely he was being pursued by the Heavenly Court, traveling by interregion teleportation array to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region was far too risky.

It seemed that he had no choice but to take Wyrm 3's advice and focus on advancing his own cultivation base for now.

He was already at the peak-High Zenith Stage, and he had made all of the preparations required for a breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage, so it was time to attempt a breakthrough.

If he could reach the Great Encompassment Stage, his powers would be enhanced to a whole new level, thereby significantly boosting his chances of successfully rescuing Jin Tong from the Nine Origins Temple.

Having made up his mind, he began to inspect his surroundings.

According to a map of the Golden Origin Immortal Region that he had acquired, this was the Oasis Mountain Range in the northwestern part of the Golden Origin Immortal Region. It was a very secluded place, and there weren't any special spirit materials or demon beasts to be found here, so it was very quiet and a perfect place for seclusion.

Han Li flew down onto an obscure part of a mountain below, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a flurry of sword qi that quickly dug out a cave into the mountain face.

After some brief renovations, a cave abode took shape, and he set up numerous layers of restrictions that encompassed the entire cave abode and the surrounding area in a radius of several dozen kilometers.

All of these restrictions were imbued with different types of law powers, so they would be able to stall even a Great Encompassment cultivator for some time.

"Fellow Daoist Lan, I'm going to go into seclusion here, you can take this time to rest as well," Han Li said, and Lan Yan nodded in response.

Han Li didn't waste any more time as he made his way into the secret chamber, while Lan Yan entered another room before taking a seat.

After entering the secret chamber, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, conjuring a crimson restriction that encompassed the entire room.

With another sweep of his sleeve, he released the Essence Fire Child.

The flames on the Essence Fire Child's body were still predominantly silver, but some of it had begun to turn white, and the law power fluctuations emanating from its body had also become significantly more formidable than before, which was naturally a very encouraging sight for Han Li.

The Essence Fire Raven had been refining that white fire bead this entire time, and its efforts were certainly paying off.

"I'll be going into seclusion for some time, so I won't be able to supervise Lan Yan. Keep an eye on her for me, and if she tries to do anything out of line, you have my permission to kill her," Han Li said as a cold look flashed through his eyes.

The Essence Fire Child nodded in response, then flew into the surrounding crimson restriction as a streak of silver light.

Lan Yan didn't seem to harbor any intentions of plotting against him, but this was going to be an extremely important period of seclusion for him, so he had to proceed with the utmost caution.

Unfortunately, Weeping Soul was still yet to fully refine Ghost King Wu Chao's power. Otherwise, he would feel much more confident and assured with her protection.

Having said that, the Essence Fire Child should've also been more than capable of keeping Lan Yan in check.

With that in mind, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed and began to meditate.

Close to half a day flew by in a flash, and by the time he reopened his eyes, he had already primed himself into the best possible condition.

With a sweep of his sleeve, he summoned a white incense burner, protruding out which was a stick of silver incense that was around three inches tall.

After igniting the stick of incense, it began to release faint, white smoke that resembled morning mist, alongside a faint, fragrant aroma.

This Soul Condensing Incense was extremely beneficial to the soul and could significantly increase one's chances of a successful breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage.

Han Li then flipped a hand over to produce three jade vials, within one of which was the True Profound Pill that had been given to him by Daoist Xie, and that was going to be the most important contributing factor to a Great Encompassment Stage breakthrough for him.

As for the other two vials, one of them contained a type of golden spirit liquid, while the other contained three green pills, and both of those things had been painstakingly acquired precisely for this breakthrough.

First, Han Li picked up the jade vial that contained the golden spirit liquid, then tipped a few drops of it into his own mouth.

A burst of radiant, golden light instantly appeared over his body, while his time law powers began to churn like boiling water. His Mantra Treasured Axis, Time Severing Torch, Clear Time Vial, Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree, and Illusory Dawn Hourglass all appeared around him in succession, then began to rapidly revolve around his body.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as he picked took one of the green pills from the other vial, then closed his eyes to channel the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra

The True Profound Pill was something that was only to be taken at the very end, so it remained in its vial for now.

Han Li closed his eyes, and the golden light radiating from his body became brighter and brighter, while a burst of tremendous time law power fluctuations swept through the air, causing the entire secret chamber to tremble and quiver.

Inside another room in the cave abode, Lan Yan's eyes abruptly sprang open as she cast her gaze toward Han Li's secret chamber with a stunned expression.

Meanwhile, above a certain swamp in the Golden Origin Immortal Region.

A streak of blue light flew onto the scene from afar, then drew to a halt above the swamp to reveal Immortal Lord Miao Fa and her two maidservants.

"Esteemed holy envoy, the trail of Han Li's spiritual qi fluctuations suddenly cuts off here," one of the maidservants said, and she was holding a translucent, blue basin that reflected the surrounding area.

Specks of green light were rising up from within the basin, and they stretched all the way to this precise spot from afar before abruptly vanishing here.

"Looks like he must've concealed his aura from this point onward," Immortal Lord Miao Fa mused as she raised an eyebrow.

"The Mirror Water Basin is no longer able to track him, so you'll have to do so yourself from now on, esteemed holy envoy," the maidservant said.

"Alright, you two can stand down," Immortal Lord Miao Fa said with a dismissive wave, then opened her mouth to release a ball of blue light.

Numerous translucent, blue threads surfaced within the blue light, then converged toward a single spot, quickly forming a millstone-sized, vertical, blue eye that began scouring the surrounding area.

Rings of blue light could be seen flashing within the vertical eye, presenting a profound sight to behold.

Initially, Immortal Lord Miao Fa was brimming with confidence, but as she continued to inspect the surrounding area with the vertical eye, her confident expression quickly turned to disbelief.

How is this possible? Even a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator like myself shouldn't be able to hide their tracks from my Water Emperor Divine Eye, how could Han Li possibly have such an advanced self-concealment technique up his sleeve?

Of course, the reality was that Immortal Lord Miao Fa was overestimating Han Li. If he had continued to travel from this point using his immortal spiritual power, then no matter how he tried to conceal his spiritual power fluctuations, there was no way that he would've been able to cover his tracks.

However, it was from this point onward that Han Li began using the Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique to conceal his own aura, and Lan Yan had been thrown into the Flower Branch domain, so of course there were no tracks left behind.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa had failed to take this possibility into account and was solely searching for residual spiritual power fluctuations, so she was naturally struggling to find anything.

However, her Water Emperor Divine Eye was so powerful that she was ultimately able to find some residual spiritual power fluctuations left behind by some of the immortal treasures in Han Li's body, such as his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

However, these spiritual power fluctuations were extremely faint, and they were constantly cutting off intermittently, so she could only proceed onward in a slow and timid manner while continuing to track the faint trail left behind.

Chi Meng and the hook-nosed man were trailing along far behind, and they were very disgruntled by this slow rate of progress, but neither of them were proficient in tracking techniques, so they had no choice but to rely on Immortal Lord Miao Fa.

Chapter 1142: Miao Fa’s Arrival

Inside his cave abode in the Oasis Mountain Range, Han Li was still attempting to reach the Great Encompassment Stage.

Three years flew by in a flash.

The golden light in Han Li's secret chamber was glowing brighter and brighter, and it was beginning to seep out even with all of the restrictions that he had set up.

Bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations were surging throughout the cave abode, making it impossible for Lan Yan to cultivate, so all she was doing now was waiting for Han Li to come out of seclusion.

She had already guessed Han Li's objective for going into seclusion, and she didn't know how to feel about this.

She didn't know what Han Li was plotting, but if he were to reach the Great Encompassment Stage, then that would surely be bad news for the Nine Origins Temple.

However, on the flip side, a breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage for Han Li would grant both of them a far higher degree of safety.

On top of that, once he reached the Great Encompassment Stage, she would become far less useful to him, and given his personality, there was a chance that he would let her go.

If Han Li were to fail to make his breakthrough, then she would have to continue leading this unpredictable and perilous life on the run, and she didn't know when she would be granted her freedom again.

With all that in mind, she didn't know if she wanted Han Li to succeed or fail.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out from within Han Li's secret chamber.

A burst of immense law power fluctuations swept through the entire cave abode like a turbulent wave, damaging close to half of the restrictions inside.

Lan Yan was also knocked by this burst of time law power fluctuations, only drawing to a halt after crashing into a wall.

She cast her gaze toward Han Li's secret chamber to discover that the golden light there had already faded, indicating that he had failed in his breakthrough attempt, and she couldn't help but heave a forlorn sigh.

Looks like deep down, I'm hoping for him to succeed, after all...

Inside the secret chamber, Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed with frustration.

Just as Lan Yan had guessed, his breakthrough attempt had concluded in failure.

There weren't any negative consequences to arise from this, but he couldn't find a reason for his failure.

At the moment, he had over two hundred time law threads, which was roughly on par with the number of law threads attained by the average Great Encompassment cultivator, so that shouldn't have been a problem.

He had also opened 395 immortal acupoints, and his physical constitution was incredibly formidable, while his soul was also far more powerful than that of the average peak-High Zenith cultivator thanks to his cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

On paper, he satisfied all of the prerequisites, so the breakthrough should've been quite smooth and effortless.

As Han Li carefully mulled over his failed breakthrough, he decided that the problem had most likely arisen from his time law threads.

Initially, everything had been going quite well, but at some point in his breakthrough attempt, his time law threads had suddenly been thrown into a state of disarray, thereby scrambling the immortal spiritual power in his body to spoil his breakthrough attempt.

Could it be that I still don't have enough time law threads?

If his time law threads were indeed the problem, then he couldn't think of any other possible factor holding him back aside from an insufficient number of time law threads.

The quickest way for him to attain more time law threads would be to use the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra to refine treasures that contained time law powers, but such treasures were extremely precious and rare.

Furthermore, he already had over two hundred time law threads, and he had no idea how many more he would have to attain in order to facilitate a successful breakthrough..

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he slapped himself on the forehead for not thinking of this earlier.

How could I have forgotten about the Eon Divine Lamp? If I can refine that into time law threads, then that would surely be enough.

At the moment, the lamp was still in an unlit state.

Since leaving the Tai Sui Immortal Manor, Han Li had made many attempts to reignite the flame, but to no avail.

Even though the Eon Divine Lamp was unlit, it was still giving off bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations.

Han Li immediately channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and his five time-attribute law treasures appeared around him one after another.

The five bursts of time law powers released by the five treasures quickly intertwined, then compressed toward a single spot to form a thick, golden ring of light.

The ring of light was compressed even further at Han Li's behest, and it began to release a burst of powerful suction force while approaching the Eon Divine Lamp.

The golden ring encompassed the Eon Divine Lamp while revolving rapidly, releasing a burst of tremendous suction force in an attempt to draw the time law powers out of the lamp.

However, despite the golden ring's best efforts, the time law powers within the Eon Divine Lamp remained completely unmoved.

Could it be that the Eon Divine Lamp is an immortal treasure of too high a caliber to be refined?

After persevering for a while longer, Han Li withdrew the golden ring, and he wasn't particularly surprised to see this as something like this had happened once before.

That golden plate that he had obtained from the ruins of the True Mantra Sect was something that he had also been unable to refine using his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

With that in mind, it seemed like the Eon Divine Lamp and the golden plate were treasures of a similar caliber.

In fact, perhaps the golden plate was a treasure of an even higher caliber as at the very least, Han Li was able to somewhat control the Eon Divine Lamp, while the golden plate was like an immovable object as far as he was concerned.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he stowed the Eon Divine Lamp away.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he pulled out a Reincarnation Palace mask, then released a mission, seeking to purchase time-attribute immortal treasures.

At this point, Han Li had already accumulated an astronomical sum of Immortal Origin Stones, so this wasn't a problem for him.

Aside from the Reincarnation Palace, he couldn't think of any other avenues that he could turn to for this cause, so all he could do was wait.

After doing all of that, Han Li began channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra once again, trying to see if there had been any other problems resulting in his failed breakthrough.

Close to half a year flew by in the blink of an eye.

Inside the secret chamber, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, and his entire body was enshrouded in a layer of golden light. Manifestations of his five time-attribute law treasures were hovering in the air around him, and the entire secret chamber was rippling with time law power fluctuations.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyes suddenly sprang open in alarm, and the manifestations of his five time-attribute law treasures vanished into his body, following which he also vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, he had already arrived outside the secret chamber directly behind Lan Yan.

Before she had a chance to react in surprise, Han Li grabbed onto her by the throat, and a string of golden runes wrapped itself around her body like a spirit snake, instantly immobilizing her.

"My apologies, Fellow Daoist Lan."

As soon as Han Li's voice trailed off, a resounding boom rang out as the mountain that the cave abode was situated in exploded violently, exposing the entire cave abode to the light of day.

Han Li looked up with one hand still locked firmly around Lan Yan's throat, and high up in the sky was a crystalline throne that was shaped like a lotus flower, seated atop which was none other than Immortal Lord Miao Fa.

Her head was cocked to the side, and she was resting her cheek on her hand as she looked down at Han Li with a disdainful expression.

Han Li's pupils instantly contracted slightly upon sensing her mid-Great Encompassment Stage aura. Despite the fact that she was seated on her throne in a lackadaisical manner, Han Li was feeling more pressure from her than he did even from the likes of Qi Mozi.

Behind her were the two identical twin maidservants, both of whom were at the early-High Zenith Stage, and one of them was holding an ornate, embroidered umbrella, while the other was holding a peacock feather fan.

"I had thought that it must've taken a very remarkable man to have defeated both She Chan and Qi Mozi, but you're just a piece of cowardly scum who would stoop as low as to use a frail and defenseless woman as a shield. How disappointing," Immortal Lord Miao Fa scoffed.

"That's not exactly a fair statement, is it? Fellow Daoist Lan is far from a frail and defenseless woman. No matter how I tried to coerce her, she refused to submit to me and even attempted suicide on multiple occasions, so I was forced to plant restrictions upon her. While it's true that I'm using her as a shield now, what else am I supposed to do in the face of an assailant far more powerful than myself?" Han Li asked in a resigned manner.

Lan Yan knew that Han Li was lying in order to paint her in a positive light, and a hint of guilt and gratitude welled up in her heart upon hearing this.

"If she's incompetent enough to have been captured, then she deserves to die," Immortal Lord Miao Fa said as she took an expressionless glance at Lan Yan, and a layer of white frost instantly appeared over her face.

Before long, her entire body had been encased in a layer of blue ice crystals.

A burst of silver flames erupted out of the tip of Han Li's finger to contend against the spreading frost as he flew back in retreat, yet he had only managed to retreat no more than a thousand feet when a huge shadow appeared over him, and the embroidered umbrella came descending upon him from above.

Han Li immediately darted away to the side to take evasive measures, but the umbrella-wielding maidservant was dancing elegantly on top of the umbrella, and it was constantly changing directions in accordance with her movements to ensure that it remained above Han Li's head.

Meanwhile, the fan-wielding maidservant flew over to Lan Yan's side, then swept a sleeve over her, and the layer of frost clinging to her body instantly melted away, following which she was casually tossed over to Immortal Lord Miao Fa.

"Lan Yan pays her respects to Immortal Lord Miao Fa," Lan Yan greeted as she fell to her knees.

"Where's Lan Yuanzi? Is he dead or alive?" Immortal Lord Miao Fa asked.

A grief-stricken look instantly appeared on Lan Yan's face at the mention of Lan Yuanzi.

Chapter 1143: No Escape

It was clear from Lan Yan's expression what had become of Lan Yuanzi, and Immortal Lord Miao Fa harrumphed coldly, "If it isn't for the fact that I'm on good terms with your master, you would already be dead right now. At least you have some backbone and didn't put our Nine Origins Temple to shame. You can stand up now."

Lan Yan immediately rose to her upon hearing this, then stood obediently behind the crystalline throne as she cast a concerned gaze toward Han Li.

After tossing Lan Yan to Immortal Lord Miao Fa, the fan-wielding maidservant also set off in pursuit of Han Li while sweeping her fan toward him to release gusts of fierce, azure wind.

Han Li was already preoccupied with evading the umbrella, and as opposed to also trying to evade the gusts of oncoming wind, he flew directly into them while simultaneously channeling his Reversal True Axis ability, aiming to take advantage of the gusts of wind to help him flee the scene.

It was very clear to him that he was no match for this woman, so he immediately attempted to flee without even trying to stand and fight.

However, as soon as he came into contact with the gusts of azure wind, it was as if his entire body had suddenly become more buoyant, and not only was he not able to get away, he was sent drifting up involuntarily into the air.

At the same time, the embroidered umbrella overhead descended from above, releasing a burst of powerful suction force that sucked him in in a flash.

As soon as he was sucked into the umbrella, a series of runed chains trailed down from above, firmly binding him to its shaft, immediately following which the umbrella closed itself around him.

Trapped within the umbrella, all of the immortal spiritual power in Han Li's body was sealed away, and he wasn't able to muster up even an ounce of strength.

The umbrella-wielding maidservant made a beckoning motion, and the umbrella shrank down to around half its original size while flying back to her.

The maidservant then closed her arms around the umbrella, hugging it to her chest, while her twin sister had also returned to her side.

An incredulous look appeared on Lan Yan's face upon seeing this, seemingly unable to believe how easily Han Li had been captured.

"How is it possible that She Chan was defeated by such a pathetic little High Zenith Stage weasel?" Immortal Lord Miao Fa scoffed in a disdainful manner.

Right at this moment, the umbrella-wielding maidservant's brows suddenly furrowed slightly as she looked down at her umbrella, which was rippling and bulging slightly, as if Han Li were struggling inside.

"Don't bother! Even the average Great Encompassment cultivator wouldn't be able to free themselves from our esteemed holy envoy's Heavenly Entrapment Umbrella," the maidservant sneered, but her expression then changed drastically as she threw the umbrella away with an alarmed yelp.

A plume of smoke had begun rising up from a small hole that had been burned into the surface of the umbrella, and a rainbow flame slowly emerged from the hole like a blooming, rainbow flower.

Immediately thereafter, the rainbow flame sprang upward, and a tiny, silver figure shot out of the hole in the umbrella, then instantly transformed into a massive, silver fire raven.

As the fire raven spread its wings, bursts of scorching flames shot out of its body like a meteor shower toward Immortal Lord Miao Fa and the others.

The fan-wielding maidservant frantically swept her fan through the air to dispel all of the oncoming bursts of fire, and at the same time, Han Li burst out of the umbrella before flying away into the distance, followed closely by the Essence Fire Raven.

"That's an Essence Fire Raven that's devoured Rainbow Fire Pill Sand! What a rare sight! Looks like you do have some tricks up your sleeve, but if you think that's going to be enough to allow you to get away from me, then you're sorely mistaken," Immortal Lord Miao Fa mused as she casually rose to her feet, seemingly completely unconcerned by the fact that Han Li was getting away.

Immediately thereafter, she joined her palms in front of her own chest, and her hands instantly turned as translucent as ice.

At the same time, wisps of white mist began to seep out from between her lips, and a cloud of thin mist instantly spread over the surrounding area in a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers, freezing the entire space encompassed within the area.

At this point, Han Li was already thousands of kilometers away, and upon sensing the drastic drop in air temperature around him, he immediately withdrew the Essence Fire Raven back into his body before accelerating dramatically to double his own speed.

However, this still wasn't enough for him to get away, and an enormous wall of ice abruptly rose up before him to block the path ahead.

Han Li immediately channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might before throwing an almighty punch at the wall of ice.

Scintillating, white starlight erupted out of his fist as it struck the wall of ice with a resounding boom, and the entire wall shuddered violently as it caved in to form a ring-shaped crater that spanned almost the entire surface area of the wall, but it was able to remain intact.

Right as Han Li was about to throw another punch to break through the wall, a flurry of snowflakes suddenly began to drift through the air overhead, and Immortal Lord Miao Fa appeared atop the wall amid a flash of white light.

In the instant that she set foot onto the wall, a layer of white light instantly spread over its surface, and in the span of mere seconds, the wall had returned to its former, undamaged state.

"There's no way you're escaping from my spirit domain. If you surrender now, you'll spare yourself from some punishment," Immortal Lord Miao Fa declared as she looked down at Han Li in a cold and arrogant manner.

Han Li paid no heed to her as he flew back in retreat while channeling his Reversal True Axis ability, and at the same time, he began making a string of hand seals, preparing to conjure up a lightning teleportation array.

However, before the lightning array was able to take shape, a huge, hexagonal ice crystal appeared directly above him, and six rays of dazzling, blue light came refracting out of it.

The rays of light cascaded down from above, instantly forming six translucent, white walls that created an encirclement around Han Li.

The walls were giving off tremendous glacial qi that instantly snuffed out the lightning flashing over Han Li's body, and it was as if his connection with the world around him had been instantly severed.

At the same time, a layer of silver light appeared over the six walls, transforming them into six silver mirrors, each of which bore a reflection of Han Li, but they were all displaying different expressions.

There was one that was watching him with a cold expression, another one that was observing him with a faint smile, one that was looking elsewhere entirely with their arms crossed...

Han Li hurriedly activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes, upon which he discovered that there was no vitality to be gleaned in these reflections, indicating that they were nothing more than illusions.

Assured by this discovery, Han Li hurriedly channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, then threw a punch at one of the silver mirrors.

However, as soon as he sprang into action, all six of the reflections did the same, converging toward him with their fists raised.

Han Li continued onward without pause as he threw a punch into the mirror up ahead with all his might, but in the instant that his fist struck the mirror, six arms came extending out of all of the mirrors from six different directions to connect with his body.

Han Li instantly felt a burst of excruciating pain jolt through his entire body, and he felt as if he were on the verge of falling apart at the seams.

Furthermore, the glacial qi emanating from the silver mirrors was only becoming more and more formidable, and a layer of white frost had already appeared over his body, while his immortal spiritual power circulation had all but stagnated.

With no time to waste, he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and true spirit bloodlines in unison, instantly transforming into a giant devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

His three heads let loose a collective, thunderous roar as he spun around on the spot like a spinning top while lashing out with his six fists in unison, directing one toward each of the six mirrors.

Six resounding booms rang out at once as a burst of tremendous power erupted from within the silver mirrors, causing them to shudder violently as a series of fine cracks appeared over their surfaces.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he was just about to lash out once again when a layer of blue light flashed over the mirrors, and all of them were instantly restored to their original condition.

At the same time, six devilish deity reflections appeared in the mirrors before lashing out at Han Li in unison, and a string of loud thumps rang out in rapid succession as Han Li was struck by a ferocious barrage of punches.

He felt as if all of the bones in his body were about to be snapped, and in particular, one of the fists had struck him on the back of the head, almost knocking him out cold.

After unleashing that devastating barrage of punches, the reflections in the mirrors finally ceased their assault.

How is this possible...

At this point, Han Li had already reverted back to his human form, and he sat down onto the ground in a defeated manner.

He didn't dare to attack the mirrors again, so he could only continue to inspect his surroundings using his Infernal Devilish Eyes, but he wasn't able to see anything that could get him out of this predicament.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa was able to see everything that Han Li was doing from outside the encirclement of mirrors, and she found his futile struggles rather amusing as she sneered, "Cease your futile struggles and accept your fate."

Chapter 1144: Only Chance

Han Li paid no heed to Immortal Lord Miao Fa as he continued to examine the six mirrors while channeling his cultivation arts to ward off the glacial qi in the surrounding area.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and he raised a hand to summon the Essence Fire Raven.

He then cast his gaze toward the surrounding mirrors to discover that sure enough, they only contained reflections of him, but not of the Essence Fire Raven.

Looks like these mirrors that are formed by ice law powers are unable to manifest fire-attribute entities! Han Li thought to himself as he raised a finger and pointed it at one of the mirrors.

The Essence Fire Raven transformed into a layer of flame that wrapped itself around his arm before shooting out of his fingertip, burrowing deep into the mirror like a fiery drill.

The mirror of ice immediately began to melt, and its surface began to ripple like that of a disturbed lake.

"That Essence Fire Raven is very impressive, but it won't be enough to free you!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa harrumphed coldly as she prepared to descend upon Han Li from above, but right at this moment, the surrounding space abruptly shuddered as a slightly warm breeze blew over from the southeast.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa immediately stopped what she was doing as she cast her gaze into the distant sky, where a fiery red figure was approaching from the southeast atop a fiery cloud.

All of the clouds in her wake had taken on a bright red hue, as if they had been set alight, and the entire freezing air temperatures were beginning to rapidly rise again.

A hint of clear resentment and disdain surfaced in Immortal Lord Miao Fa's eyes at the sight of the approaching figure, which drew to a halt around ten thousand feet away.

"Ah, I wasn't expecting to run into you here, Immortal Lord Miao Fa! I'm pursuing a wanted fugitive on the Immortal Slaying List. Would you happen to have seen him?" Chi Meng asked as she feigned a surprised expression.

"There's only a wanted fugitive of our Nine Origins Temple here, and he's already been detained. If you're searching for a wanted fugitive of the Heavenly Court, then I suggest you go elsewhere," Immortal Lord Miao Fa replied in a cold manner.

"Well, it just so happens to be the case that the two fugitives are one and the same. Now that you've captured him, you can hand him over to me, and I'll inform the Heavenly Court of your contribution to request a reward for your Nine Origins Temple," Chi Meng said with a wide smile.

"I am the one who captured him, so it's only right that I take him back to our Nine Origins Temple for interrogation, and I'll hand him over to you once we've completed our interrogation," Immortal Lord Miao Fa countered in an unyielding manner.

"You're saying you've captured him? Are you sure about that?" Chi Meng asked with a sly grin.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and she noticed that a colony of red fire ants had suddenly burrowed their way out of the ground behind the wall of ice, and they were crawling over the six silver mirrors around Han Li.

The ants left behind trails of scorching heat in their wake that burned deep troughs into the mirrors of ice, and thus, a clash between fire and ice ensued.

The flames on the bodies of the fire ants were rapidly whittled away, and it was often the case that they would only be able to crawl for about an inch before their flames were snuffed out and they were frozen solid.

However, there were simply too many of them for the mirrors of ice to contend with, and collectively, they formed a formidable force to be reckoned with.

Trapped within the encirclement of mirrors, Han Li was unable to see what was happening outside, and he was still attempting to drill through one of the mirrors using the power of the Essence Fire Raven.

Right as his extremities were beginning to grow numb from the infiltration of glacial qi into his body, a dull thud finally rang out as the fiery, silver drill extending out of his fingertip pierced its way fully through the mirror of ice.

Han Li hurriedly threw a punch at the mirror with all his might, and a loud crack rang out as all six mirrors shattered in unison, freeing him from the encirclement.

Immediately thereafter, he was greeted by the sight of countless fiery ants converging toward him from all directions, and he had no idea what was happening, but he certainly wasn't going to linger here as he sprang up into the air to flee.

It was only then that he spotted Immortal Lord Miao Fa swooping down at him from above out of his peripheral vision, and he hurriedly channeled his Reversal True Axis ability to evade her.

Meanwhile, Chi Meng was also flying along in hot pursuit behind Immortal Lord Miao Fa, and there was a wide smile on her face as she called out, "Seeing as you weren't able to capture him, I suppose we'll just have to see which one of us manages to get him!"

As soon as her voice trailed off, tongues of golden flames erupted out of the fiery cloud beneath her, instantly accelerating her drastically through the air so that she was able to overtake Immortal Lord Miao Fa and race along directly beside Han Li.

Somehow, there were suddenly two mid-Great Encompassment cultivators pursuing him at once, and he couldn't help but lament his own ill fortune.

Right at this moment, Chi Meng reached out to make a grabbing motion toward Han Li, and a long, fiery dragon flew out of the palm of her hand before pouncing at him with its cavernous mouth wide open.

As the fiery dragon closed in on Han Li, bursts of scorching heat surged out of its body, causing the surrounding space to shimmer and warp.

Han Li was struck by a sense of asphyxiation, and he felt as if a burst of invisible, obstructive force had suddenly appeared up ahead, forcing him to slow down involuntarily.

Right as he was about to be inundated by the flames surging out of the fiery dragon's mouth, a burst of silver flames rose up from his shoulder before flowing over his entire arm.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, and a huge, fire raven head erupted out of his arm before biting down onto the fiery dragon's head.

The fiery dragon was instantly decapitated, and its headless body recoiled, while its disembodied head began to struggle violently while clasped between the Essence Fire Raven's beak, sending countless bursts of flames spraying in all directions.

Han Li felt as if his entire arm had been set alight, and it was incredibly painful, but he could only grit his teeth and persevere.

Chi Meng's eyes instantly lit up with elation as she exclaimed, "That's an Essence Fire Raven that's devoured Rainbow Fire Pill Sand! I knew I made the right decision to come here!"

She immediately darted closer to Han Li as she spoke, and Han Li instantly felt as if his entire body had been plunged into a giant pot of bubbling oil, while his blood also began to churn violently through his veins as if it had been set alight.

His skin turned bright red, while his eyes turned completely bloodshot, and all of his sudden, his previously stagnant immortal spiritual power began circulating so quickly that he was barely able to contain it.

"A young man like you should be reckless and hot-blooded. Come, let me warm you up even more!" Chi Meng said with a wide smile as she made a hand seal, and Han Li instantly felt the surrounding air temperature rise by tenfold.

At the same time, a ball of radiant, white light emerged from under him, and it contained a projection of a Three-Legged Golden Crow with its wings spread wide and scorching flames surging out of its body.

Embroiled within the flames, Han Li was like a pill in a cauldron, unable to struggle free no matter how vigorously he struggled.

Thankfully, the Essence Fire Raven had formed a fiery, silver outer garment around his entire body. Otherwise, he would've already been close to ashes at this point.

Even so, he was still in a state of excruciating pain from the unbearable heat.

Right at this moment, a clear cry suddenly rang out, and a giant ice phoenix appeared out of thin air before flying toward him, sweeping up gusts of glacial wind as it flapped its wings to propel itself through the air.

The ball of fiery, white light beneath Han Li immediately lashed out in retaliation, releasing a fiery tornado to clash against the ice phoenix.

All of a sudden, a vast cloud of vapor appeared throughout the entire area in a radius of thousands of kilometers, severely impacting visibility while also drastically dropping the nearby air temperature.

"It looks like your Nine Origins Temple insists on opposing our Heavenly Court, Immortal Lord Miao Fa," Chi Meng remarked in a cold voice.

"I had already captured him, yet you broke the rules, so don't blame me for retaliating," Immortal Lord Miao Fa replied in an expressionless manner.

"Fine. In that case, how about we have a battle right here, and the winner gets to take him, while the loser goes back empty-handed. What do you say?" Chi Meng proposed with a smile.

"I was about to propose the exact same thing," Immortal Lord Miao Fa replied.

As the two of them were conversing with each other, the unrest in Han Li's body began to settle down, and much of the scorching heat in the air had abated thanks to the ice phoenix's timely arrival.

Despite this, Han Li didn't dare to relax even for a single instant, and he knew that this was going to be his only chance to escape.

Chapter 1145: Trapped Once Again

Taking advantage of this opportunity, Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and true spirit bloodlines in unison, and a cloud of devilish qi surged out of his body alongside a flash of silver lightning as he transformed into a massive bird with three different heads, namely those of the Lightning Bird, the Heavenly Phoenix, and the Azure Luan Bird.

The three-headed bird was over a thousand feet in size, and it had a pair of azure and crimson wings, as well as a massive tail consisting of seven fiery feathers. Its talons were silver in color and as sharp as blades, and there were arcs of silver lightning flashing over them.

The giant bird spread its wings, and two gusts of fierce, azure wind were released, propelling it up into the air. At the same time, jets of crimson flames erupted out of its tail feathers, while a torrent of silver lightning surged out of its talons.

In the blink of an eye, the giant bird had accelerated to a mind-boggling speed, and after just a few flaps of its wings, it had already vanished into the distant sky.

Chi Meng's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, while Immortal Lord Miao Fa's body began to dissipate into a flurry of snowflakes as she set off in pursuit of Han Li.

"So he really does have some tricks up his sleeve. This is turning out to be much more fun than I expected!" Chi Meng grinned to herself, not looking concerned in the slightest.

Immediately thereafter, she also set off in pursuit of Han Li atop her fiery, red cloud.

Meanwhile, Han Li was fleeing with all his might.

In his current form, his speed wasn't inferior by much compared with using his lighting teleportation array, and he had the advantage of being able to travel continuously, rather than having to stop to conjure up new lightning arrays between bouts of teleportation.

However, it didn't take long before the surrounding air temperature began to plummet again, and a vast cloud of white mist appeared around Han Li.

As soon as Han Li flew into the cloud of white mist, he immediately felt as if he had crashed headfirst into a wall of wind and snow, slowing him down significantly.

Han Li couldn't help but be stunned by the enormous area that Immortal Lord Miao Fa's spirit domain was able to encompass, as well as the power of the structures manifested by the Creation Tier spirit domain, such as the wall of ice from earlier and this fearsome snowstorm.

Clearly, the disparity of a single cultivation rank wasn't an accurate reflection of the vast gap between early and mid-Great Encompassment cultivators.

However, there was no time for Han Li to ponder all of this as he opened all three of his beaks in unison, releasing an azure whirlwind, a pillar of silver lightning, and a plume of crimson flames that fused as one in mid-air to form a vibrant and colorful pillar of light that erupted directly forward.

The pillar of light appeared extremely out of place in the bland, white snowstorm, and it blasted a huge hole that was tens of thousands of kilometers in length through the snowstorm, allowing Han Li to pass through it without any further obstruction.

After passing through the snowstorm, Han Li discovered that what was supposed to have been a summer's day had turned into winter, and that the entire landscape had been encased in ice as far as the eyes could see.

Before Han Li had a chance to even fully take in his surroundings, Immortal Lord Miao Fa's voice suddenly rang out from behind him.

"I'll admit that you have quite a few tricks up your sleeve for a mere High Zenith cultivator, but what are you going to do now?"

As soon as her voice trailed off, a huge shadow began to appear directly ahead of Han Li, one that seemed to connect the heavens to the earth.

Han Li could immediately tell that this was none other than the same wall of ice that had obstructed him earlier, and he immediately channeled his Reversal True Axis to roughly double his own speed.

A layer of glacial qi was spreading down the wall of ice, and in the blink of an eye, it had already spread over half of the wall.

Han Li could only swoop down to fly toward the bottom half of the wall, which still hadn't yet frozen solid.

However, even with his incredible speed, he was unable to outrun the spreading glacial qi, and it looked as if the wall were going to fully freeze solid before he could reach it.

Right at this moment, a burst of silver lightning flashed through the eyes of his Lightning Bird head, and two balls of silver lightning that he had been charging up for quite some time erupted out of his talons to strike the foot of the wall of ice.

An earth-shattering thunderclap rang out as that section of the wall of ice exploded into countless shards of ice, creating a huge hole that Han Li was able to pass through.

Immediately thereafter, he spread his wings again to regain altitude and continued to flee into the distance.

A furious look flashed through Immortal Lord Miao Fa's eyes upon seeing this, and right at this moment, she suddenly noticed that Chi Meng was nowhere to be found.

Even after flying through the wall of ice, Han Li knew that he couldn't grow complacent, and he continued to channel his Reversal True Axis ability, burning through his immortal spiritual power and law powers at an alarming rate.

Thanks to his tireless efforts, he was able to slowly open up a gap between himself and Immortal Lord Miao Fa, but before he even had a chance to catch his breath, a burst of radiant, white light suddenly appeared up ahead, and Chi Meng emerged within it.

The white light was so bright that Han Li reflexively narrowed his eyes against it, and in the next instant, an enormous, semi-transparent dome of light descended from above, crashing down upon him before forcing him to the ground.

Han Li flapped his wings with all his might to dart forward through the air, only to crash into the dome of light, which shuddered violently upon impact.

A dense layer of runes then emerged over its surface, giving off peculiar energy fluctuations as they converged toward Han Li from all directions, rocking his soul violently while forcing him to the ground.

Upon landing on the ground, Han Li reverted back to his human form, and the dome of light around him quickly shrank down to only the size of a house.

Han Li looked around to discover that the dome of light resembled an upside-down bowl, and that its surface was riddled with countless runes.

There were also nine fiery, crimson dragons coiled on top of the dome, and all of them were glowering down at him in a menacing fashion.

Han Li could detect extremely formidable fire law power fluctuations emanating from the nine dragons, and by his estimate, this had to have at least been a fifth tier immortal treasure.

After capturing Han Li using the dome of light, Chi Meng descended out of the sky as she remarked in a disappointed manner, "You're nothing special, after all! All you've done is run like a coward up to this point. How on earth were those idiots from the Golden Origin Immortal Palace wiped out by you? They're a disgrace to our Heavenly Court!"

Han Li paid no heed to her disappointed musings as he activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes to closely examine the immortal treasure, hoping to identify some point of vulnerability that would allow him to escape.

"Just give it up! This Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome is a fourth tier immortal treasure that even a Great Encompassment cultivator would struggle to escape from, let alone a mere High Zenith cultivator like yourself. Just surrender to spare yourself the physical punishment," Chi Meng coaxed.

After inspecting the entire dome, Han Li discovered that he was surrounded by a ring of formidable law powers with no vulnerabilities to be exploited.

Right at this moment, Immortal Lord Miao Fa also arrived on the scene, and her brows furrowed slightly at the sight that she was greeted by.

"You're too late, he's already my prisoner," Chi Meng gloated with a triumphant smile.

"Is that so? But I don't see any shackles around him. If all you've done is trap him, then didn't I already accomplish the same thing earlier?" Immortal Lord Miao Fa objected.

"Clearly, neither of us is going to be able to convince the other, so let's just finish our battle and let the outcome decide who gets to keep him," Chi Meng said.

"Sounds good to me!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa harrumphed coldly as she sprang up into the air.

Chi Meng was just about to set off in pursuit when she suddenly seemed to have recalled something, and she turned to Han Li as she warned, "Don't try any funny business! If you struggle recklessly in my Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome, you could easily end up dead! Unlike Miao Fa, I actually want to keep you alive."

After that, she flew up into the air in pursuit of Immortal Lord Miao Fa, and a burst of tremendous pressure descended from the heavens as both women flew up into the clouds.

Half of the sky was set alight by scorching, red flames, while the other half of the sky had been devoured by a glacial snowstorm, but Han Li had no time to appreciate the spectacle.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he removed his Profound Heavenly Gourd from his waist, then tipped it over so that its opening was aimed at a point where the underside of the dome was in contact with the ground.

Chapter 1146: Vial Spirit to the Rescue

Han Li took a deep breath, then slammed a hand into the underside of the gourd, and a burst of rumbling instantly rang out from within. A vortex of azure light emerged from the mouth of the gourd, and a thread of dark green light shot out from within.

A resounding boom rang out as a beam of light that was imbued with the laws of destruction struck the Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome before exploding into a small, green cloud.

The dome shuddered violently, but it remained completely unscathed, and to make matters even worse, the five out of the nine dragons above the dome suddenly seemed to have sprung to life, opening their cavernous mouths to blast forth torrents of scorching flames toward the dome beneath them.

The entire space within the dome was instantly inundated by five bursts of viscous flames, and as soon as the flames came into contact with Han Li's body, he was struck by an unprecedented sense of agony that caused a heart-wrenching howl to escape from his lips.

The Essence Fire Raven instantly flew out of his body of its own accord, forming a fiery, silver outer garment around him to keep the viscous flames at bay.

Even so, waves of indescribable heat continued to infiltrate his body, inflicting upon him intense agony.

While protecting Han Li, the Essence Fire Raven opened its beak to release a torrent of silver flames that resisted the flames that continued to surge down from above, and the clashing silver and crimson flames formed a two-colored fiery barrier above Han Li's head.

Han Li's heart sank even further upon seeing this. In the past, whenever the Essence Fire Raven had encountered fire-attribute attacks, it had always chosen to devour them.

However, on this occasion, it was doing the exact opposite, and Han Li hurriedly asked it why this was the case through their spiritual connection.

In response, the Essence Fire Raven informed him that these flames were imbued wit ha special type of fire law powers, thereby making it impossible to devour. On top of that, it was also very clear that the Essence Fire Raven was being dominated by these crimson flames.

To compound Han Li's woes even further, the remaining four fiery dragons seemed to have also been enraged by the Essence Fire Raven's resistance, and they began blasting flames down into the dome as well.

The nine bursts of crimson flames formed an inescapable barrage that inundated Han Li from all directions, and the Essence Fire Raven was forced to give up its resistance as it focused solely on protecting Han Li.

However, the collective power of all nine dragons was far more formidable than just the five from before, and even the Essence Fire Raven was struggling to withstand the assault.

What was even more concerning was that the Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome seemed to also possess the ability to absorb all fire-attribute power, so a great deal of the Essence Fire Raven's power was being sucked into the dome.

Of course, Han Li wasn't just going to accept his fate, and he was attacking the dome with all his might with his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, but the dome simply refused to budge.

As time passed, the Essence Fire Raven's silver flames had been whittled down significantly, but the Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome was only growing more and more powerful, and the fiery assault was quickly becoming too much for Han Li to bear.

Right at this moment, the Essence Fire Raven suddenly opened its mouth to release a white bead, and it hovered above Han Li like a lamp while giving off rays of dazzling, white light.

Enhanced by these rays of white light, the silver flames around the Essence Fire Raven's body instantly reared up to force back the oncoming crimson flames.

Han Li was immediately able to identify the white bead as the fire-attribute immortal treasure that he had obtained from the Eon Pagoda. He had thought that it had already been refined and absorbed by the Essence Fire Raven, but that was clearly not the case.

However, the resistance didn't last long before the white bead was also forced downward by the crimson flames, and the nine fiery dragons had even personally made their way into the dome to surround the white bead in a menacing fashion.

Much of the bead's power had already been exhausted by the Five-Elemental Great Annihilation Array, and after having so much of its remaining power absorbed by the Essence Fire Raven, it was nowhere near powerful enough to contend with the Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome.

At the same time, all of the crimson flames within the entire domain abruptly converged around Han Li to form a fiery, crimson cocoon, as if it had been compressed by some type of powerful force.

The temperature inside the fiery cocoon reached an extremely inhospitable level, and Han Li's skin began to crack open like a dry lakebed.

The Essence Fire Raven immediately sprang into action upon seeing this, and the rainbow flames on its head brightened significantly, following which two of them, namely the crimson and orange flames, rose up from its head before fusing into the white bead above.

A white cocoon of flames took shape around the bead to keep the crimson flames at bay, finally allowing Han Li some breathing room.

The Essence Fire Raven had sacrificed two of its Rainbow Fire Pill Sand flames to save him, and a hint of guilt welled up in his heart upon seeing this, but he still didn't know how to get himself out of this predicament.

Right at this moment, a furious voice suddenly rang out in front of his chest.

"Are you an idiot? If you can't beat them, then just run! I can't believe you're stuck here when you're capable of transmigration at will!"

"Who's there?" Han Li asked in an alarmed manner.

The voice was rather indistinct, and it was unclear where it had come from, but it had struck Han Li as rather familiar.

All of a sudden, a look of realization appeared on his face, and he hurriedly reached down the front of his own robe to fish out the Heaven Controlling Vial.

The vial appeared no different from normal, but right at this moment, a pair of beady, pea-sized, black eyes suddenly appeared on its surface, and they were looking up at Han Li with a very humanized look of anger.

"Were you the one who spoke just now, Senior Vial Spirit?" Han Li hurriedly asked.

"Who else could it have been but me? I can't believe you've been backed into a corner by a Great Encompassment cultivator and a mere fourth tier immortal treasure! You're an utter disgrace!" the vial spirit reprimanded.

"I did consider making an escape using transmigration, but if I flee from here, won't the Heaven Controlling Vial be left behind and fall into the hands of others?" Han Li asked.

"Is the Heaven Controlling Vial more important than your life?" the vial spirit asked.

"My life is important, but the Heaven Controlling Vial has been with me ever since the beginning of my cultivation journey, so it's just as important to me. Besides, even if I can temporarily get away, I'll eventually have to return here anyway, so it makes no difference," Han Li replied.

The vial spirit seemed to be quite pleased with this answer, and it said, "It looks like I made the right decision to come and save you. During your past transmigrations, the Heaven Controlling Vial is left without an owner, so it remains where you were, serving as a space-time anchor for your return. However, I can make it so that the Heaven Controlling Vial transmigrates with you, and with no anchor left behind, you won't return to this place."

"That's fantastic!" Han Li said as an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

"Don't celebrate too soon now! I can do this for you, but it'll cost you. Taking the vial into the river of time will cost you thirty time law threads, and that's permanent, as in they'll be gone and unrecoverable," the vial spirit said.

Time law threads were very difficult to come by, so sacrificing thirty of them at once was certainly a painful decision to make, but given the dire situation that Han Li was in, he really had no choice in the matter.

"Please tell me what I need to do, Senior," he implored.

"Just conjure up the wall of light and leave the rest to me," the vial spirit replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then began channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and his five time-attribute law treasures appeared around him amid a burst of time law power fluctuations.

The time law threads around the five treasures then intertwined with one another to form the ring of time, and all of the Time Dao Runes on the five law treasures flew out before landing upon the golden ring, producing incredibly formidable bursts of time law power fluctuations.

Upon detecting these time law power fluctuations, Immortal Lord Miao Fa and Chi Meng instantly realized that something was wrong, and they hurriedly called a temporary truce before descending back down to the ground.

At this moment, there was a ball of dark green light within the Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome that was glowing as radiantly as the sun, and the space around the ball of light was rippling incessantly.

Immediately thereafter, a huge wall of translucent light appeared, and Han Li was standing before it.

He withdrew the Essence Fire Raven into his body while gritting his teeth against the oncoming crimson flames, then took a glance back at Immortal Lord Miao Fa and Chi Meng before flying straight into the wall of translucent light.

The two women could only look on as Han Li vanished into the wall of light without a trace.

Chapter 1147: Return to the True Mantra Sect

As Immortal Lord Miao Fa stormed onto the scene, an ecstatic look suddenly appeared on her face as she spotted something within the shrinking ball of green light.

It's the Heaven Controlling Vial!

She immediately accelerated, swooping downward as quickly as she could, but right at this moment, a golden ring emerged within the ball of green light, and thirty time law threads split off from it before disintegrating into a cloud of translucent powder that flew into the green light.

The green light instantly shrank down to form a small, green vial, which vanished into the wall of the translucent light along with the golden ring.

"No!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa roared in a furious voice as the Heaven Controlling Vial slipped away right before her eyes.

Chi Meng withdrew the Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome with a dark expression, but before the two of them had a chance to approach the translucent wall of light, it had already vanished into thin air, leaving only a burst of faint time law power fluctuations in its wake.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa was barely able to contain her own fury as she turned to glower at Chi Meng.

If it wasn't for Chi Meng's meddling, she would've already returned to the Nine Origins Temple with Han Li and the Heaven Controlling Vial, and that would've been the biggest accomplishment anyone in the temple had made in the past tens of millions of years.

Chi Meng's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of Immortal Lord Miao Fa's enraged expression, and she said, "The target is already gone, so there's no point in continuing this senseless battle..."

Before she had a chance to finish, a volley of bone-chilling ice arrows had already come hurtling toward her.

A cold look flashed through Chi Meng's face upon seeing this, and she sprang directly toward Immortal Lord Miao Fa as she harrumphed, "Fine! I tried to settle this peacefully, but you clearly insist on a fight!"

Thus, their battle recommenced, while Lan Yan and Immortal Lord Miao Fa's maidservants were all watching from tens of thousands of kilometers away, with none of them daring to approach the scene.

I wonder how Fellow Daoist Han is doing...

As soon as this thought sprang up in Lan Yan's mind, she was immediately struck by a pang of guilt toward her sect, and she could only heave a forlorn, internal sigh.

......

Meanwhile, Han Li was already beside the vast river of time.

Countless water-droplet-shaped balls of light were flowing through the river, stretching as far as the eyes could see.

Right at this moment, two streaks of light, one golden and one green, sped toward him from afar.

Within the streak of golden light was a golden ring that slid itself onto his finger, while the ball of green light landed in his grasp before transforming into the Heaven Controlling Vial.

"What are you just standing here for? Now that you've brought the Heaven Controlling Vial into this place, your Time Dao Runes will be expended far faster than normal, so hurry and choose a destination for your transmigration," the vial spirit urged.

With no opportunity to plan in advance, Han Li was a little hesitant, unsure of where to go.

After some thought, he suddenly recalled that there were some questions that he had about the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, as well as his recent, failed breakthrough.

Seeing as he was able to physically transmigrate this time, was this not a perfect opportunity to make a trip to the True Mantra Sect to visit Patriarch Miro?

"Senior Vial Spirit, would you be able to take me back to the True Mantra Sect prior to its destruction?" Han Li asked.

"Of course, but you'll have to expend even more time law threads in order to take the Heaven Controlling Vial with you," the vial spirit replied.

"I still need to sacrifice more law threads?" Han Li asked with a pained expression.

The loss of thirty time law threads was already a very steep price to pay, and he certainly didn't want to have to sacrifice any more.

"It depends on the time period that you wish to transmigrate to. The further away it is from the present, the more time law powers must be expended. If you wish to return to the True Mantra Sect prior to its destruction, that's going to cost you at least twenty more time law threads," the vial spirit explained.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li made up his mind and decided, "Alright, I'll go there."

"Hold on a second," the vial spirit said, and as soon as its voice trailed off, twenty time law threads split off from the golden ring on Han Li's finger, then disintegrated into a cloud of translucent dust that vanished into the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Layers of green ripples began to emanate from the Heaven Controlling Vial, and it didn't take long before a particular ball of light came drifting toward Han Li from the river of time.

"This is the one you want," the vial spirit said, and Han Li immediately extended a tendril of spiritual sense toward the ball of light upon hearing this.

However, before he was even able to catch a clear glimpse of the scene contained within the ball of light, it abruptly released a burst of tremendous suction force that drew him in in the blink of an eye, and his vision instantly turned to black as his consciousness faded away.

......

After an indeterminate period of time, Han Li's eyes sprang open, and he found himself standing in an unremarkable room.

The room wasn't very large, and it only had two windows, while the furnishings were also quite bare and simple. There was a pine wood set of table and chairs situated near one of the windows, while the other half of the room was taken up by three beds with neatly folded blankets on top of them.

Hanging on the wall directly across from the beds was a portrait of none other than Patriarch Miro.

This seemed to be a room shared by several True Mantra Sect disciples, and to Han Li's relief, there didn't appear to be any danger afoot.

A golden ring that was riddled with over one thousand six hundred Time Dao Runes was hovering above his head, and the Heaven Controlling Vial was hovering at its center.

However, the vial spirit had disappeared, and the vial itself was also looking rather blurry, perhaps due to the impact of the golden ring.

Han Li made his way out of the room to discover a small courtyard outside, and there appeared to be hundreds of similar courtyards nearby.

These courtyards had all been constructed along a huge, white mountain, and standing beside these courtyards was a series of white jade palaces that stretched as far as the eyes could see.

There were also some mountains hovering in mid-air that were laden with palaces as well.

Having already come to this place once through spiritual transmigration, Han Li knew that this was the True Mantra Sect.

However, the last time that he was here, the sect was being attacked by the Heavenly Court, and it was already in a severely war-torn state, whereas at this point in time, it was still as pristine and tidy as ever.

White-robed True Mantra Sect disciples were flying through the sky above, and Han Li hurriedly concealed himself in order to avoid detection, then carefully released his spiritual sense to scour the surrounding area.

Moments later, an elated look appeared on his face as he flew toward the summit of the giant, white mountain, while simultaneously channeling his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique to conceal his own aura.

Before long, he had already arrived in front of a two-story pavilion on the mountain summit, and beside the pavilion stood a stone plaque that read "Merit Pavilion".

There was barely anyone here, and an elderly man was seated at the entrance of the pavilion, seemingly acting as a supervisor of sorts.

The man was a mid-High Zenith cultivator, and upon Han Li's arrival, he seemed to have detected something as his eyes abruptly sprang open.

However, a perplexed look then appeared on his face as he discovered that there was nothing to be seen.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he pointed a finger at the elderly man, and several translucent chains shot out of his fingertip before racing toward the man's head.

As soon as those chains left Han Li's body, he was immediately revealed, and the elderly man's expression changed drastically as he sprang to his feet while summoning a white badge in an attempt to activate the restrictions on the Merit Pavilion behind him.

However, the translucent chains were far too fast, and they had already vanished into his glabella before he had a chance to react.

The elderly man was instantly immobilized, locked in a strange, half-seated, half-standing posture.

After immobilizing the elderly man, Han Li took a moment to inspect his surroundings, and only after verifying that no one had detected what he had just done did he allow himself an internal sigh of relief.

He took a white badge from the elderly man, and after inspecting it momentarily with his spiritual sense, he immediately understood how it worked.

He strode over to the Merit Pavilion, then swept the badge through the air, releasing a burst of white light that vanished into the doors of the pavilion.

A translucent, white light barrier instantly appeared over the doors, with countless runes flashing over its surface.

Han Li released another streak of white light using the badge, and this time, the runes on the light barrier quickly receded, following which the light barrier itself vanished as the doors of the pavilion slowly swung open.

A faint smile appeared on his face, and he was just about to step inside the pavilion when he suddenly stopped in his tracks, then pointed a finger at the elderly man.

Five thin strands of black light shot out of his fingertip before vanishing into the elderly man's body, and his wooden expression instantly became much more natural as he sat back down again.

This was a puppetry secret technique that he had learned from Daoist Xie during his time in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, and he was using it to control the elderly man to make him appear more natural so that he didn't draw any attention to himself.

After that, Han Li made his way into the pavilion before closing the doors, and a white light barrier instantly reappeared over their surface.

Chapter 1148: A Familiar Scene

Han Li cast his gaze into the pavilion to discover that the first floor wasn't all that spacious, and it was filled with around twenty to thirty antiquated wooden bookshelves, all of which were laden with books, jade slips, and other types of scriptures that were clearly all cultivation arts and secret techniques.

Just like the doors of the pavilion, these scriptures were also enshrouded in a white light barrier.

Just as Han Li had guessed, this was the True Mantra Sect's scripture library.

This was a rare opportunity to return to the True Mantra Sect, and he didn't want to squander it.

His fate seemed to have been somehow intertwined with the True Mantra Sect, and he had frequently explored different avenues to learn more about the sect's history. The more he learned, the more astonished he became.

Even though the True Mantra Sect was situated in the Black Soil Immortal Region, which was not a very large immortal region, it was a sect of a very lofty status in the True Immortal Realm due to its expertise in the laws of time and of course, Patriarch Miro.

He had already expended fifty time law threads to get here. While it was true that he had come here in order to flee from Immortal Lord Miao Fa and Chi Meng, now that he was here, he fully intended to take full advantage of this opportunity.

He had always been cultivating the laws of time on his own, and even though he was able to make rapid progress in the endeavor, there were many gaps in his knowledge that he wanted to fill, so he was eager to find some journals containing cultivation insights from some powerful True Mantra Sect cultivators.

The laws of time were extremely difficult to comprehend and master, but they were also an integral part to the very fabric that this realm was woven from.

Nothing could escape from the effects of time, and every single living being seemed to be able to come into contact with it, but was unable to truly grasp it. It was like a reflection in a pond of water, something that could only be seen, but not grasped.

Hence, regardless of whether someone had made much progress in their cultivation of the laws of time, written records of their cultivation experiences and insights could perhaps be of some help to Han Li.

With that in mind, he began to quickly make his way through the bookshelves, stopping occasionally to use the white badge in his hand to withdraw the restrictions around the bookshelves in order to access the scriptures inside. However, the more he read, the less enthused he became.

The scriptures on these bookshelves were all quite profound, but they were all cultivation arts and secret techniques aimed at Golden Immortals and even True Immortals. Some of them contained some cultivation insights, but all of those sections were very brief and vague, providing no benefit to Han Li.

It looks like all of the scriptures here are of a rather lowly caliber. The higher grade scriptures must be kept somewhere more secretive.

With that in mind, Han Li made his way up to the second floor of the pavilion.

There were only around a dozen bookshelves on the second floor, and they were also laden with scriptures.

Time was of the essence, so Han Li immediately began reading through the scriptures.

The scriptures here were indeed of a higher level than the ones on the first floor, but not by much, and they weren't of much use to him.

It didn't take long before Han Li read through all of these scriptures in futility, and he heaved a forlorn sigh before turning to depart.

At this point, a good chunk of the Time Dao Runes on the golden ring had already been snuffed out, so he couldn't afford to waste any more time here.

All of a sudden, he stopped in his tracks and cast his gaze toward a nearby bookshelf that was placed against a wall.

He had only hurriedly examined the scriptures on the bookshelves earlier, so he had failed to notice that the positioning of this bookshelf was a little strange in that it seemed to have been intentionally moved around a foot out of line with the other bookshelves.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he pushed the bookshelf back, then swept his spiritual sense over the surrounding area, upon which an elated look suddenly appeared on his face.

He placed a hand against the section of the wall that had previously been blocked by the bookshelf, and a loud click rang out as the wall caved inward to reveal an opening, inside of which was a palm-sized, golden jade box.

He was just about to open the box when a layer of golden light appeared over its surface to repel his hand.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, then reached out with both hands for the jade box, while a layer of golden light surfaced over each of his hands.

The jade box released another layer of golden light to contend against the golden light emanating from Han Li's hands, but it was quickly overwhelmed and torn apart, following which the jade box sprang open to reveal a golden jade slip inside.

Han Li picked up the jade slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it to discover that it contained a secret technique called the "Immortal Golden Cloud".

According to the jade slip, this was a defensive secret technique that used time law powers as a foundation.

On top of that, this wasn't just any defensive ability. Instead, it was proclaimed to be the True Mantra Sect's premium defensive secret technique.

However, the prerequisites that had to be fulfilled in order to cultivate this ability were extremely stringent. Firstly, one had to possess tremendous time law powers and a very high understanding of the laws of time. Otherwise, they wouldn't be able to bear the overwhelming power of the Immortal Golden Cloud, nor would they be able to comprehend the complexities of the secret technique.

In addition to that, the cultivator had to possess at least three hundred time law threads, and only then would they have sufficient time law powers to support the ability.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

The Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra was a time-attribute cultivation art of the highest caliber, and he had already developed a very deep understanding of the laws of time, but the problem was naturally the requirement of three hundred time law threads.

At the moment, he only had around a hundred and fifty time law threads left, which fulfilled only half of the minimum requirement.

Even so, he was still very pleased to have found this secret technique.

He stowed the jade slip and the golden box away, then returned the wall and the bookshelf to their original state so no one would notice that anything was amiss.

After doing all of that, Han Li made his way downstairs, yet right as he was about to exit the pavilion, a streak of golden light came flying over from afar, then descended outside the Merit Pavilion to reveal an imposing man who was at the mid-High Zenith Stage.

"Your Merit Pavilion is still as deserted as ever, Fellow Daoist Jiang," the man chuckled.

Han Li hurriedly channeled his puppetry secret technique to control the elderly man, who looked up at the visitor as he replied in an indifferent manner, "Barely anyone ever comes here anyway."

The man didn't seem to have noticed anything amiss about the elderly man, and he lowered his voice as he said, "I don't mean to make a joke at your expense, Fellow Daoist Jiang. Our sect is receiving more and more pressure from the Heavenly Court, and my Heavenly Star Palace has also been largely deserted of late.

“It may be a rather wearisome task, overseeing these places for ten thousand years, but at the very least, we're in a much better situation than those elders who were sent on missions out of the sect. I've heard that many of them have already met their demise."

To Han Li's relief, it appeared that the two of them were on good terms with each other, and under his control, the elderly man asked, "Can I help you with something?"

"I heard that our patriarch is going to be giving a lecture on the Sun View Peak, and I came here to invite you to attend the lecture with me," the man replied with a smile, and Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this.

There was a very good chance that this patriarch in question was Patriarch Miro, who was also a cultivator of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra. There was no guarantee that he would specifically speak about the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra during his lecture, but the cultivation insights that he divulged had to be related to the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, so this lecture was not to be missed.

With that in mind, a hint of excitement welled up in his heart, and the elderly man replied at his behest, "Thank you for the kind offer, Fellow Daoist Chen, but I still have some matters to attend to right now, so I'll have to go a little later."

The man faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response.

"In that case, I'll be going ahead on my own. You should also come as soon as you can, Fellow Daoist Jiang. We may be using different cultivation arts from our patriarch, but I'm sure his cultivation insights will still be invaluable for us to hear."

The man then promptly departed, flying away as a streak of golden light.

The doors of the Merit Pavilion swung open, and Han Li emerged from within, then made a beckoning motion, upon which the elderly man stood up and made his way into the pavilion.

He then flicked a finger through the air, sending a strand of translucent light flying into the elderly man's glabella, and he shuddered violently before falling to the ground in an unconscious state.

Han Li tossed the white badge onto the floor beside the elderly man, then closed the doors of the pavilion behind him.

The elderly man was going to be unconscious for at least four or five days, so he wouldn't be able to interfere with anything that Han Li did from here onward.

From there, Han Li set off in the same direction that the man from earlier had departed in, and it didn't take long before he arrived near a lush mountain that was teeming with trees and riddled with strange-looking rocks.

This was not an unfamiliar mountain to Han Li. Instead, he had already seen it three times, and the first of those occasions was when he first used the Heaven Controlling Vial to witness Patriarch Miro's lecture on the mountain summit.

He had also been to this mountain during his time in the True Mantra Sect ruins, and on this day, he found himself here once again.

The mountain extended all the way up into the clouds, making it impossible to see its summit, and there was a long stone staircase leading all the way from the summit to the foot of the mountain.

At this moment, the staircase was packed with seated True Mantra Sect disciples, all of whom were listening intently to the lecture, which had already commenced.

Despite the fact that he was all the up on the mountain summit, Patriarch Miro's voice was clearly audible to everyone, and every single syllable that he enunciated had a profound and ethereal quality to it.

The nearby world's origin qi was trembling incessantly in the face of Patriarch Miro's voice, and at this moment, there were countless streaks of light flashing through the air, transforming into all types of phenomena, including gusts of fierce wind, vortexes of scorching fire, and storms of glacial ice.

After observing these phenomena for a moment, Han Li began to fly his way up toward the mountain summit in secret.

However, instead of flying all the way to the mountain summit, he sat down partway up the mountain for fear that Patriarch Miro would notice him if he were to get any closer.

From here, he could already make out the scene on the mountain summit. Patriarch Miro was seated at the center, surrounded by his five disciples, and standing upright on its hindlegs beside Mu Yan was a fat rat that was also looking at Patriarch Miro.

Chapter 1149: Seventh Disciple

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this, but he didn't pay much heed to it as he focused his attention on the lecture.

As he listened, his expression gradually became more and more focused, until a look of utter enrapturement appeared on his face.

At the moment, Patriarch Miro wasn't specifically talking about the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, but Han Li could tell that every single word that he spoke was closely related to the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

The cultivation art for the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra flowed through Han Li's mind as he cross-compared it with the lecture that was currently being delivered, and he was able to gain a deeper understanding of the cultivation art, striking him with a sense of enlightenment where there had previously been some confusion.

Close to a day flew by in the blink of an eye.

Right at this moment, Patriarch Miro's voice abruptly cut off, and Han Li was instantly snapped out of his enraptured state.

He cast his gaze toward the mountain summit to discover that Mu Yan had raised a question, and he couldn't help but feel envious of Mu Yan for having someone to answer his questions.

After listening to Patriarch Miro's lecture, he had gained a much deeper understanding of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, but some new questions pertaining to the cultivation art had also arisen in his mind.

After answering Mu Yan's question, Patriarch Miro resumed his lecture, and Han Li hurriedly began listening again.

Some time later, Patriarch Miro suddenly stopped once again as he cast a surprised gaze toward a certain spot in the air.

His disciples were immediately snapped out of their enraptured state, and Mu Yan instantly sprang to his feet with a furious expression as he yelled, "Who's there?"

A burst of invisible force surged out from between Patriarch Miro's lips to strike that spot in the air, and the space there was shattered, following which the invisible force seeped deep into the broken space, forming a passageway that led to some unknown destination.

A faint crack then rang out from deep within the spatial passageway, as if something had been shattered.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he discovered that this was the scene where Patriarch Miro had caught him eavesdropping on his lecture all those years ago.

Patriarch Miro swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light, which swept over the shattered space to smooth it over again.

"It's alright, there's no need to be alarmed," he said in a calm manner, and his disciples sat back down again.

"Who was spying on us just now, Master? Was it someone from the Heavenly Court?" Qi Mozi asked with tightly furrowed brows.

Patriarch Miro shook his head and offered no response, but he turned to take a glance at a spot partway up the mountain precisely where Han Li was seated.

At the moment, Han Li had concealed himself using his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique, and it was only a casual glance, but he knew that Patriarch Miro had already seen him.

Should I run? Han Li thought to himself as he prepared to flee the scene, but Patriarch Miro had already withdrawn his gaze, paying no further heed to Han Li as he resumed his lecture once again.

After a brief moment of hesitation, Han Li decided to remain where he was.

He wasn't aware of Patriarch Miro's true power, but just that fleeting glance alone told him that Patriarch Miro was definitely far more powerful than even the likes of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, so there was no way that he would be able to get away if Patriarch Miro wanted to capture him.

Hence, he may as well stay and listen to the lecture. Furthermore, he was cultivating the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, which made him half a True Mantra Sect disciple, so even if Patriarch Miro were to capture him, he should have no intentions of harming him.

With that in mind, Han Li felt much more reassured, and he sat down again to continue listening to the lecture.

The lecture continued for another half a day before Patriarch Miro declared its conclusion.

All of the disciples of the True Mantra Sect bowed respectfully to him before departing, and before long, he was the only one left on the mountain summit.

"You can come out now," Patriarch Miro said in a calm manner, and Han Li appeared behind him amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

"I pay my respects to Senior Miro," Han Li greeted as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

Patriarch Miro sized up Han Li for a moment, following which a warm smile appeared on his face as he murmured to himself, "Not bad at all!"

"I came here by chance and was enraptured by your lecture, so I concealed myself to listen in secret. I hope you'll forgive me, Senior Miro," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

"It's fine. You've cultivated the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and that makes you a disciple of my True Mantra Sect, so why can't you listen to my lecture?" Patriarch Miro asked with a benevolent smile.

Han Li wasn't surprised that Patriarch Miro was able to identify the cultivation art that he was using, and he was quite relieved to see that Patriarch Miro didn't seem to harbor any enmity toward him.

"You were the one spying on me earlier as well, weren't you? You may be here in the present, but you're not from the present. It's incredible to think that there's a treasure in this world capable of facilitating travel through space and time," Patriarch Miro mused.

Han Li was stunned that Patriarch Miro was able to see through everything so easily, and he offered no response.

The Heaven Controlling Vial was his biggest secret, so he naturally wasn't going to tell Patriarch Miro about it.

Patriarch Miro seemed to have seen through his concerns, and he reassured, "Don't worry, I have no intention of taking your treasure. It's a very remarkable treasure that you have, so make sure to keep it safe."

An awkward look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, but thankfully, Patriarch Miro didn't dwell on the subject.

A benevolent look appeared in his eyes as he asked, "What's your name?"

"Han Li," Han Li replied after a brief hesitation.

"Han Li, are you willing to become my disciple?" Patriarch Miro asked.

Han Li was completely rooted to the spot by this sudden and unexpected turn that the conversation had taken.

"I've always been very careful when it comes to taking disciples, and up to this point, I only have six, but a wise and powerful man once prophesied that I'll have a total of seven disciples in my lifetime, and that my final disciple will be the one to inherit my teachings. You are the only one in this world aside from myself to have successfully cultivated the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, so you must be this prophesied disciple," Patriarch Miro explained.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Patriarch Miro was undoubtedly an extremely powerful cultivator, and there was some connection between the two of them as well, but those factors on their own weren't enough to convince him to accept Patriarch Miro as his master.

Patriarch Miro seemed to have gleaned his thoughts, and he smiled as he said, "You don't have to make a decision right away. How about I take you on a tour of our True Mantra Sect?"

"I would be honored, Senior," Han Li replied with a nod.

With that, Patriarch Miro swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of golden light that transformed into a wide, golden path, one that seemed to stretch on infinitely into the distance.

He then beckoned for Han Li to step onto the path, and Han Li duly obliged.

As soon as he set foot onto the golden path, a burst of peculiar time law powers instantly rose up from beneath his feet to envelop his entire body, and scenery around him instantly began to transform rapidly while revolving around him, as if he had just stepped into a space-time passageway.

Before he had a chance to look closer at the transforming scenery, he found himself in a golden space, and he looked up into the sky with an astonished look on his face.

Ever since he began integrating his true spirit bloodlines with the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, his understanding of his true spirit bloodlines had become deeper and deeper over time.

The Heavenly Phoenix bloodline was the first true spirit bloodline that he had ever attained, and thanks to his in-depth understanding of the bloodline, he had become far more sensitive to spatial power.

Hence, he could sense that this golden space was already very far away from Sun View Peak, far beyond the maximal distance that could be traveled using his lightning teleportation array.

What was even more astonishing to him was that Patriarch Miro had been able to bring them here without producing any detectable spatial fluctuations.

"This is our True Mantra Sect's Ubiquitous Path ability, and it can be used to move space. However, it draws upon the power of time as opposed to spatial power," Patriarch Miro explained upon seeing Han Li's surprised expression, and he was even more stunned upon hearing this.

All of the major cities and sects in the True Immortal Realm generally had spatial restrictions to prevent infiltration using spatial teleportation abilities, but if he could master this ability, then he would be able to easily bypass those restrictions.

"I didn't think that such an ability could be derived from time law powers," Han Li mused with an impressed expression.

"Our True Mantra Sect has been studying the laws of time for countless years, and during that time, countless time-derived abilities have been created, with the Ubiquitous Path being only one of them. If you're interested in such abilities, then come with me," Patriarch Miro said with a smile, then released a burst of golden light to sweep up Han Li before flying onward.

Han Li allowed himself to be carried along by Patriarch Miro as he inspected the surrounding golden space.

This seemed to be a secret area similar to the Tai Sui Immortal Manor, and there the landscape down below was dotted with enormous buildings that were ten times more imposing and majestic than all of the other buildings that Han Li had seen in the True Mantra Sect thus far.

Many True Mantra Sect disciples were cultivating here, as if this were another True Mantra Sect.

"This is the True Mantra Profound Domain, a domain that was created by my predecessors, and it's the true foundation of our True Mantra Sect," Patriarch Miro introduced with a hint of pride in his voice.

Han Li nodded in response, and he began carefully inspecting the surrounding space once again when a look of surprise suddenly appeared on his face.

What he had failed to notice prior to this was that there was a burst of time law power fluctuations permeating throughout this entire space, just like in the Eon Pagoda.

The difference was that the time law powers in the Eon Pagoda existed to weaken those who were imprisoned inside, while the time law power fluctuations here had no effect other than to accelerate the flow of time in this place.

Time in this area passed roughly 50% faster than it did outside, and as he continued onward with Patriarch Miro, the flow of time only accelerated further and further.

Before long, the flow of time had accelerated to ten times the rate of the outside world, and the further Han Li advanced, the more astonished he became.

Chapter 1150: Foundation of the True Mantra Sect

Patriarch Miro was able to fly countless times faster than Han Li, and it didn't take long before he had covered tens of millions of kilometers.

However, the golden space was so enormous that there was still no end in sight.

After flying onward for a while longer, Patriarch Miro suddenly descended in front of a giant, golden mountain down below.

The mountain reached all the way up into the clouds, obscuring half of the entire sky up ahead, as if it were a gargantuan, golden beast that was resting on its haunches.

The entire mountain was giving off rays of golden light, and every single rock was giving off time law power fluctuations, which culminated into an all-encompassing wave that filled the entire area.

Before Han Li even had a chance to find some stable footing, a burst of indescribable law power fluctuations immediately surged toward him, causing him to stumble back a few steps before steadying himself.

He then cast an astonished gaze toward the golden mountain up ahead as he exclaimed, "Are those rocks all Xumi Star Rocks?"

As a cultivator of the laws of time, he was well-versed in all materials that contained time law powers, so he was able to determine that this mountain was entirely formed by a time-attribute material called the Xumi Star Rock.

Xumi Star Rocks were an extremely precious type of time-attribute material that was said to arise in the boundless space beyond the True Immortal Realm, and just a small piece of the material could fetch a very high price, let alone an entire, giant mountain's worth.

"This Golden Xumi Mountain was secured from beyond the True Immortal Realm by the eleventh master of the True Mantra Sect, Daoist Master Tian Shi, and it's the center of the True Mantra Profound Domain," Patriarch Miro introduced.

"As expected of a sect that's able to contend with the Heavenly Court," Han Li praised in a heartfelt manner.

At this point, the flow of time had already accelerated to hundreds of times faster than the outside world.

Han Li couldn't help but wonder how the True Mantra Sect had been able to accomplish this. If he could replicate these conditions, then he would essentially have hundreds of times more time to cultivate than everyone else, and that was truly a very alluring prospect.

"Come with me," Patriarch Miro said with a smile as he proceeded onward.

There was only a single building in the area, namely a giant palace situated at the foot of the golden mountain. The palace was also entirely constructed from Xumi Star Rocks, and it was extremely resplendent and majestic, but there were no plaques or anything similar at the entrance, so it was unclear what was inside.

The palace gates were tightly shut, and there was a 卍 symbol on each gate. [1]

Patriarch Miro strode over to the palace, and a layer of golden light appeared over the palms of his hands as he pressed them against the pair of 卍 symbols.

The palace gates instantly began to glow with dazzling, golden radiance, and four golden deity projections emerged within it.

The first deity was an imposing, square-faced man in a suit of golden armor, wielding a giant ax in one hand and a huge shield in the other.

The second deity had a golden beak in the place of a mouth and eight golden wings on their back. There was also a crystalline, golden crow on their head, what was most peculiar of all was that they had three legs.

The third deity was an adorable and chubby little girl with a pair of short and stubby wings on her back and a bright halo above her head. She was holding a small, golden bow that was nocked with an arrow with a heart-shaped tip, as if it were a children's toy.

The final deity was a beautiful woman with six arms that were holding a selection of musical instruments, namely a guqin, a bianzhong, a vertical flute, a pipa, a bell, and a war drum, all of which were producing pleasant music.

As soon as the four deities appeared, they immediately turned to Patriarch Miro with wary and forbidding looks on their faces.

Patriarch Miro began to chant an incantation, and countless golden runes surged out of his mouth before fusing into the bodies of the four deities.

Only then did the enmity in their eyes gradually recede, and they backed away to stand on either side of the gates, which slowly swung open.

Patriarch Miro gestured for Han Li to come with him, then led the way into the palace, and Han Li duly obliged.

Beyond the palace gates was a spacious hall that was thousands of feet in size. There were dense, golden patterns engraved onto the ground at the center of the hall, forming an extremely massive and complex array.

Bright, golden light and golden runes were emanating from all parts of the array, but they were all restricted within the array, with none of them escaping beyond the array's boundaries.

Two stone pillars were standing beside the array, one white and one golden, and these two pillars had also been forged from Xumi Star Rocks.

The golden pillar was inseparably connected to the ground and riddled with flame-shaped golden runes, while the white stone pillar was etched with silver runes, and there was a black hole that was flashing with black light above it.

One Immortal Origin Stone after another was flying out of the black hole, forming an endless stream that was constantly flowing into the golden array before disintegrating into balls of pure immortal spiritual power that fused into the array.

At the same time, bursts of fiery, golden light were also emanating from the golden stone pillar, injecting bursts of time law powers into the array.

With this continuous influx of immortal spiritual power and time law powers, the array began to operate, and head-sized balls of golden light flew out from within, giving off bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations as they rose up into the air.

Hovering above the golden array was a golden plate that was riddled with complex patters, and at its center was a thumb-sized bulge, protruding out of which was a golden needle.

The balls of golden light surged into the plate, and the golden needle began to rapidly spin.

Rings of golden light were emanating from the golden plate before vanishing into the nearby space, and Han Li's eyes widened slightly with astonishment at the sight before him.

What he was astonished by was the discovery that this array was the source of the accelerated flow of time in the entire True Mantra Profound Domain.

To put it more accurately, it was the golden plate above the array.

The other factor contributing to Han Li's astonishment was that this plate was the very same one that he had obtained from the True Mantra Sect ruins.

"As I'm sure you've already noticed, the flow of time in the True Mantra Profound Domain is different from that of the outside world, and the reason for that is this Heavenly Wheel Sundial. This sundial has the ability to alter the rate of flow of time, and it's the reason why our True Mantra Sect has been able to become as powerful as it is today," Patriarch Miro introduced.

With this domain at the True Mantra Sect's disposal, its disciples could cultivate dozens, even hundreds of times faster than everyone else, so it was no wonder that the sect had become so powerful.

"This Heavenly Wheel Sundial is truly an extraordinary treasure, but it seems like a huge amount of Immortal Origin Stones and time law powers are required to support it. On top of that, this array also appears to be quite remarkable," Han Li remarked.

"This array is called the Celestial Time Array, and it's one of the ten most powerful ancient arrays. Only with this array can the Heavenly Wheel Sundial be used. It's also true that a tremendous amount of resources is required to support the sundial's operation.

“The Immortal Origin Stones aren't the problem, but the constant stream of time law powers is rather difficult to come by. Thankfully, this Golden Xumi Mountain contains near-boundless time law powers, so it's perfect for supporting the Heavenly Wheel Sundial," Patriarch Miro explained.

Han Li's heart sank slightly upon hearing this.

Creating this domain had clearly been quite a difficult task even for the True Mantra Sect, so the chances of him being able to use the Heavenly Wheel Sundial on his own were slim to none.

"One thing worth noting is that if the Heavenly Wheel Sundial is made to alter the flow of time in a huge area like the entire True Mantra Profound Domain, then it'll require an astronomical amount of resources to support it, but that requirement becomes much less if you only want to alter the flow of time in a small area," Patriarch Miro remarked in a meaningful manner, and Han Li's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this.

It felt to him like Patriarch Miro was telling him because he already knew that the Heavenly Wheel Sundial would fall into his hands someday.

"Come, there's more to be seen deeper in the palace," Patriarch Miro said as he led the way forward again, and Han Li followed along with slightly furrowed brows.

After making their way around the array in the hall, the two of them continued onward, passing through a long corridor to arrive at a crossroads with two paths ahead, one leading to the left, and the other to the right.

The path on the right was glowing brightly while giving off bursts of formidable law auras that seemed to belong to powerful immortal treasures, many of which were of the time attribute.

In contrast, the left path appeared far more unremarkable.

"On the right is our True Mantra Sect's treasure vault, where many immortal treasures are kept. Let's go to the scripture hall on the left first, that's where our sect's most precious cultivation arts and secret techniques are kept," Patriarch Miro explained, then led Han Li down the left path into a golden hall that was rectangular in shape.

A series of grids had been dug into the walls on either side of the hall, and inside each grid was a book or a jade slip, but all of them were sealed behind golden light barriers.

Next to each grid was a small plaque that displayed the name of the scripture inside.

[1]. In Buddhism, the swastika is a symbol that represents auspiciousness and good fortune. As for why it was later adopted by Hitler, that's a bit of a long story that you can check out for yourself if interested.

[Back]

Chapter 1151: Scripture Hall

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up at the sight of all of the time-attribute secret techniques laid out around the hall.

"This True Mantra Palm Seal allows one to cultivate time law powers into a palm projection that contains nine circles, which are capable of storing different types of time law powers. The more you store, the more powerful the palm projection will be. If you can gather nine types of time law powers, the palm projection will reach the peak of its powers and be capable of destroying virtually anything."

This Time Destruction Divine Light is also an offensive ability that uses time law powers to manifest a ray of light capable of piercing through even space itself.

The plaques next to the grids only displayed the names of the scriptures inside, so Patriarch Miro began describing all of the secret techniques to Han Li one by one.

The more Han Li heard, the more stunned he became.

All of the secret techniques here were profound beyond his imaginations, and there were hundreds of them in this hall.

Han Li had even spotted the Reversal True Axis, the Eye of Truth, and the Mantra Domain, which he had already cultivated himself.

"I can see that you've already learned some of the abilities here, but you haven't made much progress in them at all, and that's a real pity. In particular, the Reversal True Axis and the Mantra Domain are abilities with immense potential that you haven't been able to tap into," Patriarch Miro suddenly remarked.

"Please enlighten men, Senior Miro," Han Li hurriedly implored.

"The Reversal True Axis is a very one-dimensional ability in that it only does one thing. I'm assuming that you're only able to enhance your own speed by about a dozenfold at the very most, right? I can tell you now that those who truly master the Reversal True Axis can enhance their own speed by hundreds of times, even over a thousandfold," Patriarch Miro said.

Han Li couldn't help but gasp in astonishment upon hearing this.

"That's why the Reversal True Axis is our True Mantra Sect's most powerful auxiliary ability, despite its one-dimensional nature," Patriarch Miro continued. "However, the ability asks a lot of one's physical constitution. I can tell that this is not a problem for you, given that you're already extremely advanced when it comes to physical cultivation, so it's a real pity that you've made so little progress in the Reversal True Axis."

Han Li's heartbeat immediately began to accelerate with excitement, but at the same time, he was kicking himself for his own oversight.

At some point, he had decided that he had already cultivated the Reversal True Axis to a sufficient degree, so he didn't allocate any more time to making further advancements.

After that, he acquired the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and that took up almost all of his time and attention, so all of his other time-attribute abilities were left untouched.

"As for the Mantra Domain, that's an ability that allows you to control the world around you through just your words. I used a hint of its power during my earlier lecture, and you saw what that amounted to.

“There are very stringent spiritual sense requirements for cultivating this ability, but once again, that is not a problem for you, so it's a massive waste that you're still stuck at the stage where you can only conjure up pure illusions in your Mantra Domain," Patriarch Miro continued.

Han Li had spent a great deal of effort on honing his Mantra Domain, so he felt a little indignant as he protested, "But aren't illusions already quite useful on their own?"

"The Mantra Domain is not just an illusory ability for fooling ordinary people! If you encounter someone well-versed in the laws of illusions, then your Mantra Domain will have no effect on them in its current form, so do not continue to stray down this wrong path," Patriarch Miro said in a stern manner.

Despite the stern tone that had crept into Patriarch Miro's voice, Han Li remained receptive to his advice as he could tell that Patriarch Miro was saying all of this for his benefit.

At this point, he had already been made aware of the power and potential of the Reversal True Axis and the Mantra Domain, both of which were abilities that suited him very well.

Given that he was going to have to dedicate a great deal of time and effort to honing those two abilities, he was no longer as interested in seeing all of the other time-attribute abilities in the hall.

All of a sudden, Han Li stopped in his tracks and cast his gaze toward a particular grid, one that contained the scripture for the Immortal Golden Cloud.

"This is our sect's most powerful defensive ability, but the prerequisites required to cultivate it are extremely stringent, so even though you've already obtained the cultivation method, I suggest you leave it for now," Patriarch Miro advised.

"You already know about that?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"Of course. I knew as soon as you appeared in the True Mantra Sect. How can I oversee the True Mantra Sect if I didn't have at least that level of competence?" Patriarch Miro answered.

Han Li felt a little embarrassed upon hearing this. He had thought that he had managed to remain hidden from Patriarch Miro this entire time, but as it turned out, nothing that he had done had managed to escape Patriarch Miro's notice.

He then thought back to his plan to venture into the Nine Origins Temple, and he realized just how reckless and foolish that was. If the vial spirit hadn't saved him from Chi Meng and Immortal Lord Miao Fa, he would've either already been dead by now or fallen into the hands of the Nine Origins Temple or the Heavenly Court, which was no better a fate than death.

He had been advancing extremely quickly in his cultivation over the years, but the cultivation of his mental state hadn't been able to keep up, and that was what had resulted in such an irrational decision.

With that in mind, Han Li gently exhaled, and all of the lingering arrogance and agitation in his heart was expelled in the wake of this wake-up call.

He continued onward, examining the scriptures that he had passed by as he did so, and it didn't take long before he reached the very back of the hall.

Next to the final grid was a plaque that read "Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra", but the grid itself was completely empty.

Not only that, but the other five branch cultivation arts, such as the Mantra Axis Scripture and the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome, were also missing.

"The Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra is the most prized cultivation art of our True Mantra Sect, and it's only ever been passed down verbally, so there are no written versions," Patriarch Miro explained, and Han Li nodded with an enlightened expression.

However, at the same time, he was also rather perplexed about why the other five time-attribute cultivation arts had all been written into books and seemed to have been quite prevalent.

Perhaps the scriptures of the sect had spread over time following its destruction at the hands of the Heavenly Court.

"That's all of the cultivation arts and secret techniques, how about we go and take a look at the treasure vault?" Patriarch Miro suggested with a smile.

Han Li naturally raised no objections to this, and the two of them made their way into the neighboring treasure vault.

The layout of the treasure vault was similar to that of the scripture hall. A series of grids had been dug into the walls, with each grid containing one or a set of immortal treasures.

The difference was that there was an array in each grid to nurture the immortal treasures inside.

All of these immortal treasures were of an extremely high caliber, and even the worst ones were sixth tier immortal treasures, while the best ones weren't inferior to the white bead that Han Li had secured for the Essence Fire Raven.

However, following that brief period of self-reflection, Han Li's mental state had completely settled, and he remained unmoved by these treasures.

"There are some more remarkable places in our True Mantra Sect. Would you like to take a look at them as well?" Patriarch Miro invited.

"There's no need for that. I can see that the True Mantra Sect is indeed more powerful than I had ever imagined, but I'm accustomed to doing things on my own, and I can't stay here for much longer anyway, so I'm afraid I'll have to turn down your kind offer of taking me as your disciple," Han Li replied as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute.

At this point, the number of remaining Time Dao Runes on the golden wheel above him would only be enough to allow him to remain in this time and space for about two more days, so even if he were to accept Patriarch Miro as his master, there wouldn't be much time for Patriarch Miro to instruct him.

On top of that, the True Mantra Sect was still incomparable to the monolith that was the Heavenly Court, and while he would gain some benefits from accepting Patriarch Miro as his master, it doing so would also throw him into the center of the conflict between the two almighty powers, so the benefits were simply outweighed by the drawbacks.

Patriarch Miro remained calm and collected after hearing what Han Li had to say, as if he had already anticipated such a response.

Instead of being incensed by Han Li's rejection, a smile appeared on his face as he said, "Looks like that wise man was correct in his evaluation. You are a very level-headed person, and you weren't swayed by everything that I showed you just now. I'm very happy to see that."

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this.

"At the moment, you still think that you can remove yourself from the conflict between our True Mantra Sect and the Heavenly Court, but that's only because you don't know enough about the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

“Anyone who cultivates the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, regardless of whether they join our True Mantra Sect or not, will inevitably be targeted and hunted by the Heavenly Court. On top of that, if I'm not mistaken, you should already be under some pressure from the Heavenly Court, right?" Patriarch Miro asked.

"How can you tell?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I can sense the auras of the Spirit Refinement Technique and a Reincarnation Palace mask inside you. On top of that, I can sense that this is no ordinary mask, so you must be a Reincarnation Disciple. That, in addition to the fact that you're cultivating the laws of time, tells me that the Heavenly Court will definitely not be looking favorably upon you," Patriarch Miro explained with a faint smile.

"Your wisdom is truly unmatched, Senior," Han Li sighed with a resigned nod.

"Hence, whether you join our True Mantra Sect or not won't affect the Heavenly Court's attitude toward you. In fact, the Heavenly Court is most likely already convinced that you're a disciple of our True Mantra Sect," Patriarch Miro continued, and Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this.

Chapter 1152: Master and Disciple

"Given the predicament that you're already in, you may as well join our True Mantra Sect. You've done quite well in your cultivation of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra thus far, but you've also made many mistakes.

“Right now, the five types of time law powers in your body are still relatively weak, so you won't be able to feel anything, but once those time law powers become stronger, problems will gradually begin to arise. When that time comes, you'll be torn apart and killed by the rampant time law powers in your body," Patriarch Miro warned.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Having just heard Patriarch Miro's lecture, he had gained a much deeper understanding of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and he could already sense that something wasn't quite right with the time law powers in his body.

He couldn't put his finger on exactly what was amiss, but he could tell with certainty that Patriarch Miro was telling the truth.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li arrived at a decision.

"In that case, I'm willing to join the True Mantra Sect," he said as he prepared to kneel down and kowtow to Patriarch Miro to officially accept him as his master.

Patriarch Miro was ecstatic to hear this, and he immediately raised a hand to release a burst of invisible force, holding up Han Li to prevent him from kneeling down.

"You and I are not even from the same time period, so there's no need for such formalities."

A surprised look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

"Even though I'm taking you as my disciple, you are already a very formidable cultivator, and I'm sure you'll be able to reach the Great Encompassment Stage soon. Hence, even though we're officially master and disciple, you can regard me as a friend to be treated on equal terms with yourself," Patriarch Miro continued with a smile, and Han Li was even more surprised to hear this.

All of the sects in the True Mantra Sect placed a great deal of importance in hierarchies of seniority, particularly when it came to master and disciple relationships. According to Han Li's knowledge, the True Mantra Sect was an ancient sect that also held these values in very high regard, so it was very surprising to him that Patriarch Miro was completely disregarding all of that.

Having said that, this suited him just fine.

He had become accustomed to fending for himself over the course of his cultivation journey, so the idea of having to kneel and kowtow to someone was a rather awkward and unappealing one.

"That wouldn't be right. I've taken you as my master, so I should observe the formalities of a disciple," Han Li said in a respectful manner.

Patriarch Miro didn't dwell on the subject as he sat down onto the ground while gesturing for Han Li to do the same.

After they had both taken a seat, a solemn look appeared on Patriarch Miro's face as he asked, "Han Li, how is the True Mantra Sect in your time period?"

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then replied, "In my time period, the True Mantra Sect had already been eradicated by the Heavenly Court long ago, and the Time Dao Ancestor of the Heavenly Court personally brought about its fall."

"I see..." Patriarch Miro replied in an unsurprised manner, as if he had already anticipated this.

"Master, I must warn you that Qi Mozi is not to be trusted. He will go on to betray the True Mantra Sect and defect to Heavenly Court, almost single-handedly bringing about the sect's downfall in the process, so make sure to act swiftly against him," Han Li urged.

Patriarch Miro's expression remained unchanged as he replied, "If it is the will of the heavens, then there's no need to try and alter it. Otherwise, no one can tell what could be brought about."

Han Li was just about to say something when Patriarch Miro raised a hand to stop him.

"Who's to say that our True Mantra Sect won't be destroyed just because I stop Qi Mozi's scheme? There's no need for us to discuss this matter any further. You just said that you won't be able to stay here for long, so in the remaining time that we have together, I want you to show me your Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra so I can determine the problems that you're facing."

Han Li obliged to this request, speaking no further on the matter of Qi Mozi as he channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

The Mantra Treasured Axis, the Time Severing Torch, the Clear Time Vial, the Illusory Dawn Hourglass, and the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree appeared around him one after another, then began to revolve around his body.

He wanted to fully display everything to Patriarch Miro, so he was channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra with all his might, revealing all of the Time Dao Runes and time law threads on the five time-attribute law treasures.

The fifty time law threads that he had expended to come here had all come from the Time Severing Torch, so at the moment, there were only just over a hundred time law threads left on it.

There were around thirty time law threads around the Mantra Treasured Axis, while each of the other three remaining law treasures only had a few law threads around them.

Patriarch Miro first gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, then immediately shook his head in disapproval.

Han Li raised some questions pertaining to his cultivation to Patriarch Miro, then also told him about his failed Great Encompassment Stage breakthrough before cupping his fist in a salute as he implored, "Please enlighten me, Master."

"The laws of time are one of the three paramount laws that transcend above all others, and nothing in this world can escape from its influence. As for the laws of the five elements, they form the foundation of all laws.

“The Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra is a cultivation art that uses the simplest reasoning of the five elements to divulge the secrets of the laws of time," Patriarch Miro said, while Han Li listened intently, latching onto his every word.

"The laws of the five elements are present in all other laws, as is the case with the laws of time. The five elements form an equilibrium in which they give rise to, but also conflict with one another, resulting in an eternal, unbroken cycle.

“That is the essence of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra. Regardless of how much time passes, the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra continues to exist in a self-sustaining cycle, granting it immortality in the all-encompassing river of time," Patriarch Miro continued.

Han Li was struck by a sense of enlightenment upon hearing this, as if a lamp had been ignited in his heart.

He had always wondered why the laws of the five elements featured so prominently in the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra when it was a time-attribute cultivation art, and this answered that lingering question.

"Hence, the most important thing in cultivating the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra is balance. The five elements can only coexist in harmony when all is balanced. Otherwise, catastrophic outcomes will arise. Right now, everything in your cultivation is extremely unbalanced.

“Your Time Severing Fire Domain has a huge number of time law threads, far outnumbering those of your Clear Time Vial, Illusory Dawn Sand Domain, and Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree. With such a severe imbalance present, how could you possibly have succeeded in your breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage?" Patriarch Miro explained.

"I see. The problem is that it's not so easy to increase the number of law threads on my Clear Time Vial, Illusory Dawn Hourglass, and Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree. Things that contain time law powers are difficult to find to begin with, and it'll make it even more difficult if I have to find treasures that contain similar time law powers to my Clear Time Vial, Illusory Dawn Hourglass, and Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree. Do you know any other way to attain time law threads, Master?" Han Li asked.

"The Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra grants you the extraordinary ability to refine the time law powers in external items into time law threads. In contrast, all other cultivators of the laws of time can only slowly and arduously attain time law threads by deepening their understanding of the laws of time and advancing in their cultivation base.

“You are able to progress countless times faster than them, yet it seems like you're still not satisfied," Patriarch Miro scolded in a stern manner.

"I understand that I'm asking for a lot, but in my time period, the Heavenly Court is constantly hot on my tail, so I can't afford to make slow and steady progress. Given that our True Mantra Sect is so powerful, would it be possible for me to have a few materials that contain time law powers that I can refine into law threads?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"So that's what you had in mind!" Patriarch Miro chuckled. "Of course I have the materials that you seek, but I'm assuming there are many restrictions to this type of space-time transmigration, so you may not be able to take them back with you."

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing, clearly having failed to consider this problem.

"In any case, it can't hurt to try," Patriarch Miro said as he swept a sleeve through the air to summon three items, namely a length of green wood, a broken, blue halberd, and an earthy, yellow stone.

All three items were giving off formidable time law power fluctuations that weren't inferior in the slightest compared with the Fire Age Fireflies nests.

"Thank you, Master!"

Even though there was a chance that these items wouldn't be able to make it back to his time period with him, Han Li was still very happy to have had them bestowed upon him.

"The path of cultivation must be one that's walked one step at a time. At the moment, the time law powers in your body are very unsettled, and that's an indication that you've been progressing too quickly, so you must take the time to remedy this problem," Patriarch Miro cautioned.

"Yes, Master," Han Li replied with a serious nod. "Also, I have another question pertaining to spirit domains. It's already been many years since I first attained my spirit domain, but up to this point, it's still in its most elementary form, and I haven't been able to reach the Creation Tier or the Spiritform Tier. Why is this?"

"As one of the three paramount laws, the laws of time are extremely powerful, but the Heavenly Dao is balanced in that it's far more difficult to progress in one's mastery of the laws of time than it is for other laws, and the same applies to the cultivation of your spirit domain. I'm afraid this is not something that I can help you with. The only way to advance your spirit domain is to deepen your understanding of the laws of time," Patriarch Miro replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then raised some other questions, some pertaining to the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, some to immortal treasures, and some about other facets of cultivation.

Not only did Patriarch Miro possess an unfathomable cultivation base, he also seemed to possess a boundless understanding of laws, immortal treasures, and all other aspects of cultivation, allowing him to answer all of Han Li's questions and provide him with frequent bouts of enlightenment.

Before long, almost all of the Time Dao Runes on the golden wheel had faded away.

Even though Han Li had only spent a short time with Patriarch Miro, his understanding of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, the laws of time, and the overall concept of cultivation had improved by leaps and bounds.

The two of them remained seated across each other in the hall, and Han Li didn't raise any further questions.

Patriarch Miro seemed to be able to sense that Han Li was about to leave, and he didn't say anything, either.

"Thank you for your guidance, Master. I have benefited immensely from our time together," Han Li said as he extended a respectful bow.

"As your master, it's only right that I instruct you in your cultivation. If anything, I feel quite inadequate in only being able to provide you with such limited guidance. Having said that, seeing as you possess the ability to transmigrate through space and time, you should be able to return here in the future. There are still many things that I have yet to teach you about the cultivation of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra," Patriarch Miro sighed.

Chapter 1153: Entering the Primordial Land

"I would also love to return here to receive more instruction from you, but I still haven't completely mastered this form of space-time transmigration, and I have to pay quite a heavy price per transmigration, so I may not be able to return to this place," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"Is that so?" Patriarch Miro mused as he raised an eyebrow. "In that case, take this with you. This contains the insights that I've made from cultivating the laws of time."

He flipped a hand over to produce a jade book as he spoke, then handed it to Han Li, who gleefully accepted the offering.

"Thank you, Master."

"It would naturally be ideal if you could successfully take those things back with you, but if you're unable to, then make sure to pay a visit to a place called the Yama Manor when you return to your time period," Patriarch Miro instructed.

"The Yama Manor? Where's that, and why do I need to go there?" Han Li asked.

"You'll know when the time comes," Patriarch Miro replied with a faint smile.

Han Li was rather perplexed by Patriarch Miro's enigmatic words and actions, but he didn't give it too much thought.

"Master, I have another request for you: would it be possible for you to give me a diagram for the Celestial Time Array outside?" Han Li requested.

"Of course. The array diagram isn't all that complex, so you should be able to memorize it now," Patriarch Miro replied as he handed a jade slip to Han Li.

Han Li took the jade slip, then injected his spiritual sense into it and began quickly memorizing its contents.

Just as Patriarch Miro had said, the array diagram wasn't very complex, and he was able to memorize it quite quickly.

Right at this moment, the final Time Dao Rune on the golden ring above his head finally faded, and the ring abruptly swelled to several times its original size, forming a black vortex above Han Li.

A burst of tremendous suction force surged out of the vortex, sucking him into it.

Patriarch Miro rose to his feet as he warned, "Han Li, the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra is an extraordinary cultivation art capable of allowing one to alter heaven and earth. Even the Time Dao Ancestor has always wanted to obtain it, and many other Dao Ancestors have been searching for it as well, so make sure to proceed with the utmost caution..."

Before Patriarch Miro had a chance to finish, Han Li was swallowed up by the black vortex and promptly lost consciousness.

......

After an indeterminate period of time, a burst of radiant, white light appeared before Han Li, and he descended back onto some firm ground, while the Heaven Controlling Vial fell into his lap.

After taking a moment to steady himself, Han Li looked around to discover that his vision was still rather blurry, and that all of the surrounding scenery was rather shadowy and indistinct.

He immediately sat down and closed his eyes for a while, and only after his spiritual sense had completely settled did he reopen his eyes.

In doing so, he discovered that he was seated atop a protruding cliff, and all he could see around him was the clear, blue sky, as well as clouds of different shapes and sizes.

He hurriedly cast his gaze toward his right hand, which was still holding the array diagram for the Celestial Time Array, but the jade slip had been enveloped in a burst of strange power, and it was rapidly fading into non-existence.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly pulled out the three time-attribute materials given to him by Patriarch Miro and the copy of the Immortal Golden Cloud, but those things also faded away without a trace in a span of mere seconds.

Han Li wasn't overly surprised to see this. After all, Patriarch Miro had already warned him of this possibility.

In any case, he had already reaped immense benefits from this trip back to the True Mantra Sect, so he wasn't all that disappointed.

However, now that these things were gone, he would have to travel to the Yama Manor that Patriarch Miro had mentioned. He had never even heard of this place before, so there was most likely going to be a long search ahead, and that was something that he would just have to think about another time.

Right at this moment, the vial spirit's voice suddenly rang out.

"It's very impressive that you were able to regain your bearings so quickly after such a prolonged stint of physical transmigration without the Heaven Controlling Vial acting as a space-time anchor for your return."

"Thank you for saving me, Senior Vial Spirit," Han Li hurriedly said as he pulled out the Heaven Controlling Vial.

"There's no need to thank me. I'm going to have to hibernate for a while to rest, so you'll have to fend for yourself for now. Make sure you don't end up dead," the vial spirit grumbled.

"Do you know where we are right now, Senior Vial Spirit?" Han Li asked.

"I'm sure you can already tell from the world's origin qi here that we're in the primordial land. As for exactly where we are, I have no idea. The primordial land is so vast that it may well be larger than all of the three thousand known immortal regions combined, and there are countless true spirits and other powerful creatures dwelling inside, so that's why I was telling you to take care not to end up dead..."

The vial spirit's voice became quieter and quieter as it spoke, until it faded altogether, and the pair of beady, little eyes on the vial also disappeared.

Han Li could only tuck the vial back down the front of his robe as he rose to his feet.

He strode over to the edge of the cliff, then looked down to discover that the landscape was smothered under a blanket of yellow sand that stretched as far as the eyes could see, with only some hills, patches of reddish-brown deserts, and spruces of sparse vegetation punctuating the monotonous expanse of yellow sand.

For now, I'll just have to find a safe place to go into seclusion for a while, Han Li thought to himself, then rose up into the air and flew away as a streak of azure light.

......

After flying through the boundless, yellow desert for over a month, Han Li finally arrived at a lush oasis.

Along the way, he was attacked by many sand beasts, but none of them posed any meaningful threat to him. He descended onto a hill on the edge of the oasis with the intention of taking a rest before he continued on his journey, yet he had only just sat down when he suddenly cast his gaze in a certain direction with slightly furrowed brows.

He could sense bursts of fiercely clashing energy fluctuations there, and after a brief hesitation, he concealed his own aura before setting off in that direction.

As he drew closer to the scene, he began to hear what sounded like choruses of animalistic roars, and after flying over a tall ridge, he was greeted by the chaotic sight of two primordial tribes locked in a fierce battle.

One of the tribes was comprised of creatures with black, humanoid bodies coupled with rhinoceros heads. There were tens of thousands of them, all of whom stood at over thirty feet tall, and each of them was wielding a giant, stone ax.

The eyes of all of these humanoid rhinoceros creatures were glowing bright red, as if they were in a berserked state, and they didn't seem to be able to feel any pain, nor did they appear to have any regard for their own safety.

The other tribe outnumbered the humanoid rhinoceros beings, but they were far smaller in stature. They were quite similar in appearance to normal big cats, such as tigers and leopards, but their bodies were riddled with cloud-shaped spots.

None of them were carrying any weapons, and they relied solely on their extremely sharp bone claws to inflict damage upon their enemies.

The humanoid rhinoceros beings were extremely strong and sturdy, while their feline opponents moved as swiftly as the wind, so they were quite evenly matched, and that made for a horrific battle where both sides had already suffered extensive casualties.

Han Li was standing atop the ridge, observing the battlefield from afar, and he noticed that there was a vacant area at the center of the battlefield that the combatants from both tribes seemed to have been actively avoiding.

At the center of this area was a giant, humanoid rhinoceros being that was close to a hundred feet tall, and he was locked in battle against a muscular, feline creature. Unlike their brethren, the two of them both possessed some powerful abilities in addition to their physical attacks, and it was clear that these were the leaders of the two tribes.

As he was observing the battle, the leader of the feline creatures suddenly seemed to have caught a whiff of Han Li, and he immediately turned to the ridge as he roared, "I smell the stench of a human!"

The giant rhinoceros being immediately stopped what he was doing and turned his attention to the ridge as well upon hearing this.

Han Li knew that he had been caught, and he could only heave a resigned sigh.

"I'm only just passing through."

However, the primordial beings weren't interested in hearing his excuses, and under the orders of their leaders, both parties disengaged themselves from the battle before retreating to open up some distance between themselves.

"There's a human over there! Kill him!" the two tribal leaders ordered in unison, and the two tribes that had been fiercely clashing just a moment ago immediately joined forces against a common enemy, charging toward the ridge in a collective fury.

Han Li immediately turned to depart upon seeing this, not wanting to get involved in this mess, but it then occurred to him that he still didn't know where he currently was, so it would be a good idea to find out from these primordial beings.

With that in mind, he sprang up into the air, then plummeted like a meteorite toward the pair of tribal leaders.

The giant rhinoceros being instantly lashed out upward with his huge ax, releasing countless crimson ax projections that swept toward Han Li in a frenzy.

Meanwhile, the feline creature sprang up into the air to meet Han Li, and with each stride that it took, a yellow cloud would appear beneath its paw, providing a staircase leading up to the heavens.

Even though they seemed to be sworn enemies, they worked together very well, and if Han Li were to be forced back by the storm of ax projections, then that would give the feline creature an opportunity to pounce on him.

Chapter 1154: Eight Regal Bloodlines

In the face of the storm of ax projections, Han Li displayed no intention of backing down. Instead, he accelerated even further as he charged straight into the fray.

Contrary to everyone's expectations, he wasn't immediately torn to shreds. Instead, he was able to force his way through all of the ax projections with his physical body alone before descending upon the giant rhinoceros being.

The rhinoceros being was rather taken aback by Han Li's formidable physical constitution, but he could sense that Han Li's aura wasn't particularly powerful, so he charged forward with his ax raised in a fearless manner.

Han Li stomped a foot down onto the sharp edge of the giant ax, and a resounding boom instantly rang out as the ax exploded into pieces.

The rhinoceros being's arms shuddered violently from the impact, and a numb sensation instantly spread through his entire body as his legs gave out from under him, forcing him to his knees.

Taking advantage of the force of the impact, Han Li sprang up into the air again to evade a sneak attack from the feline being, and right as his assailant was passing him by, he grabbed onto the back of his neck, then gave it a gentle squeeze, and the feline being immediately lost the ability to resist.

He carried the limp and powerless feline being by the scruff of the neck as he crashed down onto the rhinoceros being's shoulder, forcing him to bow his head to the ground.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and most of the primordial beings from the two tribes didn't even get a chance to catch a clear glimpse of what had happened before they discovered that their leaders had been subdued by Han Li.

All of them came rushing back from the ridge to surround Han Li while yelling demands for him to release their leaders.

Han Li paid no heed to them as he hoisted up the feline being's body with one arm so that their faces were level with each other, and he asked, "What are your two tribes called, and why are you fighting here?"

The powerless feline being merely took a resentful glance at Han Li and offered no response.

"I'm sure you know what a soul search technique is, right? Don't force me to use it, or you're going to regret it," Han Li threatened in a cold voice.

The feline being shuddered slightly, but remained silent.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as he raised a finger before extending it toward the feline being's forehead, and a translucent thread shot out of his fingertip before making its way toward the feline being's glabella.

To Han Li's surprise, the rhinoceros being beneath his feet suddenly answered his question in the feline being's stead.

"We are the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe, and they are the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe. We are fighting here because our two tribes have been sworn enemies for generations."

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and it immediately occurred to him that this was a rather strange turn of events.

"If you're sworn enemies, then why are you speaking up for him? It looks like you don't want me to search his soul, so that must mean that you're trying to hide something from me," Han Li deduced with a cold smile.

A look of alarm and frustration appeared on the rhinoceros being's face upon hearing this, and he was internally cursing humans for their cunning ways.

Han Li didn't hesitate any longer as he pressed his finger against the Cloud Spot Tiger being's glabella, and the translucent thread extending out of his fingertip instantly pierced into the latter's head.

The rhinoceros being immediately let loose a thunderous roar, and all of the surrounding primordial beings from the two tribes instantly converged toward Han Li, paying no heed to the safety of their two leaders.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which contained thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and they transformed into thirty-six pillars of golden lightning that formed a circle around him with a diameter of several thousand feet.

Huge balls of golden lightning erupted out of the pillars of lightning amid rumbling thunderclaps and loud, electric buzzing.

Primordial beings had an innate fear of lightning and fire, and none of them dared to venture into the wall of golden lightning that Han Li had erected.

Han Li took advantage of this opportunity to quickly search through the Cloud Spot Tiger being's soul, and a short while later, he withdrew his finger as a rather peculiar look appeared on his face.

From the Cloud Spot Tiger being's memories, Han Li had learned the true reason behind why this conflict had erupted between the two tribes.

The Silver Horn Rhinoceros being was telling the truth in that the two tribes really had been sworn enemies for generations and had already been in conflict for millions of years, but that wasn't the sole instigating factor for this conflict.

As it turned out, thirty years ago, the ruler of all of the primordial tribes, the True Spirit King, had suddenly declared that a blood inheritance ceremony was going to be held in the Holy Primordial Palace on Eight Plains Mountain, and all tribes that still possessed the eight ancient regal bloodlines had been summoned to Eight Plains Mountain.

The eight regal bloodlines belonged to the eight True Spirit Kings who ruled over the primordial land in ancient times, but at some point, eight True Spirit Kings had parted ways, leaving only a single one behind.

The descendants of the other True Spirit Kings were littered throughout the primordial land, and those that possessed purer regal bloodlines remained powerful forces to be reckoned with, while those with less pure bloodlines were often less fortunate, with some of them even going extinct entirely.

This blood inheritance ceremony was once the most important event in the primordial land, but it had already been tens of millions of years since the last one was held due to the incomplete nature of the eight regal bloodlines.

As soon as it became known that the ceremony was going to be held again, the entire primordial land was stirred up into a frenzy. All of the primordial tribes viewed it as a great honor to be able to attend the ceremony, and the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe and the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe were no exception.

However, their two tribes didn't even have a single inkling of any of the eight regal bloodlines, and they didn't even rank among the top one hundred most powerful primordial tribes, either, so they naturally had no right to take part in the ceremony.

Initially, their two tribes had no intention of attending the ceremony as they would only be embarrassing themselves, but some Silver Horn Rhinoceros beings had recently discovered an adolescent beast on their territory, one that possessed one of the eight regal bloodlines.

The adolescent beast was in a state of slumber, seemingly having sustained severe injuries, and it was currently under the protection of the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe.

However, right as the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe was planning in secret to deliver the adolescent beast to Eight Plains Mountain, news of their plan was somehow leaked to the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe.

The latter naturally didn't want to see the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe's plan succeed. After all, if they were to successfully deliver the adolescent beast to Eight Plains Mountain, they would most likely receive a handsome reward that could elevate their power and status beyond that of the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe. With that in mind, the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe had attacked the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe to try and claim the adolescent beast for themselves.

Han Li released the Cloud Spot Tiger being, and the latter slumped to the ground in an unconscious state.

"Where is this adolescent beast right now?" Han Li asked as he looked down at the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being.

The latter offered no response, but a strange gleam had appeared in his eyes.

Han Li hurriedly pressed a hand down onto the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being's head as he harrumphed, "I commend you for your bravery, but you're not going to detonate your own soul under my watch."

"You won't get any information out of me!" the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being roared.

A burst of translucent light emerged from the palm of Han Li's hand as he used his Spirit Refinement Technique to protect the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being's consciousness, thereby preventing him from detonating it.

"You have tens of thousands of brethren, so even if you detonate your own soul, I'll still be able to find that adolescent beast just fine, do you understand? I don't want to have to kill you, so don't go throwing your own life away for no good cause," Han Li said in a cold voice.

The Silver Horn Rhinoceros being calmed down a little upon hearing this, but he then immediately objected, "You humans are not to be trusted! Just kill me!"

"It's up to you whether you trust me or not, but I can tell you that I bear no ill will toward that adolescent beast. I have some questions for you, and I'll let you go once you've answered them," Han Li said.

The Silver Horn Rhinoceros being was slightly swayed upon hearing this, given that Han Li had refrained from killing the Cloud Spot Tiger being and also prevented his own self-detonation.

Han Li could see that the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being was coming around a little, and he asked, "Which area of the primordial land are we in right now?"

The Silver Horn Rhinoceros being was clearly rather taken aback by this question, and it took a moment for him to reply, "We are a subsidiary tribe to the Earth Dragon Tribe, and we are on the southwestern outskirts of the Earth Dragon Tribe's territory."

Han Li was rather flabbergasted to hear this. What kind of answer was this?

After some contemplation, he adopted a different line of questioning.

"How are areas in the primordial land distinguished from one another, and where is this area of the primordial land relative to the nearby immortal regions?"

"Our primordial land has always been split up into territories ruled over by major tribes, such as the territory of the Nine-Tailed Heavenly Fox Tribe, or the territory of the Bright Regal Peacock Tribe. Relative to the nearest immortal regions, the Earth Dragon Tribe's territory is somewhere between the Golden Origin Immortal Region and the Spirit Platform Immortal Region," the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being replied.

The Spirit Platform Immortal Region is right next to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region...

Somehow, he had ended up near the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region once again.

Han Li suppressed this thought as soon as it surfaced in his mind.

After being pursued by Chi Meng and Immoratal Lord Miao Fa, he had come to realize just how massive a disparity in power there was between him and mid-Great Encompassment cultivators, and he knew that venturing into the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region to search for Jin Tong would be a complete suicide mission.

Chapter 1155: Adolescent Beast

The Silver Horn Rhinoceros being could see that Han Li was a little distracted by his thoughts, and he attempted to move ever so slightly.

Han Li immediately snapped back to his senses before stomping down with mountainous force, causing the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being to sink even further into the ground.

"I did say that I won't kill you, but that doesn't mean that you should test me," Han Li warned.

The Silver Horn Rhinoceros being shuddered before falling still, not daring to move again.

"Which one of the eight regal bloodlines does that adolescent beast possess?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know," the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being replied.

"Looks like searching your soul will be more convenient, after all," Han Li harrumphed as he raised an eyebrow.

"I'm telling the truth! At the moment, the adolescent beast is in a strange state where it looks like it's been encased in a rock, and it's not giving off any aura fluctuations at all, so I can't tell what it's supposed to be," the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being explained.

"In that case, how do you know that it possesses a regal bloodline?" Han Li asked.

"Beings that possess regal bloodlines are naturally able to exert dominance over other primordial beings and evoke an urge to pledge subordination. You're a human, so you won't know about that," the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being explained.

As it turned out, Han Li actually was rather familiar with this concept. It was just like how his Heavenly Phoenix bloodline allowed him to naturally subjugate many species of avian demon beasts.

"Take me to the adolescent beast," Han Li ordered.

The eight regal bloodlines were most certainly all very powerful bloodlines. At the moment, Han Li was still missing two types of true spirit bloodlines in his Twelve Awakening Transformations, and if he could obtain one of those bloodlines from the adolescent beast, then that would certainly be very welcome news.

"You said you would release me once I answered your questions, yet you're blatantly going back on your word now! I knew you humans can't be trusted!" the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being yelled in a furious voice.

"Who told you that I'm a human?" Han Li asked.

"You're not a human? That's impossible!" the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being denied with a shake of his huge head.

Han Li offered no response, choosing to let his actions do the talking as he channeled his true spirit bloodlines and transformed into a giant Lightning Bird.

At the same time, he withdrew all of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords back into his body, revealing his Lightning Bird form to all of the surrounding Silver Horn Rhinoceros beings and Cloud Spot Tiger beings.

Han Li knew that there was no way that the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being would be willing to take a human to see the adolescent beast, and he didn't want to have to wipe out these two tribes, either, so he had to resort to trickery.

All of the primordial beings present were instantly rooted to the spot upon sensing the true spirit aura emanating from Han Li's body.

"You... What... How is this possible?" the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being stammered in disbelief.

"I bear no ill will toward the adolescent beast. You say that it's currently in a strange state of slumber, right? Perhaps I can even help it," the Lightning Bird declared in a thunderous voice, then spread its wings and soared into the heavens.

Without Han Li weighing him down, the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being was able to clamber to his feet, and after a prolonged period of contemplation, he acquiesced, "Alright, I'll take you to see it."

After that, Han Li woke up the unconscious leader of the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe, and following a brief conversation, he learned that the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being's name was Sang Tu, while the Cloud Spot Tiger being's name was Yun Bao.

Thus, what was supposed to have been a battle to the death reached a premature conclusion thanks to Han Li's intervention.

Shortly thereafter, all of the primordial beings had returned to their respective tribes, leaving only seven or eight people behind to accompany Sang Tu and Han Li to the place where the adolescent beast was being kept.

Before long, the group arrived at a small mountain, where Sang Tu led Han Li to a semi-concealed cave entrance.

As soon as Han Li reached the cave entrance, he was immediately struck by an aggressive wave of heat alongside a strong, sulfurous odor.

"It's in there?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

At the same time, he swept his spiritual sense through the interior of the cave, but didn't discover any special auras inside.

"Inside this cave is a lava lake, and my tribesmen often enter the cave to collect materials to forge our axes. Normally, we wouldn't enter the deepest part of the cave, but one of our tribesmen inadvertently fell in, and that was how the adolescent beast was discovered," Sang Tu explained.

"Alright, lead the way," Han Li instructed, and Sang Tu nodded in response before making his way into the cave entrance.

Now that the battle was over, Sang Tu had reverted back to his normal form, which was only around ten feet in height and far less imposing than the form that he had displayed on the battlefield.

As it turned out, not only did the Silver Horn Rhinoceros beings adopt an alternate physical form in battle, the same applied to the Cloud Spot Tiger beings as well. In their normal form, all of them walked in a bipedal, upright fashion, and much of the stripes on their heads had faded away, making them far less animalistic in appearance.

Han Li followed Sang Tu into the cave, and he discovered that the interior of the cave was very spacious.

On top of that, the walls and the ceiling above had all been chiseled smooth.

There was a path in the cave that was over ten thousand feet in length and gradually sloped downward, and at its conclusion, the path tapered to a round hole that was roughly seventy to eighty feet in size.

Beyond the hole was another cave that was illuminated by fiery, red light, and that was the source of the intense heat and sulfurous odor.

"That's where we discovered the adolescent beast," Sang Tu said as he pointed into the round hole.

"Take me inside," Han Li replied with a nod, and Sang Tu did as he was told, leading the way into the cave.

Han Li followed him inside, and he was greeted by the sight of a giant, underground lava lake.

The lava in the lake wasn't flowing. Instead, there were huge slabs of hardened, black rock over its surface that were formed by cooled and solidified lava. Bright, red light could be seen shining through the gaps between the slabs of rock, and that was coming from the still molten lava below.

Han Li swept his gaze over the surface of the lake, and he quickly spotted what appeared to be a black rock hovering above the center of the lake. It resembled a black dog that was curled up into a ball, and he immediately flew toward it with an intrigued expression.

As he arrived at the "rock" and was able to take a closer look, a peculiar feeling suddenly welled up in his heart.

Meanwhile, Sang Tu and the others had all involuntarily lowered their heads in a submissive manner, and it was clear that this dog-shaped black rock was the adolescent beast that Sang Tu had spoken of.

Han Li took a glance at them, then returned his gaze to the rock, and the more he inspected it, the more pronounced the look of befuddlement in his eyes became.

"Something's not right," Sang Tu said in a puzzled manner as he arrived by Han Li's side. "The last time I was here, the lake was still very active, and there wasn't anywhere near as much black stone on the surface."

"Was this adolescent beast always this color?" Han Li asked.

"It was black when we first found it, but I distinctly recall that its coloration definitely wasn't as dark as it is now," Sang Tu replied in a confident manner.

Han Li reached down to gently stroke the creature, and he immediately felt a cool sensation on his fingertips.

"It seems like this beast was severely wounded by an ice-attribute attack, and it had no choice but to completely seal itself away in order to save its own life. Right now, it's using the heat of the lava lake to help ward off its injuries," Han Li explained.

"So that's why so much of the lake's surface has cooled and solidified," Sang Tu mused with an enlightened expression.

"Alright, I'll be taking it back with me now," Han Li declared.

"I can't let you do that!" Yun Bao objected as he stepped into Han Li's path.

Han Li cast his gaze toward Yun Bao, and a hint of fear immediately flashed through the latter's eyes, but he stood his ground as he said, "If it's staying here to ward off its injuries, then won't we be endangering it by taking it away from here?"

"Your concerns are not unwarranted, but rest assured, I have a way to save him," Han Li replied with a nod, then spread a hand open, and a bright, silver flame appeared over the palm of his hand, giving off incredible heat that was hundreds of times more potent than that of the lava lake.

Sang Tu and the others all reflexively sprang back in retreat in the face of the unbearable heat.

"Can I take it with me now?" Han Li asked.

"My apologies, I shouldn't have doubted you," Yun Bao conceded in an apologetic manner.

"Alright, let's take it back to the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe," Han Li decided, and Sang Tu was ecstatic to hear this, while a concerned look appeared in Yun Bao's eyes.

Han Li had noticed both of their reactions, but he didn't say anything.

Shortly thereafter, the group departed from the cave.

......

The Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe's territory was situated on the bank of a large river, and it consisted of clusters of tall, tent-like buildings constructed from rocks, beast hide, and wood, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

Upon the return of Sang Tu, all of the Silver Horn Rhinoceros beings emerged from their tents to greet their leader, only to involuntarily bow their heads in the face of the bloodline pressure that they felt from the adolescent beast.

However, fierce killing intent then surfaced in their eyes at the sight of Yun Bao and his subordinates, and the situation could've easily spiraled out of control had Sang Tu not stepped forward to keep his tribesmen in check.

Sang Tu led everyone to his tent, and the adolescent creature was set down onto his beast hide bed.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li released the Essence Fire Child, and as soon as it appeared, the temperature in the tent instantly spiked drastically, forcing Sang Tu and the others to back out of the tent in discomfort.

Chapter 1156: Reunion with Xiao Bai

A hint of guilt welled up in Han Li's heart at the sight of the five remaining colored flames on the Essence Fire Child's head.

The Essence Fire Raven had expended two of its seven Rainbow Fire Pill Sand flames to protect him inside the Nine Dragon Divine Flame Dome, and Han Li had always felt rather guilty about this.

In contrast, the Essence Fire Raven didn't seem to be bothered by this at all, and as soon as it was released, it began skipping around joyfully on the palm of Han Li's hand as it always did.

"I promise that I'll recover everything that you've lost," Han Li vowed in a solemn manner, and the silver figure nodded firmly in response.

After that, Han Li raised a hand to send the dog-shaped black rock rising up into the air, following which the Essence Fire Raven transformed into a burst of silver flames that enveloped the entire rock.

Plumes of black smoke began to rise up from the black rock, and its surface gradually melted away like a layer of ice.

The black coloration became lighter and lighter, and it was as if layers were being peeled away from the exterior of the rock, gradually revealing the contents inside.

Before long, the entire outer layer of black rock had melted away, revealing what appeared to be an ice crystal, encapsulated within which was a small, white, furry beast that was curled up into a ball.

"Xiao Bai!" Han Li couldn't help but exclaim at the sight of the beast.

Indeed, the creature encased within the ice crystal was none other than the Pixiu that had traveled to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region with Jin Tong, Xiao Bai.

Sang Tu and the others were very surprised by the fact that Han Li seemed to be familiar with the adolescent beast, but Han Li paid no heed to their reactions as he instructed the Essence Fire Raven to melt away the final layer of ice.

However, even after the ice had melted away, Xiao Bai's eyes remained shut, and it was as if it were nothing more than a lifeless body.

Han Li began scouring his gaze and spiritual sense over Xiao Bai's body, and only then did he discover that even though Xiao Bai had been freed from its self-imposed seal of ice, its soul remained in a state of slumber, as if it had been sealed away by its own bloodline power.

Han Li could tell that this was an emergency self-preservation measure adopted by Xiao Bai, but he had no idea how to awaken Xiao Bai from this state.

The Essence Fire Raven could see that Han Li was preoccupied with the task of awakening Xiao Bai, so it vanished into his body on its own.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, releasing his spiritual sense into Xiao Bai's consciousness to try and awaken it.

However, upon entering Xiao Bai's consciousness, he discovered that there was nothing but a boundless expanse of darkness inside, and there seemed to be a burst of strange power that was sucking his spiritual deeper and deeper into the darkness.

Han Li immediately withdrew his spiritual sense from Xiao Bai's consciousness as a safety precaution upon sensing this strange suction force.

He then attempted to awaken Xiao Bai through the spiritual connection that existed between them, but as he projected his spiritual sense onto Xiao Bai, his surroundings suddenly turned to complete darkness, just like the all-encompassing darkness in Xiao Bai's consciousness.

Right at this moment, a pair of giant, glowing eyes emerged within the darkness, and they projected a cold gaze onto Han Li.

Before Han Li had a chance to figure out what was happening, he felt a burst of sharp pain in his consciousness before snapping back to reality with a flabbergasted look on his face.

"Can you save him?" Sang Tu asked.

"This beast is an acquaintance of mine, but for some reason, his consciousness is completely enshrouded in darkness, and as soon as I attempt to awaken him, I see a pair of glowing eyes that reject my spiritual sense," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"That sounds like... Could it be that this beast is a descendant of one of the eight ancient True Spirit Kings, the Ink-Eyed Pixiu?" Yun Bao exclaimed with a stunned expression, and Sang Tu's expression also changed drastically upon hearing this.

"What's an Ink-Eyed Pixiu?" Han Li asked.

"The Ink-Eyed Pixiu was said to be a tribe of beings that possessed the most powerful ocular ability under the heavens, allowing them to see the essence of all things and identify all manners of treasures. There are even legends claiming that their eyes are able to see through the ethereal cycle of reincarnation and predict the futures of others," Yun Bao explained.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this. It was true that Xiao Bai possessed the ability to find hidden treasures, but he certainly wasn't able to see into the cycle of reincarnation or predict the future.

"Not only that, but it's said that the eyes of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu can also connect to a strange space, and that once an Ink-Eyed Pixiu develops to fully maturity, they'll be able to suck enemies into that space with just a single look. Unless the enemy is far more powerful than them, there's no way they'll be able to escape from that space," Yun Bao continued.

"Xiao Bai does have a special space in his stomach that's completely isolated from the outside world, but I'm not aware of anything noteworthy about his eyes," Han Li mused.

"It seems like the entire Ink-Eyed Pixiu Tribe was wiped out after the Ink-Eyed Pixiu True Spirit King disappeared. Even to this day, it's extremely rare to see descendants of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu Tribe. If we can take him to Eight Plains Mountain, he'll surely be regarded as a precious treasure by all of the primordial tribes, and the True Spirit King will definitely be able to wake him up, " Sang Tu said.

A hesitant look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

His original intention was to find a place to cultivate in seclusion until he reached the early-Great Encompassment Stage and recovered all his Time Dao Runes, at which point he would travel to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region in anticipation for the Reincarnation Palace mission, but he had to reconsider his plans now.

After some contemplation, he decided to save Xiao Bai first. Once Xiao Bai woke up, he would be able to ask him about what happened in the Nine Origins Temple, thereby giving him better chances of saving Jin Tong while carrying out the Reincarnation Palace mission.

With that in mind, Han Li declared, "I'm willing to accompany you to Eight Plains Mountain to save Xiao Bai."

Sang Tu and Yun Bao's expressions both changed slightly upon hearing this, and the former immediately said, "Our Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe can complete that task on our own."

Yun Bao gave a cold harrumph, but didn't say anything.

After all, Xiao Bai had been found by the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe and was still on the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe's territory, so he had no right to speak on the matter.

"Are you planning to move your entire tribe to Eight Plains Mountain, Chief Sang Tu?" Han Li asked.

"Of course not, I'll only be taking the most capable warriors of our tribe for the journey," Sang Tu replied.

"In that case, what's going to become of the rest of your brethren? Don't forget that none of the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe's most capable warriors are going anywhere," Han Li said in a meaningful voice, and a sheen of cold sweat instantly beaded up on Sang Tu's forehead upon hearing this.

If he were to take Xiao Bai to Eight Plains Mountain, then the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe would be backed into a corner and be left with no choice but to kill all of the Silver Horn Rhinoceros beings that were left behind.

Even if they were to be rewarded by the True Spirit King for delivering Xiao Bai to Eight Plains Mountain, it would hardly matter if their entire tribe were wiped out.

"I'm willing to work with the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe to deliver Xiao Bai to Eight Plains Mountain," Sang Tu conceded, and Yun Bao cast a grateful glance toward Han Li upon hearing this.

"After the two of you depart, your tribes will be without their leaders, and eventually, word of this is inevitably going to spread, to the other nearby tribes, which could view this as a potential opportunity to strike. Hence, not only do the two of you have to work together, your two tribes must also join forces and look out for one another in each other's time of need. Otherwise, there's a good chance that neither of your tribes will still exist by the time that you're back," Han Li continued.

Sang Tu and Yun Bao both displayed reluctant expressions to the idea, and it was clear that this was a rather difficult notion for them to stomach.

The two tribes had been in conflict with one another for millions of years, so how could they possibly set their differences aside and work together at the drop of a hat?

"I understand that this may be a difficult proposition for you to accept, but you don't need to be allies forever. Just maintain this alliance until the two of you are back from the blood inheritance ceremony, and you'll be free to do whatever you want after that," Han Li said with a smile.

Sang Tu and Yun Bao were both silent for a long while, following which both of them nodded in unison.

"Thank you for pointing out a path forward for us, Senior. We'll do as you say."

"There's no need to refer to me as senior, just call me Shi Mu or Fellow Daoist Shi. By the way, when is this blood inheritance ceremony set to begin?" Han Li asked.

"It was announced thirty years ago that the ceremony would commence in a hundred years, so we have less than seventy years left. The journey to Eight Plains Mountain will be quite a lengthy one, so we'll have to set off soon," Sang Tu replied.

At this point, Han Li had already essentially become the joint leader of the two tribes, and he instructed, "In that case, go back to your tribes right away and make the necessary arrangements. We'll depart as soon as possible."

Sang Tu and Yun Bao gave a collective, affirmative response, following which both of them promptly departed.

Sang Tu declared that this tent would be reserved for Han Li for now, and that no one was to approach the tent without permission.

Han Li sat in the tent for a moment, then swept a sleeve through the air to open the Flower Branch domain.

After that, he picked up Xiao Bai in his arms and stepped into the bamboo pavilion in the domain.

Chapter 1157: Spoils

As soon as Han Li set foot into the Flower Branch domain, he was immediately struck by the feeling that something wasn't right.

Before he had a chance to think about it, he was overcome by a rumbling commotion interspersed with ghostly shrieks that constantly varied in pitch, making for an extremely unpleasant cacophony of noises.

He could feel his own mental state starting to become affected, and he hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to stabilize his own soul before turning to the direction that the noise was coming from, upon which he discovered that the source of the commotion was none other than the pavilion that Weeping Soul was currently staying in.

At this moment, the entire pavilion was enshrouded within a cloud of black mist that was as viscous as ink, and it had formed a swirling, black vortex with ghostly figures flashing in and out of sight within, causing the restrictions around the pavilion to tremble incessantly.

Thankfully, those restrictions had been personally set up by Han Li and had been infused with his time law powers. Otherwise, they most likely wouldn't have been able to contain the black vortex.

What's going on?

Han Li hurriedly flew over to the pavilion before injecting a wisp of spiritual sense into it, but as soon as his spiritual sense entered the black vortex, it was immediately devoured, and a burst of formidable devouring force surged out of the vortex, attempting to infiltrate his mind.

Han Li hurriedly withdrew his spiritual sense, and only then was he able to shrug off the strange, devouring force.

At the same time, a hint of elation appeared on his face.

This phenomenon was definitely being caused by Weeping Soul, and that indicated that she had made a breakthrough in her absorption of Ghost King Wu Chao's power.

A contemplative look then appeared on his face as he pondered how to proceed. This wasn't something that he could intervene in, so he would just have to count on Weeping Soul to get through this on her own.

With that in mind, he swept a sleeve through the air to release dozens of streaks of golden light, which descended near the pavilion to create an even sturdier golden light barrier.

This light barrier was also imbued with time law powers, and it resonated with the restrictions inside the pavilion to fortify one another.

Much of the commotion ringing out in the pavilion was instantly stifled, and it no longer had any effect on Han Li, who made his way to the newly constructed pavilion beside the spirit medicine garden.

The entire pavilion was laden with all types of ores, materials, and immortal treasures that he had gathered from the Tai Sui Immortal Manor, and some of the larger spirit materials were piled up on the ground outside the pavilion.

As for the spirit plants and spirit medicines he had obtained from the Tai Sui Immortal Manor, there were too many of them to count.

Han Li set Xiao Bai down on the top floor of the pavilion, then set up a protective restriction.

After that, he began to inspect all of the treasures in and out of the pavilion with a look of mixed emotions on his face.

While he was certainly ecstatic to have collected such a massive haul, there were so many things here that sorting through them was going to be a huge pain. Having said that, if he could sell everything, then he would be able to earn an astronomical sum of Immortal Origin Stones.

He had constantly been busy with other things since departing from the Tai Sui Immortal Manor, and he finally had some free time to take stock of everything.

He flipped a hand over to produce a blank jade slip, then began carefully tallying, categorizing, and recording all of the treasures in the pavilion.

After a day of work, everything inside the pavilion had been organized, so he made his way outside to record all of the spirit materials and spirit plants there as well.

After doing all of that, Han Li sat down near the pavilion, then swept a sleeve through the air to release an assortment of items, all of which seemed to be storage tools.

These storage tools had been gathered from cultivators that had met their demise in the Tai Sui Immortal Manor, and the collection was sure to contain a sizable amount of wealth.

The most valuable of all of the storage tools were undoubtedly those that once belonged to She Chan and Lan Yuanzi.

Han Li had roughly inspected the contents of She Chan's storage tool in the past, but hadn't yet gotten the chance to conduct a detailed inspection.

He picked up She Chan's storage tool before emptying its contents, and a huge mountain of items instantly appeared on the ground.

Sure enough, She Chan didn't disappoint. She possessed tremendous wealth, and even if all of the materials and immortal treasures were to be disregarded, she still had over twenty million Immortal Origin Stones.

There were around thirty to forty of these Immortal Origin Stones that were particularly worthy of note in that they were even larger than mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones, and they were radiating dazzling light that was giving off astonishing immortal spiritual power fluctuations.

Are these high-grade Immortal Origin Stones?

Han Li's eyes lit up as he picked up one of those special Immortal Origin Stones, and a burst of vast and pure immortal spiritual power instantly surged into his body, making him feel as if he were bathing in a hot spring.

The sensation was so blissful that he was almost unable to suppress the urge to moan out loud.

A wide grin appeared on his face as he looked down at the Immortal Origin Stone in his hand.

Even though he had never seen one before, he was certain that this was a high-grade Immortal Origin Stone, and the immortal spiritual power that it contained was far purer and more concentrated than even the immortal spiritual power in his body.

With an Immortal Origin Stone like this, he would most likely be able to fully replenish his immortal spiritual power reserves within the span of just a few seconds.

However, high-grade Immortal Origin Stones were extremely precious, and it would be far too wasteful to use them for immortal spiritual power replenishment.

Han Li had read from some scriptures that there were many brilliant uses for high-grade Immortal Origin Stones, including refining high-grade immortal treasures, assisting in making breakthroughs, and even severing corpse souls.

After playing with the high-grade Immortal Origin Stones for a while, he carefully stowed them away, then stowed away the other Immortal Origin Stones as well.

He then categorized all of the other items in She Chan's storage tool before moving onto Lan Yuanzi's storage tool.

Back in the Eon Pagoda, he had taken Lan Yuanzi's storage tool after capturing him.

With that, Han Li repeated the process, emptying out everything in the storage tool before categorizing them as well.

Lan Yuanzi's storage tool only contained fewer than seven million Immortal Origin Stones, and there wasn't even a single high-grade Immortal Origin Stone among them.

After that, Han Li sorted his way through the rest of the storage tools as well. The owners of these storage tools hadn't been particularly advanced in cultivation base, so the sum of all of the Immortal Origin Stones in those storage tools combined only amounted to fewer than five million.

Han Li placed all of these Immortal Origin Stones into his own storage tool, and he was unable to suppress a pleased smile.

Prior to this, he only had fewer than ten million Immortal Origin Stones in his possession, yet his wealth had more than quadrupled!

On top of that, by his estimates, he would be able to double this wealth once again once he sold all of the treasures around him.

Han Li picked out all of the treasures inside and outside the pavilion that could be of use to him, then put on his Reincarnation Palace before putting up all of the rest of the treasures for sale.

There were so many treasures that it took him over a month to sell the majority of them, netting himself over thirty million more Immortal Origin Stones, and that was only because Han Li had sold them all for low prices as he was in a hurry to do so. Otherwise, the earnings would've been even more substantial.

The rest of the items were rather special and difficult to sell, so he would just have to wait and see if there would be any takers.

In any case, he already had over seventy million Immortal Origin Stones, and that was enough for him to use for a very long time.

Such a vast number of Immortal Origin Stones would be considered an immense amount of wealth even for Great Encompassment cultivators, and his personal wealth currently outweighed that of some of the largest sects in some small immortal regions.

With so many Immortal Origin Stones at his disposal, he was confident that he would be able to afford the time law materials that he needed.

Unfortunately, such materials were extremely rare, so even if he had the Immortal Origin Stones, he would have to wait for such items to present themselves.

Right at this moment, Han Li raised an eyebrow and flew out of the Flower Branch domain to arrive in the tent outside.

"Senior Shi Mu."

Sang Tu's voice rang out from outside, but he didn't step into the tent.

At this moment, Sang Tu and Yun Bao were both standing outside the tent, and each of them was accompanied by around a dozen subordinates.

Docked behind them was a bone flying boat that was four hundred to five hundred feet in length, but it had been constructed from very ordinary materials, and there were two winged tiger demon beasts tied to it.

Behind the flying boat were several smaller flying boats and carriages that were laden with cargo, and they were also being drawn by the same type of winged tiger demon beasts.

It was clear that the time of departure had arrived, and Han Li instructed, "Come in."

"All of the preparations are already complete, Senior Shi Mu. When should we set off?" Sang Tu asked in a respectful manner.

"Let's set off right away," Han Li replied.

With that, he emerged from the tent, and he was personally escorted by Sang Tu and Yun Bao to the finest room on the flying boat.

The boat then began to glow as it rose up into the air, following which the pair of winged tiger beasts spread their wings and took flight.

The two winged beasts were only at the Golden Immortal Stage, but they were able to fly extremely quickly, displaying speed that wasn't inferior to some High Zenith cultivators.

Of course, Han Li had better flying boats in his collection that could speed up the journey, but he refrained from bringing them out as they could expose him as a human.

"I'm going to go into seclusion, don't bother me unless something important comes up," he instructed, and Sang Tu and Yun Bao hurriedly gave affirmative responses before departing.

Han Li was quite pleased with their displays of obedient subordination, and he set up some restrictions in the room, then entered the Flower Branch domain and sat down in the bamboo pavilion.

While it was true that everything that he had recently sold had earned him a great deal of wealth, those weren't the biggest spoils that he had reaped from the Tai Sui Immortal Manor.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li summoned a collection of four items.

The first one was a golden scroll that was bound by a thin, golden string, and it was the scroll that had been present on the same altar as the Eon Divine Lamp.

The second item was a purple jade slip, which contained the Five Lightning True Mantra that had been given to him by the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

The third item was the Eon Divine Lamp, and the final one of the four items was the diagram for the Almighty Sword Array.

These four items, in addition to the white fire bead, were the biggest spoils that he had reaped from the Tai Sui Immortal Manor.

Out of the four items, Han Li picked up the golden scroll.

He had roughly examined all three of the other items before, but he was still yet to open this scroll, so he didn't know what it was.

However, the fact that it had been placed together with the Eon Divine Lamp indicated that it was definitely no ordinary scroll.

Chapter 1158: Resurrecting the Divine Lamp

Han Li loosened the golden string and unfurled the scroll with a hopeful look on his face.

The words "Eon True Mantra" were inscribed onto the cover of the scroll in antiquated characters, and the title immediately gave Han Li a good idea of what the contents of the scroll were.

Just as he guessed, the scroll contained a time-attribute cultivation art that allowed one to attain Flames of Eons, which were capable of bringing all things to decay and demise.

Han Li carefully read through the golden scroll, and it took him almost an entire day to finish it, upon which an elated look appeared on his face as he picked up the Eon Divine Lamp.

The Eon True Mantra was extremely profound, and while it couldn't compare with the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, it was still one of the True Mantra Sect's premium time-attribute cultivation arts.

However, Han Li's elation didn't come from obtaining this cultivation art. Instead, it arose from the fact that the cultivation art contained the refinement method for the Eon Divine Lamp.

With its flame snuffed out, the Eon Divine Lamp had been reduced to something that was completely useless, and Han Li was naturally eager to restore it to its former glory.

With that in mind, Han Li stowed the Five Lightning True Mantra and the Almighty Sword Array Diagram away.

He was originally planning to study those two items closely, but now that he had found the refinement method for the Eon Divine Lamp, that took priority above all else.

Han Li unfurled the Eon True Mantra once again, then directed his attention to the section where the refinement method was recorded.

Even though the refinement method was laid out, it was not going to be easy to execute, particularly because he had only just obtained the Eon True Mantra.

The refinement method wasn't all that complex, as long as one was already cultivating the Eon True Mantra. For such a cultivator, all they would have to do was slowly nurture the Eon Divine Lamp with their time law powers.

Even though the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra that Han Li was cultivating was far more profound than the Eon True Mantra, he couldn't use it to refine the Eon Divine Lamp.

As one of the three paramount laws, the laws of time were extremely difficult to cultivate, so he absolutely could not cultivate the Eon True Mantra and the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra simultaneously. Otherwise, something could easily go awry in his cultivation, leading to catastrophic consequences.

The reason why Patriarch Miro hadn't tried to teach Han Li any of the True Mantra Sect's many time-attribute secret techniques was precisely because he was afraid that Han Li would bite off more than he could chew and take on too much at once.

However, just because he wasn't going to cultivate the Eon True Mantra didn't mean that it would be impossible for him to refine the Eon Divine Lamp.

With that in mind, he raised a hand, and the golden flame that he had obtained from the altar in the Eon Pagoda appeared over the palm of his hand.

Immediately thereafter, he summoned the Time Severing Torch as well, and at the same time, a flurry of spiritual sense threads flew out of his glabella.

The Time Severing Torch began to release bursts of time law powers, and Han Li injected these time law powers and his spiritual sense into the golden fireball in unison.

The golden flame instantly swelled to around twice its original size, and it also began churning violently.

The time law powers from the Time Severing Torch, the golden flame's own time law powers, and Han Li's spiritual sense threads were all clashing against one another in a chaotic fashion.

All the while, Han Li was making a rapid string of hand seals, controlling the time severing law powers and his spiritual sense threads to ensure that they were interacting with the golden flame's law powers in a manner that he desired.

In doing so, he was able to alter the time severing law powers to simulate the law powers of the golden eon flame.

This was a spirit conversion technique that had been taught to him by Patriarch Miro, and it allowed him to use his spiritual sense as a medium to use one type of law powers to simulate another.

Due to the fact that almost all of the immortal treasures in Han Li's possession had been taken from others, he was simply unable to use many of them, and he had brought up this problem to Patriarch Miro.

This was not something that was out of the ordinary. Generally speaking, it was quite rare for a cultivator to obtain an immortal treasure that just so happened to correspond with the law powers that they were cultivating, unless that immortal treasure had been refined specifically for them.

As a result, cultivators were often unable to unleash the full power of the immortal treasures in their possession.

A powerful cultivators in the True Mantra Sect had invented this True Mantra Spirit Conversion Technique to remedy this exact problem, allowing the cultivator to simulate other types of law powers in order to make better use of their immortal treasures.

Of course, there couldn't be too much of a disparity between the two types of law powers. They had to be of the same attribute, and ideally, they should also possess similar properties.

The True Mantra Spirit Conversion Technique couldn't allow one to perfectly replicate a specific type of law powers, but it could certainly produce a very similar product.

Time severing laws and eon laws were fundamentally quite similar, so there was a very good chance that the True Mantra Spirit Conversion Technique would yield a successful outcome.

Qi Mozi had most likely used the same technique to gain control over the Eon Divine Lamp.

Initially, Han Li was very unfamiliar with the True Mantra Spirit Conversion Technique, and the time severing laws were constantly clashing violently with the eon laws.

However, as he became more and more well-versed with the secret technique, the conflict between the two types of law powers began to slowly subside.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

......

Several years flew by in a flash.

The journey had been quite smooth up to this point. The convoy was attacked by some primordial beasts on several occasions, but Sang Tu and Yun Bao were able to deal with them with relative ease.

However, Sang Tu and Yun Bao didn't dare to let any complacency creep in, and they patrolled the surrounding area in shifts, constantly on the lookout for potential danger.

At this moment, Sang Tu and another Silver Horn Rhinoceros being were patrolling the convoy, and the latter took a glance at Han Li's room, then asked through voice transmission, "Chief, do you think Senior Shi really wants to help us? I can't shake the feeling that it wasn't the right decision to give him that adolescent Pixiu."

"Shush! Senior Shi is far more powerful than us, so even your voice transmissions could be overheard by him!" Sang Tu scolded in a stern manner, and the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being immediately fell into a fearful silence.

The two of them stared at Han Li's room in a tense silence for a long while, but nothing happened, and only then did they heave a collective sigh of relief.

"You think I don't know all of that? The problem is that Senior Shi is far too powerful for us to oppose. On top of that, the little Pixiu is so precious that if we were to deliver it to Eight Plains Mountain with the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe on our own, then that would only spell disaster for us.

“Not only will we not be rewarded, we'll be torn to shreds by other envious tribes! Hence, regardless of what Senior Shi's objectives are, we have no choice but to rely on him, so make sure you don't say anything like that ever again, and also forbid everyone else from discussing Senior Shi!" Sang Tu ordered through voice transmission in an even quieter voice.

"Your foresight is truly unmatched, Chief," the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being praised with a look of admiration in his eyes.

Sang Tu was just about to say something else when a dull thump suddenly rang out from Han Li's room.

Sang Tu and the Silver Horn Rhinoceros being were both given a massive fright, thinking that Han Li had overheard their conversation, but there was no followup to the loud thump, and the two men were left staring at each other with perplexed expressions.

At this moment, Han Li was sitting in the bamboo pavilion in the Flower Branch domain, looking extremely disheveled. His clothes and hair had been severely singed, while many parts of his body had been charred black, and the eon flame was nowhere to be seen.

Despite this, his eyes were glowing with elation.

After six years of tireless effort, he had finally managed to successfully emulate eon laws using the True Mantra Spirit Conversion Technique.

In a moment of elation, he failed to control the law powers in his hands, thereby causing the eon flame to explode, and that had almost resulted in severe injuries.

After taking a pill, he quickly recovered from his injuries, then sat down with his legs crossed and picked up the Eon Divine Lamp.

After that, he summoned his Time Severing Torch, and bursts of time severing law powers surged out of the torch, then quickly came together to form a golden flame that was giving off very similar law power fluctuations to the eon flame.

The counterfeit eon flame flew forward to envelop the Eon Divine Lamp at his behest, and it slowly fused into the lamp.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and he hurriedly began refining the Eon Divine Lamp in accordance with the method outlined in the Eon True Mantra.

A layer of faint, golden light instantly appeared over the lamp's surface, and Han Li heaved a long sigh of relief upon seeing this.

It seemed that his efforts had not been in vain.

After that, he conjured up several more balls of counterfeit eon flames and continued to slowly refine the Eon Divine Lamp.

As the process wore on, the golden light emanating from the Eon Divine Lamp grew brighter and brighter, and the time law power fluctuations that it was giving off also became more and more pronounced.

Finally, after three months of tireless refinement, a golden flame finally appeared in the lamp.

In the instant that the Eon Divine Lamp was lit, it immediately released a burst of incredibly potent time law power fluctuations that spread through the entire Flower Branch domain, causing all of the world's origin qi in the domain to churn violently.

With that, the Eon Divine Lamp had been restored to its former glory.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he quickly made a hand seal, upon which a fiery, golden dragon shot out of the flame in the Eon Divine Lamp at his behest.

Chapter 1159: A Deal

The fiery, golden dragon circled around in the air above the Flower Branch domain, letting loose long, draconic roars as it did so.

The golden light radiating from its body was almost too bright to directly look at, and the law powers that it was giving off were also extremely formidable, even more so than when the Eon Divine Lamp had been under the control of Daoist Master Dao Yin and Qi Mozi.

The nearby space began to tremble violently, as if it were unable to withstand the fiery dragon's fearsome might, and an alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

He had no idea what was going to happen if the space within the Flower Branch domain were to shatter, and with that in mind, he hurriedly withdrew the fiery dragon, which quickly vanished into the flame of the Eon Divine Lamp at his behest.

He then cast his gaze toward the Eon Divine Lamp as he thought back to that almighty, fiery dragon, and he could help but wonder why the Eon Divine Lamp was so powerful in his hands.

Unbeknownst to him, the reason that the fiery dragon had been so powerful was because he was cultivating the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

The Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra was an unfathomably profound time-attribute cultivation art that had been derived from the most fundamental five elements of heaven and earth, and the time law powers derived from it were of an exceptional caliber, far higher than that of Qi Mozi. Hence, the simulated eon flame was also more formidable, thereby allowing him to tap into more of the Eon Divine Lamp's power.

After withdrawing the fiery dragon, Han Li continued to refine the Eon Divine Lamp.

Even though he was now able to control the lamp, he was far from proficient at it, and he had to further refine the lamp in order to fully make it his own.

However, refining the Eon Divine Lamp wasn't a task that required his full attention, so he decided to pull out the Almighty Sword Array Diagram and the Five Lightning True Mantra while he was at it.

First, he picked up the jade slip that contained the Five Lightning True Mantra, and after carefully reading through its contents, he couldn't help but be stunned by what he saw.

This was truly an extraordinary cultivation art, as expected of something that had received such high praise from the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

According to the Five Lightning True Mantra, the lightnings of the world consisted of thirty-six heavenly lightnings, seventy-two earth lightnings, and one hundred and eight cloud lightnings.

The majority of the lightnings that Han Li had witnessed in the past had all been cloud and earth lightnings, while the thirty-six heavenly lightnings were all extremely powerful and rare.

His Divine Devilbane Lightning was one of the seventy-two earth lightnings, as was the Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning in the Gray Realm's Baleful Cleansing Pond. However, the two lightnings had been combined by his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords to form a new type of lightning, one that was very close in power to heavenly lightnings.

The Five Lightning True Mantra also contained many lightning-attribute secret techniques that opened Han Li's eyes to possibilities that he had never even considered before.

However, Han Li decided not to read too deep into the Five Lightning True Mantra. Its contents were far too profound, and he didn't specialize in using lightning-attribute cultivation arts, so at the very most, he would only cultivate several of the secret techniques in the jade slip.

With that in mind, the Five Lightning True Mantra was almost wasted in his hands.

After reading through the Five Lightning True Mantra, Han Li stowed it away before picking up the Almighty Sword Array Diagram.

He released his spiritual sense to envelop the array diagram, and to his surprise, he was able to inject his spiritual sense into it without any resistance.

All of a sudden, an immense torrent of information surged into his mind.

There was so much information that it took him quite some time to completely digest it, even with his tremendous spiritual sense, and an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

The array diagram contained the methods for setting up and using the Almighty Sword Array.

Han Li had witnessed more than his fair share of sword arrays in the past, but none of those sword arrays could even hold a candle to this Almighty Sword Array.

Technically, the Almighty Sword Array wasn't a pure sword array. Instead, it communicated with the Great Dao of heaven earth through the medium of a sword array, and it was truly befitting of the prefix of "almighty".

This array diagram was the foundation of the Almighty Sword Array, and it was devoid of attributes, so there were no attribute requirements when it came to the flying swords used. As long as one could gather thirty-six flying swords of any attribute, they would be able to set up the Almighty Sword Array.

Of course, the flying swords used had to be of a very high caliber. Otherwise, they wouldn't be able to withstand the immense power of the array.

Han Li was very pleased to see this as his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords fulfilled both the quantity and quality prerequisites to support the sword array.

The Almighty Sword Array was incredibly profound, and even with Han Li's comprehension ability, he found himself having to read through the contents of the array diagram very slowly.

Right at this moment, a burst of crimson light suddenly appeared on his body.

He raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, then set down the Almighty Sword Array Diagram before putting on his Reincarnation Palace mask.

As it turned out, someone had responded to his advertisement expressing his desire to purchase items that contained time law powers.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up, and he made a hand seal, upon which a projection of a humanoid figure emerged from his Reincarnation Palace mask.

It appeared to be a young man with a head of slightly curly black hair, and even though his face was concealed by his mask, he still gave off an air of natural and unrestrained grace.

The words "Ape 3" were visible on his mask.

"I've heard much about you, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5," Ape 3 said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Do you have any time-attribute law materials for me?" Han Li asked, cutting straight to the chase.

"Of course, why else would I have contacted you?" Ape 3 replied as he flipped a hand over to produce a fist-sized, water-droplet-shaped, blue crystal.

Even though it was only a projection, Han Li could clearly see the specks of golden light in the crystal, like rays of sunlight shimmering in rippling water.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as he identified the blue crystal to be a Water Divination Time Crystal.

"This is a premium Water Divination Time Crystal. It may not be that large, but I assure you that it contains immense time law powers, enough to refine even a fifth tier immortal treasure," Ape 3 introduced with a smile.

Han Li nodded in response. Even though he could only see a projection, he could tell that the Water Divination Time Crystal didn't contain any less time law powers than the Fire Age Firefly nests that he had obtained in the past.

"How many Immortal Origin Stones would you like for it?" Han Li asked.

"I exhausted almost all of my savings to obtain this Water Divination Time Crystal, and I'm not planning to sell it for Immortal Origin Stones," Ape 3 replied with a shake of his head.

"Would you like to exchange it for something then?" Han Li asked.

"I suppose you can say that. To put it more accurately, I want to make a deal with you," Ape 3 replied with a smile.

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"I can tell that you're a direct and straightforward person, so I won't waste any time talking in circles. Right now, I am in urgent need of a batch of time-attribute dao pills. I heard that you've refined such pills in the past, and that's why I've come to you. I have enough ingredients to refine ten time-attribute dao pills, and I would like you to refine five time-attribute dao pills for me. If you can do that, then I'm willing to part with this Water Divination Time Crystal," Ape 3 explained.

"What if I'm unable to refine five time-attribute dao pills?" Han Li asked.

"If you're unable to fulfill my request, then I'm afraid the deal will have to fall through," Ape 3 replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Even though he was capable of refining dao pills, refining five time-attribute dao pills using only ten batches of materials was extremely difficult, and he didn't have absolute confidence in his ability to fulfill such a tall order.

"I don't mean to be rude, but this deal is completely skewed in your favor. I'm providing all of the ingredients, and all you have to do is provide your pill refinement expertise. If you manage to successfully refine five time-attribute dao pills, then you can have this Water Divination Time Crystal. Even if you fail, you don't risk losing anything, so what could you possibly be hesitating about?" Ape 3 asked with a hint of displeasure in his voice.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Ape 3, I fully intend to take you up on your deal, it's just that I have some questions that I would like to have answered first," Han Li said.

Ape 3's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he prompted, "Go ahead."

"Do you have a minimum tier requirement for the time dao pills refined?" Han Li asked.

"Of course. They must at least be second-tier dao pills, but rest assured, the primary ingredients that I've provided to you contain immense time law powers, enough to refine even third-tier dao pills," Ape 3 replied with a smile, and Han Li nodded in response.

"If you have any questions or concerns, then please state them now. I don't want there to be any misunderstandings that could result in this deal falling through," Ape 3 continued.

"Fellow Daoist Ape 3, I can tell that you're also very well-versed in the art of pill refinement, so I'm sure that you're aware that luck plays a very important role in pill refinement. Successfully refining five dao pills using ten batches of materials is a very tall order, even for the most seasoned Dao Pill Masters.

“I'll be sure to do my best, but if I fail, then would you be willing to accept however many dao pills I'm able to successfully refine, in addition to a sum of Immortal Origin Stones for the Water Divination Time Crystal? I'm willing to offer three times the market price for the crystal on top of the dao pills that I manage to successfully refine," Han Li requested in an earnest manner.

"I'm afraid I must refuse. I never go back on my word, so if you want my Water Divination Time Crystal, then you'll have to fulfill my request. If you fail, then I won't sell the crystal to you even if you offer me ten times the price," Ape 3 replied in a firm and unyielding manner.

Chapter 1160: Pill Tribulation

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he proposed, "How about this? If I only manage to refine less than four dao pills, then that will be the end of the matter. However, if I manage to refine four dao pills, would you be willing to sell the Water Divination Time Crystal to me?"

"I already told you that I won't accept anything less than five time-attribute dao pills for my Water Divination Time Crystal. If you insist on continuing to try and alter the terms of our agreement, then let's end discussions right here," Ape 3 replied in a cold voice.

"Fine, we'll do as you say then," Han Li sighed.

Ape 3's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he swept a sleeve through the air, upon which a storage ring and a white jade slip appeared in the item teleportation array in front of Han Li.

Han Li picked up the ring and the jade slip, then injected his spiritual sense into the latter.

The jade slip contained a dao pill recipe, and it was one that was completely different from the dao pill that he had refined in the past. The primary ingredient was something similar to Water Divination Time Crystals, while most of the other ingredients were also different, but the relationships between the ingredients were roughly the same as the ones in the previous pill recipe.

This came as quite a relief to Han Li. As long as the relationships between the ingredients hadn't changed too drastically, he would be able to make use of his prior dao pill refinement experience.

He then picked up the storage ring and inspected its contents to discover that it contained ten batches of ingredients, all of which were abundant with spiritual power.

"I'll be sure to get started as soon as possible. Is there a time limit that you'd like to impose?" Han Li asked.

"Just have them ready within ten years," Ape 3 replied, then instantly vanished from the spot, seemingly still a little displeased with Han Li.

Han Li wasn't offended by this. Instead, he was rather intrigued by Ape 3's personality. It was quite rare to see someone so frank and genuine in the Immortal Realm.

Han Li picked up the jade slip again, then closed his eyes to analyze its contents while simulating the pill refinement process in his mind.

Close to a year later, Han Li opened his eyes as he gently exhaled.

Over the course of the past year, he had studied the new pill refinement method to extremely painstaking detail and run through the pill refinement process repeatedly through his mind countless times.

Last time, nine batches of ingredients had been prepared for him, and he only had to succeed once, whereas he had to succeed five out of ten times on this occasion, amounting to a far higher level of difficulty.

Thankfully, both his pill refinement expertise and cultivation base were also significantly improved compared with last time, so he was relatively confident in his ability to complete the task.

With that in mind, he drifted out of the Flower Branch domain to arrive in the room outside.

After that, he dispelled the entrance to the Flower Branch domain, then released the Essence Fire Child.

"Stay here and keep a lookout. If any powerful enemies attack the convoy, kill them to ensure the convoy's safety," Han Li instructed.

The Essence Fire Child was becoming more and more intelligent of late, and it immediately nodded in response while patting its own chest, seemingly telling Han Li that he could count on it.

Han Li patted the Essence Fire Child on the head, then emerged from his room as a faint shadow and flew away into the distance without alerting anyone.

It would be impossible to conceal the pill tribulations brought on by the refinement of dao pills, and he didn't want the primordial beings in the convoy to see that.

After departing from the convoy, Han Li quickly picked out a peaceful and secluded mountain, then dug out a crude cave abode and set up several layers of restrictions around it before commencing the pill refinement process.

......

A black cloud was racing through the sky over the primordial land, and it contained an almighty primordial army consisting of all types of demon beasts of all types of different descriptions. At the very least, there were tens of thousands of demon beasts in the dark cloud, over half of which were tiger-like demon beasts, and the rest of the demon beasts all seemed to be rather fearful of these tiger-like creatures.

At the center of the cloud was a black throne, seated upon which was a white-haired young man with a hostile expression. The young man appeared to be completely identical to a human cultivator, with no visible demonic physical traits.

Standing around him were seven or eight powerful demon beasts, all of which were at the peak-High Zenith Stage.

"Congratulations, Young Master! The fact that our chief has sent you to participate in the blood inheritance ceremony on his behalf clearly indicates that he's already deemed you to be the next chief of our Zouwu Tribe!" a brawny man that was built like an iron pagoda said with a fawning smile.

The man had yellow tiger stripes on his face, indicating that he was a tiger demon.

"Out of all of Father's children, I possess the most potent Taowu bloodline, so he should've chosen me as his heir long ago! He must be going senile to have delayed the decision for so long!" the young man snapped in a cold and resentful manner.

"I'm sure our chief must've had his reasons," the tiger demon said in a hesitant manner.

"It's all because that senile old fart was constantly being swayed by my meddlesome siblings! If it isn't for the immense pressure from the Heavenly Court and my successful breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage, he would most likely still be in a state of indecision!" the young man harrumphed coldly.

"Now that you've reached the Great Encompassment Stage, none of your siblings can even begin to compare with you, so you can rest easy now, Young Master," a lion-like demon beast said.

"I still can't rest easy yet. My siblings have the support of many of our tribe's elders, so I can't afford to be complacent," the young man replied with a shake of his head.

"You're right, Young Master," the tiger demon agreed with a nod.

"In any case, no matter what they do, once I completely awaken my Taowu bloodline during the blood inheritance ceremony, none of them will be able to oppose me," the young man harrumphed coldly.

"Your foresight is truly unmatched, Yung Master," all of the powerful demons around the young man praised in unison.

A faint smile appeared on the young man's face in the face of everyone's collective praise, but right as he was about to say something, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he turned in a certain direction.

Everyone else quickly sensed something in that direction as well, and they turned to discover a vast expanse of radiant, golden light on the distant horizon, giving off formidable law power fluctuations alongside bursts of thunderous rumbling.

"What's going on over there? Is someone making a breakthrough?" a white elephant demon asked.

"No, this is not a phenomenon triggered by a breakthrough. Instead, someone's refining dao pills over there, and they're time dao pills to boot! I was just thinking about what offering I should make to the True Spirit King, the timing could not have been any more perfect!" the young man said with an excited expression, then sprang out of the black cloud as a streak of white light, speeding directly toward the golden light.

The young man was extraordinarily fast, and he quickly flew onto the scene before concealing himself in a white cloud in the distance.

A large section of the sky up ahead had been illuminated a bright golden color, and vast law power fluctuations were surging out of the golden clouds, causing all of the world's origin qi within a radius of millions of kilometers to ripple violently.

At the same time, the golden section of the sky felt incredibly heavy, and even the mountains down below were trembling incessantly, as if they were unable to bear the tremendous pressure.

All of a sudden, an enormous, golden vortex emerged within the golden clouds, and a beam of blinding, golden light that was imbued with devastating time law powers came crashing down toward a small mountain down below.

The white-haired young man could see that the mountain was surrounded by layers of restrictions, and a hint of fierce killing intent instantly flashed through his eyes as he came to the realization that there was an immortal region cultivator here.

However, he then took a deep breath to forcibly suppress his killing intent.

Right at this moment, a mountain that was thousands of feet in size appeared above the small mountain amid a flash of spiritual light.

The mountain was golden in color and etched with countless golden and gray runes, all of which were glowing radiantly with golden and gray light.

It was the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain!

The beam of golden light that was descending out of the heavens crashed down onto the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain with an earth-shattering boom, but the mountain was able to withstand the pillar of pill tribulation golden light with only a slight shudder.

However, that was far from the end of the pill tribulation. Shortly thereafter, another pillar of golden light that was far thicker than the previous one came crashing down from the heavens, and another earth-shattering boom rang out as much of the golden and gray light emanating from the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain was scattered.

Before the scattered golden and gray light was able to completely recover, another thick pillar of golden light came crashing down from the golden clouds.

This pillar of golden light was far more powerful than the previous two, giving off time law power fluctuations that were several times more potent, and the golden and gray light emanating from the golden mountain instantly faded away upon impact.

With the protective layer of golden and gray light eradicated, the pillar of golden light was able to strike the mountain itself, piercing over a hundred feet deep into the mountain before finally fading away.

The golden mountain was sent plummeting out of the sky, but it only descended several hundred feet before it was able to steady itself again. On top of that, another layer of golden and gray light reappeared over its surface in a span of mere seconds, and it appeared to be largely unscathed.

What a formidable pill treasure! It looks like it can withstand even fifth or sixth tier pill tribulations!

The white-haired young man's eyes lit up with excitement once again, and this time, his excitement was tinged with more than a hint of greed.

Chapter 1161: Crushing Victory

After releasing those three pillars of golden light, the golden cloud had finally exhausted all of its power, and it quickly dissipated, returning the sky to its original state.

The golden mountain rapidly shrank down before descending out of the sky, but right at this moment, countless white threads emerged out of thin air directly beneath it without any warning, and the mountain was instantly ensnared by the mass of white threads.

As a result, all of its downward momentum was arrested, and it was completely immobilized and suspended in mid-air.

At the same time, a vast expanse of white light appeared above the mountain, then transformed into a gargantuan white claw that came swooping down from above.

The space beneath the claw began to collapse, forming a huge black hole that threatened to devour the golden mountain whole like a gaping mouth.

All of a sudden, the golden mountain began trembling violently, and the rays of light that were as sharp as sword qi shot out of the mountain, hurtling toward the surrounding white threads and the giant, white claw.

The rays of light were incredibly sharp, able to tear through the space in its path with ease, but the white threads were extraordinarily resilient, remaining completely unscathed in the face of the storm of golden light. As for the white claw, the rays of golden light weren't even able to reach it before they were devoured by the black hole beneath the claw.

Right as the golden mountain was about to be caught by the massive, white claw, a burst of radiant, golden light suddenly erupted into the air from the mountain down below, then rapidly elongated to form a fiery, golden dragon that let loose a thunderous, draconic roar.

In the blink of an eye, it arrived in front of the golden mountain, the golden dragon coiled itself around the mountain, encompassing all of the white threads within its own body.

The white threads began flashing with white light, but the white light was quickly smothered by the golden flames, and all of a sudden, the white threads began extremely frail, burning away just like any normal silken threads would.

Immediately thereafter, the fiery, golden dragon sprang up and crashed violently into the giant, white claw, tearing it apart with ease before causing it to explode violently.

On top of that, nine bursts of fire simultaneously erupted out of the golden dragon's body, and they transformed into nine slightly smaller fiery dragons that pounced in unison onto what appeared to be nothing more than empty space.

A violent explosion of golden light ensued as that patch of space was shattered violently before being inundated by a sea of golden flames, which burned so intensely that the shattered space was beginning to display signs of melting.

A figure stumbled out of thin air before flying away into the distance. It was none other than the white-haired young man, and in the blink of an eye, he was already several dozen kilometers away.

His clothes were in tatters, and half of his body had also been charred black, as had most of his head of white hair, giving him a very sorry appearance.

At the same time, Han Li flew out of the mountain down below, and the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain quickly flew back up his sleeve at his behest.

Back in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, the roof of the golden palace where the High Zenith Pills had been held had a very similar pill-tribulation-transcending ability as the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain.

After the palace collapsed, Han Li had taken its roof, which he had then fused into the Integrated Five Extremes Mountain to significantly enhance its power.

"How dare you! Do you know who I am?" the white-haired young man roared in a furious voice as bright, white light erupted out of his body, and a white "王" character appeared on his forehead. [1]

The burns on his body began to rapidly heal, while bright, scythe-like claws emerged from his fingertips, and a pair of large, white wings appeared on his back, while his aura swelled drastically.

A tremendous, Great Encompassment Stage aura erupted out of his body, sending incredibly powerful shockwaves sweeping through the air in all directions.

Even Han Li couldn't help but stumble back a couple of steps in the face of these violent shockwaves.

Before he had a chance to steady himself, the white-haired young man abruptly vanished from the spot, only to reappear behind Han Li an instant later before thrusting his sharp claws viciously at Han Li's heart from behind.

Rings of white light were proliferating out of his sharp claws, giving off bursts of peculiar law power fluctuations that crackled and popped in the air like firecrackers.

The claws were able to tear through space with ease, gouging out a pair of large black holes.

However, right as the claws were about to reach Han Li, an antiquated golden lamp suddenly appeared before them without any warning.

Han Li had also turned around to face his assailant, and a wave of golden flames erupted out of the lamp at his behest, separating him from the white-haired young man before sweeping toward the latter.

Having just experienced the power of the eon flames, the white-haired young man didn't dare to rush headfirst into them again, so he was forced to stop in his tracks with a look of alarm and frustration on his face.

He was frustrated because the immortal region cultivator's cultivation base was clearly inferior to his own, yet that powerful immortal treasures of his made him completely untouchable.

At the same time, he was alarmed by the fact that Han Li was able to keep up with the speed of his attack.

The Taowu was a primordial being renowned for its incredible speed, and there weren't many tribes in the entire primordial land that could compete with it in that regard.

Not only did the white-haired young man possess the Taowu bloodline, he was also a Great Encompassment cultivator, so he had grown accustomed to being able to strike down his opponents with just a single blow, yet a mere human cultivator was somehow able to keep up with his speed.

Right as the white-haired young man was about to spring back to distance himself from the golden flames, a wave of golden ripples surged out from within the flames, instantly encompassing the white-haired young man within it.

The white-haired young man was instantly immobilized as a wave of formidable time law power fluctuations washed over him. An alarmed look appeared on his face as he prepared to unleash his power to free himself from the golden ripples, but before he was able to do so, a fiery, golden dragon crashed into him with tremendous force before transforming into a radiant, golden sun that exploded violently.

The nearby space was torn to shreds by an incredibly formidable burst of law power fluctuations, and the white-haired young man's body was also torn to pieces.

Despite this, he was able to survive, and a furious roar erupted out of his body, while a burst of dazzling, white light shot out of his body, revealing itself to be a white boat.

The boat was etched with countless primordial characters, as well as an image of countless beasts bowing in reverence.

An enormous burst of time law powers that wasn't inferior in the slightest to that of the Essence Fire Raven's white bead erupted out of the white boat, enveloping the white-haired young man's body before racing away into the distance.

The golden ripples released by the Mantra Treasured Axis were torn apart, while the white quickly vanished into the distant sky as a white shadow.

"You'll pay for this!"

The white-haired young man's resentful voice rang out in the distance, while Han Li looked on with a calm expression, making no effort to set off in pursuit as he knew that the white boat was far too fast for him to catch.

Defeating a Great Encompassment cultivator so easily should've been a source of great pride for any peak-High Zenith cultivator, yet Han Li displayed no reaction as he drew the Eon Divine Lamp back into his grasp.

Even though the white-haired young man was a Great Encompassment cultivator, his cultivation base was rather unstable, indicating that he had only recently reached the Great Encompassment Stage. On top of that, he had made a fatal error of voluntarily getting close to Han Li, thereby sealing his own defeat.

Right at this moment, a black cloud that was filled with all types of demon beasts appeared in the distance. It seemed that they were all allies of the white-haired young man, and the black cloud was racing toward Han Li with unstoppable might.

However, as soon as all of the demon beasts in the black cloud witnessed what had just become of the white-haired young man, the black cloud instantly stopped in its tracks, following which it veered away sharply, fleeing the scene in the same direction as the white-haired young man.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, but made no attempt to pursue the black cloud, either.

Even though he was able to defeat the white-haired young man using the Eon Divine Lamp, unleashing the lamp's power had expended most of his immortal spiritual power, so he was naturally unwilling to involve himself in any further conflicts.

After taking a pill to aid in his immortal spiritual power recovery, he set off in pursuit of the convoy belonging to the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe and the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe.

With the Essence Fire Raven still in the convoy, Han Li didn't have to worry about not being able to track it down.

It only took Han Li close to a month to catch up to the convoy, and he snuck back into his cabin on the flying boat without attracting any attention.

The Essence Fire Raven informed him that the convoy hadn't encountered any major peril during his absence, to which Han Li nodded in response before re-entering the Flower Branch domain.

After that, he put on his Reincarnation Palace palace and began attempting to contact Ape 3.

Shortly thereafter, a projection of Ape 3 appeared before him amid a flash of red light.

"Why have you contacted me so urgently, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5?" Ape 3 asked in a rather cold voice, but there was a clear glimmer of hope in his eyes.

Han Li offered no response as he flipped a hand over to produce a jade box, within which were five longan-sized golden pills.

Waves of rippling golden light were surging out of the pills before proliferating outward in all directions, and each pill had three golden dao patterns on their surface, all of which were giving off incredibly profound time law power fluctuations.

"Are those the dao pills I asked for?" Ape 3 exclaimed as his eyes lit up.

Once again, Han Li offered no response, letting the dao pills do the talking for him.

In order to refine these five dao pills, he had pulled out all the stops, testing his own pill refinement expertise to its limits while also using all of the auxiliary abilities at his disposal.

[1]. 王 translates directly to king in Chinese, and in China, it's often said that the patterns on a tiger's forehead are rather similar in appearance to the 王 character.

[Back]

Chapter 1162: Eight Plains

As Ape 3 continued to examine the five pills, the surprise and elation in his eyes only grew more and more pronounced.

"You truly are an exceptional pill refinement master, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5. To think that it only took you half the allotted time to refine these five time dao pills. I am in awe," Ape 3 said as he cupped his fist in an admiring salute.

"You said that I had to have them ready within ten years, so I naturally had no time to waste. On top of that, luck was on my side as well. Take a look and see if you're satisfied with the pills," Han Li said with a faint smile as he placed the jade box into the item teleportation array before making a hand seal, and the box instantly vanished before reappearing in front of Ape 3, who immediately picked it up before conducting a close examination of the five dao pills one by one.

"There's nothing wrong with the pills, and all five of them are third tier dao pills, which is much better than the outcome I anticipated. I'll throw in a million extra Immortal Origin Stones on top of the Water Divination Time Crystal for your brilliant work," Ape 3 said with a pleased nod.

"There's no need for any additional compensation. We agreed for you to give me the Water Divination Time Crystal in exchange for five time dao pills, so it wouldn't be right for me to take anything more from you," Han Li replied in a principled manner, and Ape 3's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this.

"It seems like you're a man after my own heart, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5. If you're not opposed to the idea, I would love to befriend you. I don't have your pill refinement expertise, but I do have some connections that are particularly useful in gathering all types of rare materials, so I'm not completely useless," Ape 3 chuckled.

"That sounds perfect to me," Han Li replied with a smile.

Even though not much interaction had taken place between the two of them, the fact that Ape 3 was able to bring out that Water Divination Time Crystal and ten batches of time dao pill ingredients indicated that he did indeed have some avenues of time law material acquisition.

He had refused the offer of a million additional Immortal Origin Stones precisely because he wanted to befriend Ape 3 to see if he could acquire more time law materials through him, so things had played out exactly as planned.

"Now that I've obtained these five dao pills, I need to go and arrange some things right away, so I won't chat with you any longer, Fellow Daoist Dragon 5. If you ever visit Nine Origins City, make sure to come find me!" Ape 3 said.

Nine Origins City!

Han Li's expression changed ever so slightly upon hearing this.

He had heard of this city from Lan Yan, and it was a huge city near the Nine Origins Temple, as well as one of the largest cities in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region. Could it be that Ape 3 was from the Nine Origins Temple?

Ape 3 sent the Water Divination Time Crystal to Han Li through the item teleportation array, following which the communication was quickly cut off.

Han Li removed his Reincarnation Palace mask, and a pleased smile appeared on his face as he looked down at the Water Divination Time Crystal in his hand. He then immediately channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, conjuring up that golden ring to encircle the crystal.

The Water Divination Time Crystal quickly disintegrated into countless water-droplet-shaped specks of golden light, which then transformed into forty-one time law threads, all of which wrapped themselves around the Clear Time Vial.

With this influx of time law threads, his time law powers had almost recovered to their peak.

Han Li closed his eyes as he summoned his five time-attribute law treasures, and he was very happy to see that they were revolving around him in a far smoother fashion than before.

After stowing the five time-attribute law treasures away, he pulled out the Almighty Sword Array Diagram and continued to study it intently.

He didn't know what was awaiting him on Eight Plains Mountain, so he couldn't afford to rest for even a single moment.

The array diagram hovered above his head, giving off a layer of gentle light that enshrouded his entire body.

Profound sword array permutations flowed out of the array diagram and through Han Li's heart, rapidly deepening his understanding of the Almighty Sword Array.

Several more years passed by in a flash, and Eight Plains Mountain finally appeared on the distant horizon.

......

The primordial land was an unfathomably massive place, but it had been segmented into extremely irregularly shaped areas due to the presence of all of the immortal regions.

Eight Plains Mountain was a very special place in the primordial land in that out of all of the primordial land's countless mountain ranges and rivers, most of them originated from Eight Plains Mountain.

Hence, it was no exaggeration to say that Eight Plains Mountain was the leader of all of the primordial land's mountain ranges and rivers.

It was also exactly because of this that Eight Plains Mountain was the site where the alliance had been forged between the eight True Spirit Kings in an attempt to put an end to the chaotic, war-torn era of the primordial land, and the mountain had since become the holy mountain of the primordial land.

On the summit of Eight Plains Mountain stood a circular palace that was constructed from a black stone material.

The palace was sealed off on all four sides, and at its very center was a dark red brazier that was around half the height of an adult human. Burning inside the brazier was a golden flame that was casting countless shadows onto the surrounding walls.

Placed around the palace were eight stone chairs that were very simplistic in design, looking much like the crude stone chairs that one would expect to find in rural mortal villages.

Behind each chair stood a stone statue that was around ten feet tall, most of which depicted menacing beasts, but one of them was different from the rest.

This statue resembled a white lion with a puffy mane and a pair of horns on its head. It had a pair of friendly-looking eyes, and trailing behind it was a long and thick tail, which was coiled to resemble a pristine white cloud.

While all of the other chairs were empty, the stone chair in front of this statue was currently occupied by a white-robed middle-aged man with skin as fair as jade and a set of handsome facial features. His eyes resembled a pair of bottomless ponds, while each of his pupils was bordered by a ring of faint, golden light, much like reflections of bright moons within the ponds.

The man had a pair of horns on his head that were curved backward, and there was a small goatee on his chin that wasn't very long, lending a bit of exuberance to his otherwise stoic facial features.

At this moment, the man was holding a bamboo scroll, but his gaze was fixed on the brazier at the center of the palace with a rather indecisive look on his face.

Moments later, he turned his gaze away from the brazier in a pensive manner.

It was back in this very palace that he and the other True Spirit King had forged an alliance to bring peace to the primordial land for the first time in its history. However, right now, he was the only True Spirit King left.

He was the most intelligent of the eight True Spirit Kings, Bai Ze.

It was said that he was the one who bad brought about the eight king alliance in the first place.

After that, he and the Ink-Eyed Pixiu had worked together to establish a set of basic laws for the primordial land, and only then was the era of widespread chaos finally left behind.

"Back then, I had to go through so much trouble to gather all of you in one place, yet now, all of you have either left or died, leaving this whole mess behind for me to deal with on my own. How is that fair?" Bai Ze complained as he swept his gaze over the seven empty chairs in the palace.

A wry smile then appeared on his face as he sighed, "Over the years, the primordial flame has been burning weaker and weaker, while unrest continues to brew in the entire Immortal Realm. Our primordial land will most likely inevitably be swept up in the shifting tides, so the Asura Blood Gates will have to be opened, and all of you will have no choice but to come back."

Bai Ze seemed to be rather pleased at this thought, and a smile appeared on his face as he stroked his own goatee.

......

At the foot of Eight Plains Mountain stood a black stone city.

The city's walls were over a thousand feet tall, and at the moment, its entrance was extremely busy, with one convoy after another entering the city in an unbroken stream.

There was a rather small convoy present, and it would've normally been very unremarkable, but it was made to appear quite out of place by all of the massive convoys around it.

Sang Tu was standing in front of a carriage in the convoy with a concerned look on his face, and he rubbed his hands together nervously as he said, "We're about to reach Primordial Garrison City, Senior Shi. The checks conducted at the city gate are very stringent, and our two tribes most likely aren't of sufficient status to be granted entry, so we'll need you to show yourself, Senior."

Han Li was naturally the one seated in the carriage.

He had concealed his own aura on the entire journey here, and only when the convoy had been attacked by powerful demons had he displayed his power, striking down those demons with incredible ease.

As a result, the two primordial tribes had developed a great deal of awe and veneration toward him.

After all, power was respected even more so in the primordial land than in the Immortal Realm.

Sang Tu and Yun Bao were unable to see anything wrong with Han Li's true spirit bloodline, but it would be very difficult to fool someone more powerful, and if it were exposed that he was a human, that would inevitably attract a lot of unnecessary trouble.

Han Li was here to do something important, not to start trouble for himself.

"It's fine, I'll step in if required," Han Li said in a calm manner, and Sang Tu felt very much reassured upon hearing this.

Having witnessed Han Li's displays of power over the course of their journey here, he and Yun Bao had become very trusting of and dependent on him.

He took a glance at Yun Bao, and the latter gave him a nod, following which the convoy continued onward.

Having been traveling together for so long, their relationship had improved significantly, and some tacit understanding had developed between them.

At around dusk, the convoy finally arrived at the city gate, where it was stopped by a pair of eagle-headed humanoid guards, each of which was wielding a halberd.

"Which tribes are you from?" one of them asked.

Chapter 1163: Barred from Entry

"We... We're from the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe and the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe," Sang Tu replied in a nervous manner.

The guard was rather taken aback to hear this, and he turned to his companion with an inquisitive look in his eyes.

"I've never heard of those two tribes. They don't seem to be among the top one hundred primordial tribes," the latter said with a shake of his head.

"We are a pair of small tribes on the territory of the Earth Dragon Tribe, so it's no surprise that you haven't heard of us," Yun Bao said, and it was clear that he was also feeling very anxious.

Both of the guards' expressions darkened slightly upon hearing this.

"Don't you know what's happening on Eight Plains Mountain at the moment? Hurry up and go back to where you came from!" one of the guards snapped with a dismissive wave.

"We're aware that the blood inheritance ceremony is going to be held on Eight Plains Mountain, and we're here to take part in the ceremony," Sang Tu hurriedly said.

A chorus of raucous laughter instantly rang out in response.

At this moment, another convoy had just arrived at the neighboring city gate, and it consisted of around seventy to eighty horned ape-like creatures, all of which were clad in suits of copper armor.

They were all extremely tall and imposing, standing at over twice the height of Sang Tu, and they were observing the pair of small tribes with mocking sneers on their faces.

Sang Tu took a glance at them before hurriedly averting his gaze. This was the Qing Ape Tribe, one of the top one hundred primordial tribes and one that was renowned for its bloodlust and aggression.

One of the eight former True Spirit Kings, the Zhuyan, had left behind four children, which gave rise to four different tribes, and the most powerful of those tribes was none other than the Qing Ape Tribe.

In contrast with the discriminatory treatment directed at the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe and the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe, the guards at the other city gate were far more polite to the Qing Ape Tribe, allowing them through without conducting any checks.

"Hurry up and get out of here!" the two guards at the city gate dismissed in an impatient manner.

"We've brought a bloodline descendant of one of the eight True Spirit Kings with us, so we are entitled to enter the city," Sang Tu revealed, having been backed into a corner.

The pair of guards clearly faltered slightly upon hearing this, and before they had a chance to respond, a thunderous roar suddenly rang out from nearby.

"You've brought with you a descendant of a True Spirit King bloodline, you say?"

Sang Tu shuddered as he turned to discover a Qing Ape being with a scar on his face approaching them with a furious expression.

Sang Tu hurriedly lowered his head, yet before he had a chance to explain, he felt a burst of tremendous force crash into his chest, sending him flying back through the air.

He crashed heavily against the city wall behind him, then slowly slid down onto the ground with blood gushing out of his mouth.

Yun Bao immediately turned to help him, only to be kicked to the ground as well, and the Qing Ape being stomped down onto him with a derisive expression as he scoffed, "You expect me to believe that a pair of pathetic little tribes like yours are in possession of an heir of one of the True Spirit King bloodlines?"

Under the force of the Qing Ape being's stomp, Yun Bao wasn't able to utter any sound aside from a strangled gurgle.

The Qing Ape being possessed early-High Zenith Stage power, and that was far too much for him to contend with.

"Despicable scum!" the Qing Ape being spat in a derisive fashion as he raised his foot in preparation to stomp Yun Bao to death.

None of the bystanders attempted to intervene. Instead, they were all eager to see the bloodshed that was to come.

Sang Tu struggled to his feet before attempting to rush to Yun Bao's aid, only to be stopped in his tracks by the two guards.

"Get out of here! You're going to get yourself killed!" one of them warned in an urgent voice, but Sang Tu paid no heed to the warning as his body abruptly swelled to several times its original size, and a giant, black stone ax appeared in his grasp.

However, before he had a chance to do anything, the two guards also swelled drastically in size before laying the blades of their halberds against Sang Tu's neck, and one of them yelled in an enraged voice, "If you have a death wish, then you should've just said so from the beginning!"

Meanwhile, the Qing Ape was already beginning to stomp down toward Yun Bao's head, clearly intending to kill him.

All of the Silver Horn Rhinoceros and Cloud Spot Tiger beings immediately prepared to rush to his aid, even though doing so was sure to spell certain death for them, when a cold voice suddenly rang out from the carriage behind them.

"I wouldn't do that if I were you..."

The voice wasn't very loud, but it was clearly audible to everyone present, and all of the bystanders immediately turned to the carriage with intrigued expressions.

The Qing Ape being faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which he continued to stomp down upon Yun Bao as he sneered, "Oh yeah? What are you going to do about it?"

A bolt of silver lightning shot out of the carriage, instantly arriving before the Qing Ape being.

Before anyone had a chance to see what was happening, the bolt of lightning exploded, and a jolt of numbness ran through the Qing Ape being's entire body as he was sent flying back through the air like a cannonball before crashing into the city wall with a resounding boom.

All of the bystanders were stunned to see this, and they hurriedly turned their attention to Yun Bao's savior, who was naturally none other than Han Li.

He crouched down to help Yun Bao up from the ground, then handed the latter a pill before turning to Sang Tu with his brows slightly furrowed.

It was clear that Han Li was not to be messed with, and the pair of guards hurriedly stepped away from Sang Tu.

Sang Tu stumbled over to Han Li's side, and the latter handed him a pill as well before turning his gaze to the Qing Ape being.

Qing Ape beings possessed tremendous physical constitutions, and even though he had crashed into the city wall with such immense force that cracks had appeared on the wall, he remained largely unscathed as he dusted himself off before rising to his feet.

Han Li didn't want to escalate the conflict any further, so he continued to observe the Qing Ape being with an indifferent expression instead of unleashing any further attacks.

"You're from the Lightning Bird Tribe! Are those two your subordinates?"

The Qing Ape being didn't attack, either, and it was clear that he was a little apprehensive of the Lightning Bird Tribe.

Just like the Qing Ape Tribe, the Lightning Bird Tribe had also inherited the bloodline of one of the eight True Spirit Kings, namely the Kun Peng. Overall, the Lightning Bird Tribe was slightly inferior in power to the Qing Ape Tribe, but it had an extremely powerful and protective chief.

Throughout history, there had been many cases of this chief personally avenging any juniors of his tribe that he held in high regard and had been wronged by others.

"We just want to enter the city, surely there's no need for such a serious conflict," Han Li said in a calm manner.

"I know a lot of people from the Lightning Bird Tribe, do you dare to tell me your name?" the Qing Ape being challenged.

Han Li paid no heed to him as he turned to the pair of guards and asked, "Can we enter the city now?"

"Of course, please go ahead," one of the guards hurriedly replied with a nod.

Han Li turned and made his way back to his carriage, while Sang Tu and Yun Bao were helped up by their subordinates as the convoy prepared to enter the city.

The Qing Ape being was furious at being ignored by Han Li, and he yelled, "I've never heard of a Lightning Bird being like you, so you must be some mixblood mongrel! Someone like you has no right to take part in the ceremony, either!"

For primordial beings, the matter of bloodline was one of extreme importance, and being denounced as a mixblood mongrel was sufficient cause for someone to engage the offender in a battle to the death.

However, Han Li was no primordial being, so the insult carried no sting of him. All he wanted was to enter Primordial Garrison City, then travel to Eight Plains Mountain to save Xiao Bai, so he remained unflustered as he continued to make his way toward his carriage.

However, in the eyes of all of the bystanders, this was a show of weakness and cowardice, and many of them began yelling for Han Li to leave in very unflattering terms.

The Qing Ape being was even more emboldened upon seeing this, and he sprang forward to grab at Han Li from behind as he yelled, "No mixblood mongrel is entering this gate on my watch!"

It was clear that he was striking with full intent to kill, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he heaved an internal sigh.

It seemed that an escalation of the conflict was simply unavoidable.

With that in mind, he swiveled around and made a grab for the Qing Ape being's fist while channeling his bloodline powers and starpower simultaneously.

Arcs of silver lightning sprang out of his body, forming a giant set of Lightning Bird talons that clashed violently against the Qing Ape being's fist.

An earth-shattering explosion rang out as gusts of fierce wind swept through the air in all directions.

Layers upon layers of silver lightning erupted outward incessantly, sending fist-sized balls of silver lightning flying in all directions, and all of the bystanders hurriedly rushed back in retreat.

Some of the nearby carriage-drawing wild beasts had also been stirred up into a panicked frenzy, and the entire scene devolved into complete chaos.

The Qing Ape being was quite surprised to see this. The Lightning Bird Tribe had always been renowned for its speed, and it was definitely inferior to the Qing Ape Tribe when it came to physical strength, yet somehow, Han Li's strength wasn't inferior to his own in the slightest.

Chapter 1164: Token

All of a sudden, a fierce look flashed through the Qing Ape being's eyes.

If he were to lose to a Lightning Bird being in a contest of strength, then he would be a disgrace to his own tribe.

With that in mind, he let loose a thunderous roar, and the horns on his head abruptly elongated significantly, while his body quickly swelled to twice its original size.

"Die!" the Qing Ape being roared as he swung his fist through the air with all his might, and Han Li was involuntarily forced back slightly by his tremendous strength.

However, immediately thereafter, he pushed off explosively against the ground with both feet, and his entire body shot directly upward like a lightning spear, knocking the Qing Ape being's fist aside with tremendous force.

In the blink of an eye, he had soared high up into the heavens, and he spread his arms much like a giant bird spreading its wings, following which a waterfall of silver lightning came cascading down from above.

The Qing Ape being had only just managed to steady himself after being barged into by Han Li when he looked up to see a giant Lightning Bird swooping down from above before crashing down upon him with mountainous force.

The Qing Ape being was knocked to the ground, following which the waterfall of silver lightning came crashing down upon him, charring his entire body black.

He laid on the ground while spasming uncontrollably, trying to struggle to his feet, but to no avail.

Meanwhile, Han Li merely reverted back to his human form, then made his way back to the carriage, where he observed the spasming Qing Ape being in an expressionless manner.

The Qing Ape being appeared to have sustained very severe injuries, but in reality, they were only inconsequential external injuries, that was a testament to just how formidable the physical constitutions of these Qing Ape beings were.

Han Li had no intention of taking his life, so he was content for the battle to end here.

Some time later, the numbness in the Qing Ape being's body finally abated, and he sat up to stare at Han Li with incredulity in his eyes.

"Wasn't he really arrogant just a moment ago? Why is he suddenly dumbstruck ape now?"

"That Lightning Bird senior must be some unknown mighty figure who spends all his time in seclusion. He must be serving as an elder in some powerful tribe."

All of the bystanders faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which everyone began jeering at the Qing Ape being while praising Han Li.

Sang Tu and Yun Bao were also looking at Han Li with excitement and admiration glowing in their eyes, and all hints of dissatisfaction that they had previously harbored toward him had completely evaporated.

It was clear that in their eyes, defeating an early-High Zenith Stage Qing Ape being so easily was nothing short of an unfathomable feat.

Han Li could see that the Qing Ape being had no intention of continuing the battle, so he turned and made his way back toward his carriage.

However, right at this moment, the bystanders' jeering voices abruptly cut off, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he turned around to discover another Qing Ape being approaching the scene.

This one was even more physically imposing than the previous one, and his aura was comparable with that of a peak-High Zenith cultivator.

"You're a disgrace to our tribe, Qing Chu!" the Qing Ape being reprimanded in a cold voice.

"Brother, I..."

"Piss off!"

Qing Chu was sent flying by a vicious slap from the Qing Ape being before he even had a chance to say anything.

"Is that the new blood heir of the Qing Ape Tribe?" someone exclaimed.

"That must be him! He's Qing Dian, the one with the purest Zhuyan bloodline to have emerged from the Qing Ape Tribe over the past one million years! I've heard that he's already been confirmed to be the next chief of the Qing Ape Tribe!" someone else said.

"Looks like we're in for a good show now!"

"Shhh! Don't be so loud! I've heard that he has a very fiery temper, so keep it down if you don't want to be killed!"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing all of these bystander remarks.

"My brother may be a useless piece of trash, but I can't just let you get away with beating him up. How do you want to do this? A fight to the death or until one of us yields?" Qing Dian asked.

A hint of exasperation welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this. After beating up the little brother, the older brother had come for vengeance. Was there going to be anyone else to come?

He had important matters to attend to, and he didn't have time for this nonsense.

Qing Dian waited for Han Li's response for a moment, but when it didn't come, he continued, "Forget it, let's keep it simple. How do you want to die?"

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon hearing this, and tiny arcs of lightning began to dance over his hands as he clasped them behind his back.

At this point, all of the bystanders had already fallen completely silent, and everyone was waiting with bated breath to see how long it would take for Qing Dian to kill Han Li.

Sang Tu and Yun Bao were sweating profusely, and it seemed that they were contemplating whether they should flee the scene before it was too late.

In their eyes, there was no way that Han Li would be a match for the next chief of the Qing Ape Tribe, and if Han Li were to fall, then their two tribes would surely follow.

Right as the tension in the air was reaching a peak, an exuberant voice suddenly rang out to break the tension.

"Is that you, Brother Rock?"

Han Li faltered slightly at the sound of this familiar voice, following which he turned to the city gate to discover a beautiful young woman in a white dress skipping her way toward him.

Her flawlessly gorgeous features carried a natural air of seduction, and all of the bystanders couldn't help but stare.

Even Qing Dian was slightly enraptured as his gaze fell upon the young woman, but at this moment, the young woman had eyes only for Han Li, and it seemed like no else existed to her.

"Le'er!" Han Li called out with a warm smile, and in the next instant, the young woman had already rushed headfirst into his arms.

All of the surrounding bystanders were furious to see this, and they were instantly so envious of Han Li that any admiration they had developed toward him for defeating Qing Chu had completely evaporated.

The young woman was none other than Liu Le'er, and her eyes were glowing with excitement as she asked, "What are you doing here, Brother Rock? You should've told me that you were coming here! I sensed your aura from inside the city, but I couldn't be sure if it was you. I came here just in case, and I'm really glad that I did!"

Han Li placed his hands on her shoulders, pushing her away slightly so that he could look her up and down, following which he smiled and gave an approving nod.

"You're all grown up now, no longer the little girl that used to ride on my shoulders."

Liu Le'er couldn't help but blush as she was reminded of the past, and all of the bystanders were even more enraptured to see this.

Even though she wasn't using any seductive techniques, just her mere presence alone was as intoxicating as fine wine.

Right at this moment, Qing Dian yelled in a disgruntled voice, "Where the hell did you come from? Get out of here!"

A hint of anger flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this. Not only had he been provoked without cause by these Qing Ape beings, his reunion with Liu Le'er was also being interrupted, and his patience was beginning to wear thin.

Right as he was planning to get rid of this eyesore, Liu Le'er suddenly placed a delicate hand onto his arm to stop him, then took a step toward Qing Dian as she extended an elegant curtsey.

She then flipped a hand over to produce a round, palm-sized scale as she said, "You're a fellow daoist of the Qing Ape Tribe, right? I presume you recognize this."

She raised the scale in her hand as she spoke so that Qing Dian could get a clearer look at it.

It was a white scale with layers of rippling patterns on its surface, and a hint of surprise appeared in Han Li's eyes at the sight of it.

The scale was identical to the one that he had been given by Lekima back when they had parted ways in the Eon Pagoda.

Many of the bystanders immediately extended respectful bows at the sight of the scale, and some had even fallen to their knees to kowtow in reverence.

The surprise in Han Li's eyes grew even more pronounced upon seeing this.

After extending a respectful bow, Qing Dian asked, "Why do you have a True Spirit King token? Could it be..."

"That's right, I'm a member of the Heavenly Fox Tribe," Liu Le'er replied with a bright smile.

"What is this scale, Le'er? It appears to be quite precious," Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"This Featherform Scale is a token that's unique to the True Spirit Kings, and there are only seven in existence, serving as representations of the True Spirit Kings' trust. Our Heavenly Fox Tribe has been serving the True Spirit King for a very long time, and we were rewarded with a Featherform Scale for our efforts, while I was fortunate enough to have been given the scale by the patriarch of our tribe," Liu Le'er explained, and Han Li was even more perplexed to hear this.

Why had Lekima given him something so important?

Chapter 1165: A Second Scale

Qing Dian seemed to have finally identified Liu Le'er upon seeing the Featherform Scale in her hand, but his expression only became even more hostile as he turned his gaze back to Han Li.

"This is a friend of mine, so please let bygones be bygones and allow them to enter the city with me," Liu Le'er said as she stowed the token away.

A mocking sneer appeared on Qing Dian's face upon hearing this.

"I've always heard that your Heavenly Fox Tribe likes to entangle itself with humans, it appears that those rumors are not unfounded. This man has clearly come to our primordial land with some sinister motives, yet you insist on protecting him. Could it be that your Heavenly Fox Tribe intends to betray the primordial land?"

Liu Le'er's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, but she remained calm and composed as she replied, "That's a completely unreasonable and unfounded accusation, Fellow Daoist."

She was well aware of how much all of the primordial tribes detested humans, so Qing Dian was clearly trying to turn everyone against Han Li by exposing his status as a human.

Sure enough, all of the bystanders' expressions instantly changed drastically upon hearing this, and some of them began observing Han Li through suspicious eyes, while some others were already glowering at him with open animosity.

Even Sang Tu and Yun Bao were looking at him with mixed emotions in their eyes.

They had been suspicious of Han Li's status in the past, but they had always been reluctant to acknowledge these suspicions. Not only was Han Li far too powerful for them to contend with, they also had no choice but to rely on him if they wanted to enter Primordial Garrison City.

On top of that, Han Li had just saved their lives not long ago, so they harbored a combination of fear, veneration, and gratitude toward him.

"Your name is Qing Dian, right? I suggest you keep your mouth shut if all you can spout are nonsensical accusations! How can you claim that I'm a human in spite of the true spirit bloodline in my body?" Han Li asked with a cold smile.

"Bloodlines don't necessarily have to be inherited. Humans often steal demon beast and even true spirit bloodlines for their cultivation, so just because you possess a true spirit bloodline doesn't prove anything. Also, you didn't display any reaction when she displayed her Featherform Scale, so it's clear that you have no respect for the True Spirit King, and that proves you're definitely not a primordial being!" Qing Dian sneered.

"I'll admit that your analysis is somewhat sound, but if I really were a human spy, then would I be in possession of this?" Han Li countered with a smile as he flipped a hand over to produce his own Featherform Scale.

"Another one!" someone in the crowd exclaimed.

"It's not a fake one, is it?"

"Could it be that he's also a trusted subordinate of the True Spirit King?"

Everyone was very much taken aback by what they had seen, including even Liu Le'er.

However, on this occasion, only a small number of bystanders extended respectful bows, while the rest looked on with suspicious expressions.

Qing Dian was also momentarily dumbstruck, following which he yelled, "That's clearly a counterfeit! There are only seven True Spirit King tokens in existence, how could two possibly just so happen to appear in the same place at once?"

"I'm sure you know full well whether the scale is counterfeit or not. Just like you said, there are only seven of these in existence, so who could've possibly created a counterfeit that's indistinguishable in both appearance and aura?" Liu Le'er countered.

Qing Dian faltered slightly upon hearing this, but he still refused to let Han Li through.

"I've already shown you the token, if you continue to stand in my way, then I'll have to get past you by force," Han Li threatened.

Qing Dian hesitated momentarily, following which a look of resolve suddenly appeared in Qing Dian's eyes as he rose to the challenge.

"I'd like to see you try!"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he swept his gaze over the surrounding area.

The brief hesitation that Qing Dian had displayed just now indicated that he had most likely received instructions from someone in secret.

Whoever was pulling the strings behind the scenes, the fact that they had instructed Qing Dian to stand his ground even after witnessing the token indicated that they were fully confident that Han Li was human, so they were most likely a Great Encompassment Stage being.

With that in mind, a hint of caution welled up in Han Li's heart as he communicated to Liu Le'er through voice transmission, "At the rate things are going, there's a very good chance that my identity is going to be exposed, so it won't be safe for you to be with me. Go back to the Heavenly Fox Tribe for now, and I'll find a way to contact you once I've gotten myself out of this mess."

To his surprise, Liu Le'er smiled as she replied, "Don't worry about me, Brother Rock, I'm no longer the defenseless little girl that I once was, and I can look after myself just fine."

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this, but he was then reassured by the thought that she had the support of the mighty Heavenly Fox Tribe behind her.

Intense envy welled up in Qing Dian's heart at the sight of the intimacy between Han Li and Liu Le'er, and he let loose a furious roar as he charged directly at Han Li.

With each step that he took, a dark red halo spread from beneath his foot, causing the entire city wall to tremble violently. All of the bystanders hurriedly rushed back in retreat, opening up a large area for Han Li, Liu Le'er, and Qing Dian.

Qing Dian's eyes had turned bright red, and a series of ancient, crimson patterns had appeared over the exposed sections of his skin, giving off a primordial aura of bloodlust.

At the same time, his body had swelled to around twice its original size, while his nose shrank down, and a pair of giant tusks protruded out of his mouth, giving him the appearance of a fearsome-looking ape.

In the face of the oncoming Qing Dian, Han Li stepped forward to position himself in front of Liu Le'er, and before she had a chance to do anything, she was sent flying back by a burst of gentle force, which carried her through the air before setting her down several thousand feet away.

At the same time, Han Li extended both hands forward, and countless arcs of silver lightning sprang forth before converging to form a pair of massive Lightning Bird talons, which clashed violently against Qing Dian's powerful fists.

Silver lightning erupted in all directions as Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, grabbing onto Qing Dian's fists with his hands before attempting to twist him to the ground.

However, Qing Dian remained completely unmoved, standing as firmly as a mountain.

"You really thought you could challenge me in strength? What a joke!" Qing Dian sneered as he withdrew his fists, and Han Li was unable to hold onto them, so he could only allow them to slip out of his grasp.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this. Out of his Twelve Awakening Transformations, his Lightning Bird form was outmatched in strength by his Giant Mountain Ape form, but it certainly wasn't weak, yet Qing Dian had established a clear advantage in this regard.

Before he had a chance to ponder this matter any further, Qing Dian was already swinging a fist at his head.

A burst of silver lightning flashed over Han Li's body, and he abruptly vanished from beneath Qing Dian's fist, then reappeared behind him an instant later.

At the same time, an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword appeared in his grasp, and he plunged it forcefully at the back of Qing Dian's neck.

The attack had come too fast for Qing Dian to turn around in time, but he let loose a thunderous roar, and the skin on the back of his neck suddenly turned a translucent red color.

A resounding boom rang out as countless arcs of golden lightning erupted in all directions, and a crimson halo suddenly surged out of the golden lightning before racing toward Han Li at an astonishing speed.

Han Li reflexively channeled his Reversal True Axis ability to evade the attack, and the crimson halo just barely glanced past him before striking the city wall behind him, causing it to shudder violently once again.

Han Li felt a sense of scorching pain from his shoulder, and he turned to discover that his robe there had been completely torn away, while the exposed section of his shoulder had turned a crimson color.

It was as if a layer of crimson lava were clinging to his shoulder, and it was slowly spreading to his forearm, having already burned through the True Extreme Film over his skin.

He then turned to discover that a hole had also been blasted into the city wall behind him, and bright, red lava was flowing down its surface.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as a layer of silver flames appeared over his hand, and he used it as a blade to shave away the crimson lava-like substance from his own shoulder bit by bit.

However, even after the substance had been removed, Han Li could still feel a type of peculiar power lingering in his wound there, slowing down his healing to a crawl.

"Don't try to best him in strength, Brother Rock! Let me help you!" Liu Le'er called out from afar, but Han Li shook his head at her, indicating that he was fine and telling her not to get involved.

Meanwhile, there was a hunch-backed elderly man standing on the city wall, looking down at Han Li with his hands clasped behind his back.

A formidable physical constitution and time law powers... Looks like this won't be easy for Dian'er...

The elderly man had a dark complexion, but a rather pale face, presenting a rather strange contrast. On top of that, his aura was extremely self-contained, making it seem as if he were just an ordinary, elderly mortal man.

Right at this moment, the space at the foot of the city wall suddenly became a little warped, and it appeared as if a layer of faint, red mist were permeating through the air.

Oh? If he's using even that ability, then it looks like this battle is as good as over, the elderly man thought to himself as a faint smile appeared on his face.

Chapter 1166: Another Reunion

With that in mind, the elderly man seemed to have lost interest in the battle, and he turned to depart.

However, he then suddenly seemed to have recalled something, and he communicated to Qing Dian through voice transmission, "You can kill that human if you want, but do not harm that Heavenly Fox girl."

After receiving an affirmative response from Qing Dian, the elderly man departed.

Emboldened by the elderly man's approval, a sinister grin appeared on Qing Dian's face as a cold gleam flashed over his protruding tusks.

All of a sudden, he let loose a thunderous roar, and a burst of red light erupted out of his mouth before forming a giant, crimson vortex.

The vortex was giving off bursts of formidable suction force that were acting upon Han Li, who had preemptively channeled his Reversal True Axis ability to get away, having already sensed that something was amiss.

However, as soon as he sprang into action, he immediately felt a numb sensation shoot through his shoulder where it had been wounded by the lava from earlier, and a burst of indescribable power began to rise up from within it, resonating with the suction force surging out of Qing Dian's mouth.

No matter where he went, the burst of strange power followed him, and the more time passed, the stronger the suction force became, attempting to drag Han Li into the crimson vortex.

Finally, the suction force became too much for Han Li to resist, and he was forcibly wrenched into the crimson vortex before vanishing into it.

"Brother Rock!" Liu Le'er exclaimed, but it was already too late.

She turned to Qing Dian with a furious expression, who looked back at her with a nonchalant grin.

The surrounding bystanders had erupted into a frenzy of chatter, while Sang Tu and Yun Bao were staring at each other with horrified expressions.

......

Meanwhile, Han Li had entered a strange space, and he was suspended in mid-air, surrounded by a pervasive, nauseating stench.

Up ahead was a waterfall of lava, while down below was a bubbling lake of lava.

Han Li took a moment to compose himself, then looked around to discover that the surrounding space wasn't very large, and there were dark red walls in all four directions with molten lava flowing over them.

He activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes to get a better look at his surroundings, upon which he discovered a system of blood vessels beneath the slightly irregular walls, and there was also immortal spiritual power flowing through them.

Could it be that I'm in his stomach right now? Did he just eat me? Han Li thought to himself as a peculiar look appeared on his face.

Right at this moment, the surrounding walls suddenly began to contract violently while compressing toward Han Li from all directions.

The flow of lava up above also became extremely turbulent, crashing down upon him with tremendous force and heat.

Han Li immediately swept a sleeve through the air, releasing thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which, in turn, released countless streaks of azure swordlight that erupted in all directions to fill the entire cramped space.

However, the surrounding walls remained completely unmoved, and as they continued to contract, the space around Han Li was shrinking further and further.

The waterfall of lava finally fell upon him from above, and it did so with immense weight, sending him plummeting down into the lava lake below.

His entire body was instantly inundated by scorching lava, striking him with unbearable pain.

He knew that if the surrounding space were to completely close, then he would sealed in this lava lake. Perhaps he would be able to survive in it for a short time, but there was no telling what could happen in the case of prolonged exposure.

With that in mind, his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords combined into one at his behest, then flew out of the lava lake to force open a path through the compressing walls.

Han Li shot out of the lava lake after the combined Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords with his Profound Heavenly Gourd in his hand, and a burst of green light surged out of the gourd to suck in the falling waterfall of lava.

Without the waterfall obstructing his path, Han Li was able to force his way through, and after rising up for roughly a thousand feet, he was finally able to emerge from the compressing walls, following which he flew over to a vacant area, directly in front of which was the falling waterfall of lava.

Under the protection of the Profound Heavenly Gourd, Han Li was able to fly through the waterfall, and he discovered that the area beyond it was even more spacious. There were two white stone pillars standing up ahead, and they seemed to be giving off bursts of restrictive power.

I've finally found a way out!

An elated look appeared on his face as he stowed his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and Profound Heavenly Gourd away, following which he began to observe the pair of white stone pillars with a contemplative expression.

......

Meanwhile, Liu Le'er was standing before Qing Dian in front of the city gate outside, and she interrogated, "What did you do with my brother? Why am I unable to sense his aura anymore?"

"He's already entered the space in my stomach, and he'll be reduced to molten lava soon, so of course you can't sense his aura! How about I become your brother instead?" Qing Dian chortled as he looked down at Liu Le'er, who wasn't even half his height.

Instead of displaying any panic upon hearing this, Liu Le'er appeared to be quite relieved, and she lamented, "How unfortunate..."

Qing Dian thought that Liu Le'er was referring to Han Li, but the relieved look on her face left him feeling rather perplexed.

"You're going to regret swallowing Brother Rock," Liu Le'er said with a sympathetic expression. "Well, I suppose it's already too late for you to regret it."

A hint of foreboding instantly welled up in Qing Dian's heart upon hearing this, and in the next instant, a dull thump suddenly rang out from within his oral cavity, following which a burst of black light emerged.

Immediately thereafter, he abruptly lunged forward in an involuntary manner, almost falling flat on his face. Blood began gushing out of his mouth as one of his protruding tusks was snapped into two, then flew through the air like a scimitar before piercing into the city wall.

The burst of black light then flew out of Qing Dian's mouth before rapidly swelling in size, transforming into a devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

With his true spirit bloodlines channeled to the extreme, many of the surrounding bystanders were struck by the urge to bow in reverence to Han Li.

"I knew you'd be fine," Liu Le'er said with a warm smile, in spite of her surprise at Han Li's current form.

Han Li gave Liu Le'er a slight nod, then turned his gaze to Qing Dian, who had almost been driven mad with rage.

His tusks had been refined for countless years using a vast number of precious materials, and they were comparable to sixth tier immortal treasures. They were vital to sealing the space in his body, and now that one of them had been snapped, it was going to be extremely expensive to repair, so how could he not be furious?

A guttural roar of fury erupted out of his mouth as his body swelled rapidly in size, and his height quickly exceeded that of the city wall.

The dark red patterns on his body began to glow brightly, while his pupils turned a crimson color, and tendrils of pink mist began to emanate from his entire body.

Han Li didn't suppress his own aura any longer upon seeing this, channeling both his true spirit bloodlines and his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, and his stature also swelled rapidly until it wasn't inferior to Qing Dian's in the slightest.

All of the bystanders knew that the battle was about to reach a climax, and they hurriedly fled even further away.

However, right at this moment, a figure suddenly vaulted over the city wall, then descended out of the sky before landing on Qing Dian's shoulder.

In his enraged state, Qing Dian reflexively lashed out to swat at the figure that had just landed on his shoulder, but as soon as he caught sight of the figure, he immediately withdrew his own hand, then quickly reverted back to his original form.

The figure that had landed on Qing Dian's shoulder was a handsome, white-robed young man with an elegant disposition, and the man turned to Han Li as he greeted, "Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Han."

Han Li didn't recognize the man, but as soon as he detected the man's aura, a look of realization immediately appeared on his face.

As it turned out, the man was none other than Lekima.

All of the bystanders' expressions instantly changed drastically upon seeing this, and everyone, including even Qing Dian and Liu Le'er, hurriedly cupped their fists to extend respectful salutes toward the white-robed young man.

Thinking back to the Featherform Scale, Han Li was instantly able to guess Lekima's identity, and he quickly reverted back to his human form as well.

At this point, all of the rage had already faded from Qing Dian's eyes, and he was looking back and forth between Han Li and Lekima with a puzzled expression.

Chapter 1167: Past Events of the Heavenly Fox Tribe

"Looks like you're a more important figure than you let on, Fellow Daoist Lekima. I wasn't planning to come to the primordial land after we parted ways all those years ago, but it seems like fate has brought me here anyway," Han Li said with a smile.

"I left that Featherform Scale to you precisely because I thought it would come in useful for you when you came to visit our primordial land, and that's proven to be the right decision. Looks like your fate is intertwined with our primordial land whether you like it or not, Fellow Daoist Han!" Lekima chuckled.

"Speaking of the Featherform Scale, it doesn't seem to be all that useful. I displayed it just now, only to be denounced as a fraud," Han Li said as he took a meaningful glance at Qing Dian.

Lekima's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he smiled as he said, "I'm sure there must be some type of misunderstanding involved, isn't that right, Fellow Daoist Qing Dian?"

"Indeed, Young Master, it was all just a big misunderstanding," Qing Dian hurriedly replied as he clasped the side of his face where his tusk had been snapped.

"Seeing as it was a misunderstanding, let's all move on now that it's been cleared up. Go and recover your snapped tusk, I'm sure your patriarch will be able to repair it for you," Lekima said with a smile.

"Yes, Young Master," Qing Dian replied in a slightly reluctant manner, then pulled his snapped tusk out of the city wall before departing.

"I'm assuming there must be a reason why you came here, right, Fellow Daoist Han? If there's anything that I can help you with, please go ahead and tell me," Lekima said.

Han Li hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, but ultimately decided to tell Lekima about Xiao Bai.

A look of excitement appeared in Lekima's eyes after hearing Han Li's story, and he said, "If this adolescent beast that you speak of really does possess the bloodline of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu, then our primordial land will owe you a massive favor for his return!"

"That's not important to me. Xiao Bai is a cherished companion of mine, so I just want him to be saved," Han Li said in a serious manner.

"In that case, I'll take you to Eight Plains Mountain to see our True Spirit King right away," Lekima said.

However, Han Li was rather hesitant.

"Is there something wrong, Fellow Daoist Han?" Lekima asked.

"Meeting the True Spirit King is an important matter. I'm still a little shaken after what's happened here, so perhaps I'll meet with the True Spirit King some other day," Han Li replied with a smile.

Lekima could see Han Li's reluctance, and he said, "That's fine. In that case, you can come and stay in my manor for now, and I'll take you to see the True Spirit King when you're ready."

"Young Master, I've already invited Brother Rock to our Heavenly Fox Tribe," Liu Le'er interjected in an apologetic manner.

"So you're familiar with the little celestial maiden of the Heavenly Fox Tribe as well. Looks like yu're quite the womanizer, Fellow Daoist Han," Lekima chortled with mirth.

"It's not like that, Fellow Daoist, we're only..."

Lekima waved a hand to cut him off before he had a chance to explain, giving him a look that said, "I know what's going on here, you don't need to explain anything to me."

An exasperated look appeared on Han Li's face, while Liu Le'er was looking rather amused.

"By the way, the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe and the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe may only be a pair of small tribes, but they were the ones who first discovered Xiao Bai, and they also escorted him all the way here, so I think they should be rewarded," Han Li said.

"Rest assured, I'll personally see to it that those two tribes are rewarded for their efforts," Lekima promised, and Han Li cupped his fist in a grateful salute in response.

He then made his way over to Sang Tu and Yun Bao before telling them to go with Lekima.

The two chiefs were aware that their tribes were about to experience an imminent rise, and they were extremely grateful to Han Li, insisting on getting up to kowtow to him despite their injuries.

As they parted ways, Han Li returned the Featherform Scale to Lekima, but the latter insisted that he keep it.

"Keep it. I'll make it known that I personally bestowed the scale upon you, so something like this won't happen again," Lekima said in an apologetic manner.

Han Li duly obliged, stowing the scale away again, following which he entered the city with Liu Le'er, while all of the bystanders looked on with envious expressions.

"Why did you tell me to intervene through voice transmission earlier, Brother Rock? Aren't you acquaintances with Young Master Lekima? Why didn't you want to stay in his manor?" Liu Le'er asked with a puzzled expression.

"We are indeed acquaintances, but I know very little about him. On top of that, he clearly holds a very special status, and I'm a little suspicious of his objective for gifting me that Featherform Scale, so I don't fully trust him," Han Li explained.

What he had refrained from divulging was that he was a little apprehensive of the True Spirit King as well, and he wanted to gather more information about the True Spirit King before he made a decision on whether to meet him or not.

"How did you meet Young Master Lekima, Brother Rock?" Liu Le'er asked.

"That's a long story... By the way, why do all of you refer to him as young master?" Han Li asked.

"He's the son of True Spirit King Bai Ze, so he's naturally our young master. I heard that he's been traveling for a very long time, and it was only about a century ago that he returned to the primordial land. Despite his long absence, the True Spirit King still held him in very high regard, and even our chief has to refer to him as young master," Liu Le'er explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Our chief has been intentionally keeping your activities secret from me all this time, but I had my ways of finding out, and I heard that you traveled to many immortal regions, stirring up a lot of unrest in the process. It left me feeling both concerned and a little envious," Liu Le'er said with a smile.

"What's there to be envious of?" Han Li asked in a puzzled manner. "Most of my time has been spent running away from people who want to kill me."

"But you have so much freedom! Staying in the tribe is safe, but it's so boring. All I do is cultivate and listen to our chief's repetitive lectures all day. In comparison, I really miss the days I spent with you," Liu Le'er said in a slightly dejected manner.

"A safe and stable life is always better. We cultivate in order to attain immortality, not to live in constant fear and instability," Han Li said, and a hint of melancholy had appeared in his eyes as well.

Liu Le'er listened to him with her head cocked to the side, nodding absentmindedly in response.

The two of them continued to chat with each other while making their way toward the Heavenly Fox Tribe settlement.

At this point, the sun had already set, and the sky was gradually turning dark.

......

That night.

Han Li followed Liu Le'er to a cluster of tall buildings at the foot of Eight Plains Mountain.

The buildings here were rather different from the black stone city in that they were constructed using a type of green material, and the style was also completely different, with spirit beast designs and reliefs a very common sight here.

At the highest point of this cluster of buildings was a huge, nine-tailed fox statue that towered over all of the surrounding buildings, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of it.

The statue was giving off an indescribable aura that was suppressing his true spirit bloodlines, impeding their circulation in his body.

Liu Le'er immediately noticed his discomfort, and she hurriedly said, "This is our Heavenly Fox Tribe's settlement on Eight Plains Mountain, Brother Rock. That's a statue of the Heavenly Fox Holy Patriarch, and it contains a hint of his true spirit bloodline, so it'll have a subjugating effect on the bloodlines of other tribes. All you have to do is suppress your own true spirit bloodline."

Han Li heeded her advice, channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts to suppress his own true spirit bloodlines, leaving only the Lightning Bird bloodline, and sure enough, much of his discomfort instantly faded away.

"The Heavenly Fox Holy Patriarch? Is that Liu Qi?" Han Li asked.

"How do you know of Patriarch Liu Qi, Brother Rock? Right now, not even many Heavenly Fox beings are aware of his existence," Liu Le'er said with a surprised expression.

"I happened to hear about him by chance," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner, choosing not to reveal the truth to Liu Le'er.

"Patriarch Liu Qi isn't the Heavenly Fox Holy Patriarch. The holy patriarch was one of the eight True Spirit Kings, but he somehow went missing. Patriarch Liu Qi was once the brightest prodigy of our Heavenly Fox Tribe, and he had high hopes of inheriting the Heavenly Fox Holy Patriarch's bloodline to become the new Heavenly Fox True Spirit King, but unfortunately, he also went missing, and that's why our Heavenly Fox Tribe has fallen into relative irrelevancy," Liu Le'er sighed.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but internally, his mind was racing.

He had heard a lot about the Heavenly Fox Tribe from Patriarch Liu Qi and Fox 3, and he had always thought that he had a decent understanding of the situation in the Heavenly Fox Tribe, but only after speaking with Liu Le'er did he come to realize that his knowledge of the Heavenly Fox Tribe's situation was far from comprehensive.

Han Li's expressionless response led Liu Le'er to believe that he had no interest in the affairs of the Heavenly Fox Tribe, so she hurriedly changed the subject.

"Let's go meet the chief together, Brother Rock. You've met him before in the past. He's very powerful, and he's also very kind to his juniors. Perhaps if you flatter him a little, he'll bestow upon you a gift or two."

The image of the white-robed man who had saved him all those years ago in the primordial land surfaced in Han Li's mind upon hearing this.

Their previous encounter hadn't been a very amicable one, but in any case, he had saved Han Li's life, so it was only right that Han Li paid him a visit.

Chapter 1168: Animosity

Liu Le'er was very happy to see that Han Li wasn't opposed to the idea, and she quickly led him to an entrance to the cluster of buildings.

"Young Mistress Le'er!"

Four guards clad in suits of azure armor were standing at the entrance, and they extended a collective respectful bow at the sight of Liu Le'er.

Han Li was quite pleased to see this.

The four guards were all at the mid or late-Golden Immortal Stage, yet they were still treating Liu Le'er with a high degree of respect, and that told him that Liu Le'er possessed quite a lofty status in the Heavenly Fox Tribe.

Liu Le'er paid no heed to the four guards as she eagerly rushed toward the entrance, displaying remnants of the energetic little girl she had been during her time with Han Li in the Spirit Domain Realm.

Han Li was just about to follow along when the four guards extended their weapons to block his path.

"Stay back!"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he stopped in his tracks.

"What do you think you're doing?" Liu Le'er asked as she turned around with a cold expression.

The guard with the highest cultivation base of the four cupped his fist in a salute toward Liu Le'er as he explained, "Forgive us, Young Mistress Le'er, but this fellow daoist is not a Heavenly Fox being, so if he wants to enter our settlement, then he'll have to secure permission from Elder Mu."

"I'll explain this matter to Elder Mu, so all of you can stand down," Liu Le'er said in a cold voice.

The guard was silent for a moment, but didn't relent.

"Please don't make our job more difficult than necessary, Young Mistress Le'er."

"How dare you!" Liu Le'er snapped in a furious voice as she made a grabbing motion to release a burst of gray light, which swept up the weapons of the guards to hurl them aside.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this.

It seemed that Liu Le'er was wearing some type of treasure that concealed her cultivation base, and only in the wake of this display of power from her was Han Li able to detect that she had also reached the High Zenith Stage.

Even though it was only the early-High Zenith Stage, it was still worlds apart from her cultivation base back in the Spirit Domain Realm.

The four guards immediately tightened their grips around their weapons to prevent them from being torn away.

Even though they were only at the Golden Immortal Stage, they seemed to be adept in some type of collaborative secret technique that allowed them to combine their powers to withstand Liu Le'er's grab, but blood was trickling down from the corners of their lips, and it was clear that they had not withstood the attack without physical strain.

Liu Le'er had only recently reached the High Zenith Stage, so she was still yet to fully consolidate her cultivation base. Right as she was about to unleash an even more powerful attack, an authoritative voice suddenly rang out.

"Stand down, all of you!"

At the same time, a burst of tremendous force appeared between Liu Le'er and the four guards to forcibly separate them.

A gray-robed man with a head of white hair then appeared out of thin air, and a hint of apprehension surfaced in Han Li's eyes as he channeled his Lightning Bird bloodline to conceal his own status as a human.

Despite the elderly man's rather unremarkable appearance, he was a Great Encompassment cultivator.

"Elder Mu!"

The four guards hurriedly sheathed their weapons before extending respectful bows toward the gray-robed elderly man, and Liu Le'er also extended a respectful curtsey.

"Right now, all of the most powerful primordial tribes are gathered on Eight Plains Mountain, what are you doing causing a conflict at the entrance of our settlement at a time like this?" the elderly man scolded.

"My sincerest apologies, Elder Mu, it's just that Young Mistress Le'er was trying to bring this stranger into our settlement, which is against the rules, so we stepped in to stop her," the leader of the guards immediately replied.

"He's my brother, and he's saved my life in the past, so he's not just some stranger," Liu Le'er immediately protested.

The gray-robed elderly man took a glance at Han Li, and a hint of barely detectable derision flashed through his eyes as he said, "Alright, that's enough from all of you. Le'er, you can come in with your brother."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the elderly man's expression, but he didn't say anything as he entered the settlement with Liu Le'er.

Before long, the three of them had arrived in an opulent hall.

The tables and chairs inside were all crafted from previous materials, and it seemed that this was some type of guest hall.

"The blood inheritance ceremony is about to begin, so every single second is of huge importance to you! How could you go out unannounced at a time like this? The chief is already very unhappy with you, so hurry up and go back to the Heavenly Fox Palace!" the gray-robed elderly man scolded with a stern expression as soon as he entered the hall.

Liu Le'er lowered her head slightly as she replied, "I know what I did was wrong, but I would like to request a day of rest to spend with my brother. I'll be sure to work extra hard on my cultivation tomorrow to make up for today."

"That's absolutely unacceptable! The future of our Heavenly Fox Tribe hinges on the outcome of this blood inheritance ceremony, so it must be treated with the utmost care! Go back to the Heavenly Fox Palace right now, I'll attend to this brother of yours in your stead," the elderly man said.

Liu Le'er's brows furrowed slightly as a hesitant look appeared on her face.

"It's fine, Le'er. You're clearly busy, so you don't need to accompany me any further," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"Alright, but stay here and don't go anywhere, I'll have some free time once the blood inheritance ceremony is over," Liu Le'er said, then implored Elder Mu to look after Han Li before departing, leaving only Han Li and Elder Mu left in the hall.

Han Li continued to channel his Lightning Bird bloodline as he cupped his fist in a salute, preparing to deliver a self-introduction, only for Elder Mu to turn to him with a cold sneer as he said, "I know all about you, Fellow Daoist Han, so there's no need to use those little tricks to disguise yourself. You may be able to fool the other tribes, but you can't fool our Heavenly Fox Tribe."

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, following which a faint smile appeared on his face, making no further effort to keep up his facade as he said, "In that case, it looks like I won't have to keep up my disguise any longer."

At the same time, he heaved an internal sigh. He had thought that given his ties with Liu Le'er and Fox 3, it would be easier for him to try and gather some information from the Heavenly Fox Tribe, but it was clear that he wasn't welcome here.

"For what purpose have you come to our Heavenly Fox Tribe, Fellow Daoist Han?" Elder Mu asked in a cold voice.

"Rest assured, Elder Mu, I may be a human cultivator, but I harbor no ill will toward any of the primordial tribes. I only came to visit as I happened to encounter Le'er by chance, but I'm clearly not welcome here, so I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li said as he rose to his feet, then turned to depart.

However, Elder Mu abruptly appeared in his path to intercept him.

"You think you can just come and go from this place as you please? Tell me your objectives first!" Elder Mu demanded as a gray light barrier appeared over the exit of the hall.

"What's the meaning of this? Are you trying to keep me here by force?" Han Li asked as a cold look appeared on his face as well, and a miniature lightning array appeared over the palm of his hand, which was concealed up his sleeve.

On the way to Eight Plains Mountain, he had been constantly refining his Eon Divine Lamp and studying the Almighty Sword Array, but studying something for prolonged periods of time was bound to grow tiresome, so whenever he grew weary, he would read through the Five Lightning True Mantra as a constructive form of relaxation.

The Five Lightning True Mantra contained an enormous amount of information, and Han Li was able to benefit immensely from reading through it.

In particular, he had found a lightning teleportation technique in the scripture that worked in a very similar way to his lightning teleportation array, but this lightning teleportation technique was far more advanced and profound.

After carefully studying the technique, he incorporated many of its profound elements into his own lightning teleportation array and Lightning Restraining Wood teleportation array. As a result, he was able to significantly reduce the amount of time required to activate the two arrays while also drastically increasing the achievable distance of teleportation.

In particular, the Lightning Restraining Wood array was especially compatible with the lightning teleportation technique, and when combined, the Lightning Restraining Wood teleportation array could be activated virtually instantly.

The previous Lightning Restraining Wood array had already been destroyed by Qi Mozi, but Han Li had managed to refine a new set using other lightning-attribute materials, and the new array had been set up in an obscure location on the way here.

This array was what had given him the confidence to come to Eight Plains Mountain.

On top of that, Han Li had also begun secretly injecting his time law powers into his Heaven Controlling Vial, so even if the activation of his lightning teleportation array were to somehow be interrupted, then he would still be able to escape using the Heaven Controlling Vial's time-space transmigration ability.

Using the ability would require him to sacrifice more time law threads, but at the very least, it was better than ending up dead.

"Don't think that I don't know what you're plotting. You're aware of Le'er's current status in our Heavenly Fox Tribe, so you want to take advantage of her attachment to you to benefit from our tribe.

“Unfortunately for you, our Heavenly Fox Tribe isn't as easy to swindle as Young Master Lekima, so I suggest you surrender now to spare yourself of unnecessary suffering!" Elder Mu sneered as he prepared to strike, while Han Li was preparing to activate his lightning teleportation array.

Right at this moment, an authoritative voice rang out within the hall.

"Stand down, Elder Mu!"

Immediately thereafter, a figure appeared out of thin air, and it was none other than the white-robed man that Han Li had encountered once before in the primordial land.

"Chief Liu!"

Elder Mu hurriedly stopped what he was doing, then extended a respectful bow toward the white-robed man.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly at the sight of the white-robed man, and he was secretly channeling his immortal spiritual power in case he had to defend himself.

During their last encounter, his cultivation base had still been quite low, so while it had been apparent to him that the white-robed man was extremely powerful, he wasn't able to glean the man's exact cultivation base.

Now that he had reached the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage, he could clearly sense that the white-robed man was far more powerful than even the likes of Chi Meng and Immortal Lord Miao Fa. He wasn't quite on the same level as the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, but there certainly wasn't a significant gap between them.

With that in mind, Han Li began secretly channeling his time law powers as well, and at the same time, a pair of beady eyes appeared on his Heaven Controlling Vial, preparing to transmigrate him away at a moment's notice.

Chapter 1169: Belittled

"Elder Mu, how could you be so rude to Le'er's brother? If the other primordial tribes were to find out about this, then our Heavenly Fox Tribe will be ridiculed as a bunch of ungrateful thugs. You can go now, I'll attend to Fellow Daoist Han myself," the white-robed man said.

"But Chief Liu, given Le'er's current situation, this man must have sinister motives for coming here at this time!" Elder Mu protested in an urgent voice.

"You can go now!" the white-robed man repeated in a firmer voice, and Elder Mu could only give Han Li an indignant glare before departing.

"You've made some rapid progress in your cultivation base, Han Li. How impressive," the white-robed man remarked with a faint smile following Elder Mu's departure.

"You're far too kind, Chief Liu Qing," Han Li replied as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

"Oh? You know my name?" Liu Qing asked with a surprised expression.

"I heard someone mention it in the past," Han Li replied in an ambiguous fashion, making no mention of his past experiences in the Gray Realm.

"Several of Elder Mu's descendants were killed by human cultivators, so he's very resentful of humans. On top of that, Le'er is currently cultivating a secret technique that's vital to the upcoming blood inheritance ceremony, so he's very sensitive about anything concerning her in this crucial juncture. Please forgive him for any offense he may have caused," Liu Qing said.

"It's fine," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"Elder Mu may have been a little too frank with his words, but he's not wrong. Le'er is no longer the same Le'er as before. She possesses the paramount bloodline of the Heavenly Fox Tribe, and she'll ascend to even greater heights after this blood inheritance ceremony.

“You may be her brother, but that's all in the distant past, and you're a human cultivator, so you and Le'er are destined to belong to two different worlds, do you understand?" Liu Qing asked as he looked straight into Han Li's eyes.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but internally, he was seething.

Both Liu Qing and Elder Mu were regarding him as some calculating charlatan who was trying to benefit from the Heavenly Fox Tribe through his ties with Liu Le'er, and he had never been so blatantly belittled before.

Liu Qing mistook Han Li's silence as one of contemplation, so he continued, "At the moment, you're not in the best of situations. In the wake of your conflict with the Qing Ape Tribe, you status as a human was about to be exposed, so it's understandable that you turned to Le'er for help. However, Le'er needs to focus on her cultivation right now, and I can't allow for anything to distract her.

“I can allow you to stay in our settlement until the commencement of the blood inheritance ceremony, and I'll protect you during this time, but please leave Eight Plains Mountain right away after the ceremony. Of course, if you have any requests, you can feel free to state them, but I'll only grant them on the condition that you won't ever bother Le'er again..."

Han Li was unable to contain his temper any longer, and he interjected in a cold voice, "Your concerns are unnecessary, Chief Liu. I may just be a lowly human, but I've never had to beg anyone for my protection. I only came here to catch up with Le'er for old time's sake. As for whether we'll meet again, let's leave that to fate. For now, I'll be taking my leave."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he turned to depart.

Liu Qing's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and a hint of fury flashed through his eyes. His sleeve rustled slightly, as if he were about to do something, but all of a sudden, he stopped what he was doing as he cast his gaze outside.

Even though Han Li was storming away, most of his attention was still focused on Liu Qing, so as soon as he detected what Liu Qing was doing, he also cast his gaze outside as he stopped in his tracks.

Right at this moment, two figures entered the hall.

One of them was Lekima, and he was accompanied by none other than True Spirit King Bai Ze.

"Your Majesty! To what do I owe this honor?" Liu Qing said in a respectful manner as he hurriedly emerged from the hall to greet Bai Ze.

Han Li's complexion instantly paled slightly upon hearing this. Even though he had never met Bai Ze before, there was only one man in the entire primordial land that Liu Qing would refer to as "Your Majesty".

He had come to the Heavenly Fox Tribe in order to find out more information about the True Spirit King so that he could decide whether to meet him or not, but the True Spirit King had come to him before he had a chance to find out anything.

Even though Bai Ze wasn't giving off any aura at the moment, a sense of indescribable fear had welled up in Han Li's heart, and he had only ever experienced this sensation in the presence of a very exclusive group of individuals, including Yin Chengquan, Daoist Xie following his awakening, and the Devilish Monarch.

"No need for formalities, Chief Liu. I've come here on a private matter, so make sure you don't tell anyone about my visit," Bai Ze said.

"Yes, Your Majesty. May I ask the purpose of your visit? Whatever you need from me, I'll have it arranged right away," Liu Qing immediately replied.

"There's no need for you to do anything, I'm here to see Fellow Daoist Han," Bai Ze said as he turned to Han Li with a faint smile, while Liu Qing also turned to him with a dumbstruck expression.

Han Li took a glance at Lekima, then cupped his fist in a respectful salute toward Bai Ze as he greeted, "Han Li pays his respects to Senior Bai Ze."

He may not have had a chance to find out much about the True Spirit King, but he was at least familiar with the True Spirit King's name.

"I informed Father of the matter concerning Xiao Bai, and he asked me to take him to you right away. I hope that's not an issue," Lekima said with a faint smile.

"Not at all, it's an honor for me to make your acquaintance, Senior Bai Ze," Han Li replied with a composed smile, even though he was far from pleased with the situation that had been forced upon him.

"There's no need for such formalities from you, either, Fellow Daoist Han. You saved my son's life, so our primordial tribes owe you a favor. I've heard that you also possess multiple true spirit bloodlines, so it seems like you have some rather extensive ties with our primordial tribes," Bai Ze said with a smile.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then said, "While it's true that I possess several true spirit bloodlines, almost all of them were obtained in lower realms, and I haven't maliciously harmed any of the primordial tribes during my time in the True Immortal Realm."

"It's fine, Fellow Daoist Han, Father already knows about your history. The greatest enemy of our primordial land is the Heavenly Court, and as the saying goes, an enemy of an enemy is a friend.

“Besides, you've also done all of our primordial tribes a great kindness by delivering Xiao Bai to Eight Plains Mountain, so you can rest assured in the knowledge that we bear no ill will toward you," Lekima said with a reassuring smile, and Han Li felt a little less apprehensive upon hearing this, while Liu Qing was beginning to sorely regret the attitude that he had just displayed toward Han Li.

Despite this, he remained composed as he respectfully invited Bai Ze and Lekima into the hall, but Han Li remained standing outside the hall.

"What are you doing, Fellow Daoist Han? Come and take a seat," Lekima invited with a perplexed expression.

"A mere human like myself wouldn't dare to sit as I please in the Heavenly Fox Tribe's territory. I should be thanking my lucky stars that I haven't been thrown out yet," Han Li replied.

"Hmm? What's the meaning of this?" Lekima asked as he turned to Liu Qing, and Bai Ze did the same.

"There was a slight misunderstanding between Fellow Daoist Han and myself, but it's all been cleared up now," Liu Qing explained with an awkward expression, then hurriedly made his way over to Han Li's side to cup his fist in an apologetic salute.

Han Li was in no mood to forgive Liu Qing, but he still returned the salute as he knew that he stood to gain nothing from turning Liu Qing against him.

"I have some matters to discuss with Fellow Daoist Han, so you can go now, Chief Liu," Bai Ze said, treating the Heavenly Fox Tribe settlement as if it were his own backyard.

Liu Qing didn't display any displeasure to this, and he cupped his fist in a respectful salute before quickly departing.

In recent times, the Heavenly Court had been constantly invading the primordial land under all types of excuses, and it was only thanks to Bai Ze's leadership that the primordial tribes had been able to keep the Heavenly Court at bay, so Bai Ze was an extremely revered and respected figure to all of the primordial tribes.

After leaving the hall, Liu Qing quickly arrived in another nearby hall.

Elder Mu was waiting in the hall, and as soon as he caught sight of Liu Qing, he immediately asked, "Have you already taken care of that bastard, Chief Liu? To think that a human would dare to come to the primordial land and extort our Heavenly Fox Tribe! What an insolent scoundrel! How did you deal with him?"

Liu Qing gave a cold harrumph as he shot Elder Mu a displeased glare.

He had been in the Heavenly Fox Palace earlier when he received word that Han Li had come to their settlement, and while dismissing Elder Mu, a spiritual sense conversation had taken place between the two of them.

After learning that Han Li had only arrived at Eight Plains Mountain with a pair of no-name primordial tribes, he came under the impression that Han Li didn't have any special connections or powerful backers to rely on, and that was why he had displayed such a hostile attitude to Han Li, but never did he think that the information that he had received from Elder Mu would be so absurdly wrong.

"What's wrong, Chief Liu?" Elder Mu asked as a hint of foreboding welled up in his heart at the sight of Liu Qing's furious expression.

Liu Qing swept a sleeve through the air to set up several layers of restrictions, then said, "You just told me that Han Li came to Eight Plains Mountain with the Silver Horn Rhinoceros Tribe and the Cloud Spot Tiger Tribe, and that he had no special connection, is that right?"

"That's right. He does seem to be familiar with Young Master Lekima, but how could a human cultivator like him possibly have any connections here on Eight Plains Mountain?" Elder Mu replied.

"If you knew that he was familiar with Young Master Lekima, why didn't you tell me?" Liu Qing asked in a cold voice.

At this point, it had dawned on Elder Mu that he had landed himself in some hot water, and he replied in a timid fashion, "I didn't think anything of it. Everyone knows that Young Master Lekima has a very erratic personality and likes to make random friends. His Majesty has even scolded him for this very tendency on many occasions, so I assumed that Han Li was just another one of those inconsequential friends."

"You're a fool!" Liu Qing suddenly yelled, then sat down onto a chair and closed his eyes to compose himself.

Elder Mu was given quite a fright by this sudden outburst, and he didn't dare to say anything further as he hung his head in silence.

Chapter 1170: Awakening

Before long, Liu Qing opened his eyes as he said, "I don't care how much you detest human cultivators and how much you resent Han Li, make sure to treat him with respect from now on, do you hear me?"

"Are you saying that he's still in our settlement?" Elder Qiu asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Do I make myself clear? Do I need to repeat myself?" Liu Qing snapped as a furious look resurfaced in his eyes.

"No, there's no need for that, you've made yourself perfectly clear, Chief Liu," Elder Qiu hurriedly replied.

Liu Qing gave another cold harrumph and paid no further heed to Elder Qiu.

He had agreed to keep Bai Ze's visit a secret, so he couldn't reveal the situation to Elder Qiu. He could only hope that Elder Qiu was going to heed his warning. Otherwise, he would have to resort to some forceful measures.

......

In the Heavenly Fox Tribe's guest hall.

Following Liu Qing's departure, Bai Ze immediately said, "I heard that you've brought an Ink-Eyed Pixiu with you to Eight Plains Mountain. Would I be able to see him, Fellow Daoist Han?"

"Of course, please wait a moment, Senior," Han Li replied.

At this point, he had no choice but to comply, so he quickly brought Xiao Bai out of the Flower Branch domain, and the latter was still in an unconscious state.

A hint of excitement instantly surfaced in his eyes at the sight of Xiao Bai, and he murmured to himself, "It really is an Ink-Eyed Pixiu, and it's his son as well! The heavens have truly smiled upon me."

"It sounds like you're familiar with Xiao Bai, Senior Bai Ze. I've tried to awaken him from his unconscious state, but to no avail," Han Li said.

"His name is Xiao Bai, is it? If I'm not mistaken, he's the offspring of a close friend of mine, the Ink-Eyed Pixiu True Spirit King. Many years ago, he was attacked by several Heavenly Court Dao Ancestors and lost his life in that battle, I didn't think that he still had surviving offspring.

“Thank you for bringing him to Eight Plains Mountain, Fellow Daoist Han. As for his injuries, I'm perhaps the only one in the primordial land capable of treating them," Bai Ze replied.

"Xiao Bai is a friend of mine, so it's only right that I brought him here for treatment," Han Li said, and at the same time, he was feeling a little more reassured, giving the bond that Bai Ze shared with Xiao Bai's father.

Han Li hadn't asked for anything in return for delivering Xiao Bai to Eight Plains Mountain, and an appreciative smile appeared on Bai Ze's face upon seeing this. He swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of white light that carried Xiao Bai to him, following which he produced a crimson pill with a series of white patterns on it, ones that were both similar and different from the patterns on dao pills.

The white patterns formed an image of a white beast that was very similar in appearance to Xiao Bai's Pixiu form.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly at the sight of the crimson pill, but before he could take a closer look, the pill had already flown into Xiao Bai's mouth with unerring accuracy at Bai Ze's behest.

After that, Bai Ze rested a finger against Xiao Bai's forehead, and a burst of translucent light emerged from his fingertip. Countless black runes were flashing within the translucent light, and they surged into Xiao Bai's glabella in a continuous stream.

All of a sudden, Xiao Bai's body began to tremble while giving off rings of expanding white light, and he began to moan in pain, but his eyes remained closed.

A hint of concern appeared in Han Li's upon seeing this, but he knew that it was best not to interrupt the process.

Bai Ze cycled through a string of hand seals, then laid the palm of his hand against Xiao Bai's forehead, and as he withdrew his hand, Han Li noticed that a faint, black mark had appeared on Xiao Bai's glabella.

The black mark definitely wasn't there before, so it had to have been imprinted by Bai Ze.

All of a sudden, Xiao Bai's body shuddered one final time before falling still, following which he slowly opened his eyes.

"Xiao Bai!" Han Li called out in an ecstatic manner.

"Master!" Xiao Bai exclaimed with an ecstatic look of his own, and he tried to get up, but immediately stumbled, seemingly still yet to fully recover from his injuries.

Thankfully, Han Li was able to catch him, and he said, "Don't be in a hurry to move, you're still recovering from some very severe injuries."

Even though Xiao Bai still hadn't physically recovered, he had certainly regained his voice, and he immediately began yelling, "Thank goodness you're here, Master. Boss was captured by people from the Nine Origins Temple! You have to save her! Hold on... what is this place?"

"We're in the primordial land right now. Don't worry about Jin Tong, I'll think of a way to save her," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of pure immortal spiritual power into Xiao Bai's body.

With Han Li's help, Xiao Bai was able to stand up, and he was very much taken aback by the sight of Lekima and Bai Ze, the latter of whom was looking back at Xiao Bai with a warm smile on his face.

"It's all thanks to Senior Bai Ze that you were awakened from your unconscious state, so you have him to thank," Han Li said.

"Thank you for saving me, Senior," Xiao Bai said with a grateful nod.

"Don't mention it. Your father was a very close friend of mine. Do you still remember your father?" Bai Ze asked.

"My father? I have a father?" Xiao Bai asked with a dumbstruck expression.

"Looks like your father sealed away your memories. That makes sense. Otherwise, you would've definitely already perished in an attempt to seek out vengeance against the Heavenly Court," Bai Ze mused.

"Do you know about my past, Senior?" Xiao Bai hurriedly asked with a hopeful expression.

"Of course I do, I just said that your father was a close friend of mine. However, now's not the time to reveal everything to you. You'll find out when the time comes," Bai Ze replied.

Xiao Bai was clearly not very happy with this answer, yet right as he was about to ask further questions, Han Li instructed him to hold his tongue.

"Even though Xiao Bai is now awake, he's still yet to fully recover, so I would like to take him back with me to aid in his recovery. What do you say, Fellow Daoist Han?" Bai Ze asked.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, but ultimately refused, "Your kindness is much appreciated, but I've spent a lot of time with Xiao Bai, so I've become quite familiar with him, and I'm confident in my ability to aid his recovery on my own."

Even though Bai Ze had left a good first impression on him, Han Li still felt a little apprehensive about letting him take Xiao Bai.

Bai Ze could see that Han Li was genuinely concerned for Xiao Bai, so he smiled and said, "Alright, in that case, I'll leave Xiao Bai to you."

Bai Ze then turned to Lekima and instructed, "Make sure to look after Fellow Daoist Han during his time on Eight Plains Mountain."

"Yes, Father," Lekima hurriedly replied, and Bai Ze vanished from the spot, much to Han Li's relief.

Xiao Bai glanced back and forth between Han Li and Lekima for a moment, and even though he was still yet to fully understand the situation that he was in, he knew not to ask any questions with Lekima present.

As soon as Bai Ze departed, Lekima was instantly back to his usual relaxed self, and he smiled as he said, "It looks like Father is quite fond of you. I've never seen him look out for anyone else like this."

"Truth be told, I feel a little uneasy to have received a personal visit from Senior Bai Ze," Han Li admitted.

"What's there to be uneasy about? Don't worry, Father wouldn't plot against you like Liu Qing," Lekima reassured as he gave Han Li a pat on the shoulder. "By the way, what are your plans from here onward?

“There's still some time left until the commencement of the blood inheritance ceremony, and seeing as Xiao Bai is the son of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu, he'll have to take part as well. It seems to me like Father wants you to stay and take part in the ceremony as well."

"Senior Bai Zi wants me to take part in the blood inheritance ceremony?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression, and thinking back to Bai Ze's words and attitude from earlier, it seemed that he did indeed have such intentions.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li said, "I'm honored by the invitation, but I'm afraid that I can't give a verdict on whether I'll attend the ceremony or not right away."

At the moment, Jin Tong was still trapped in the Nine Origins Temple, so he had to ask Xiao Bai about the situation there before he could make a decision on whether to stay in the primordial land or leave.

"Of course. Are you going to continue to stay here, or would you like me to arrange another place for you to stay?" Lekima asked with a smile.

"The Heavenly Fox Tribe doesn't seem to be very welcoming of me, so I'll have to trouble you to find me some other place to live," Han Li replied.

"No problem, leave it to me," Lekima promised, and the two of them departed from the hall together.

Due to the special nature of Xiao Bai's identity, he had been ushered back into the Flower Branch domain by Han Li.

Right at this moment, the two of them were approached by Liu Qing, who asked with a warm smile, "Are you leaving, Young Master? Has His Majesty already left?"

"I haven't seen Fellow Daoist Han for a very long time, so I want to take him to my residence to stay with me for a few days. Will that be fine with you, Chief Liu?" Lekima asked.

"Of course! You're welcome to return to our Heavenly Fox Tribe at any time, Fellow Daoist Han," Liu Qing replied.

Han Li responded with a curt nod, then quickly departed with Lekima.

Liu Qing personally accompanied the two to the entrance of the settlement, then watched as they departed before heaving a faint sigh.

Han Li was led to a peaceful courtyard that was filled with lush greenery by Lekima, who said, "You won't be disturbed by anyone here. I have arranged for people to stand on lookout duty outside, and if you need anything, feel free to tell them."

Han Li was very pleased with this place, and he nodded in response.

It seemed that Lekima had other matters to attend to, and he only stayed for a short while before departing.

Chapter 1171: Bodhi Banquet

Following Lekima's departure, Han Li scoured the entire courtyard with his spiritual sense, and only after verifying that nothing was amiss did he set up a few layers of restrictions before making his way into a room deep inside the courtyard.

He set up several more layers of restrictions there, and only then did he enter the Flower Branch domain, where he was immediately approached by Xiao Bai.

"Alright, there's no one else here aside from the two of us, tell me what happened with Jin Tong," Han Li said in a serious manner.

"After we parted ways, Boss and I traveled to the Golden Origin Immortal Region and found the Gold Devouring Immortal that you mentioned to us. Boss was able to devour that Gold Devouring Immortal and reach the Great Encompassment Stage," Xiao Bai recounted.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this, only to then be replaced by a grim look.

The fact that Jin Tong had been captured even after reaching the Great Encompassment Stage meant that her captor had to have been extremely powerful, so saving her was undoubtedly going to be very difficult.

"What we failed to anticipate was that the Gold Devouring Immortal had an owner, and it was a very powerful figure in the Nine Origins Temple. He personally pursued Boss and me, and we fled for many years, but were ultimately unable to get away. In the end, that man captured Boss, but she was able to tear open space to allow me to escape, and she told me to go and find you. I didn't think that I would see you so soon," Xiao Bai continued.

"Do you know the name of Jin Tong's captor and his status in the Nine Origins Temple?" Han Li asked.

Xiao Bai shuddered slightly as a hint of lingering fear flashed through his eyes, and he replied, "His name is Gui Lingzi, and he seems to be one of the Nine Origins Temple's four holy envoys."

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon hearing this.

He had heard about Gui Lingzi from Lan Yan, and according to her, Gui Lingzi was the leader of the four holy envoys and was even more powerful than Immortal Lord Miao Fa.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa was already a huge pain to deal with, let alone an even more formidable Gui Lingzi.

"The only silver lining is that Gui Lingzi didn't have any intention of harming Boss. Instead, it seems like he wants to offer up Boss to someone else during a Bodhi Banquet or something like that, so she's not in any danger for now," Xiao Bai added.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this. He had never heard of this Bodhi Banquet before.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he put on his Reincarnation Palace mask and offered a reward for information on the Bodhi Banquet, while Xiao Bai waited obediently off to the side.

To Han Li's surprise, a response came in very quickly, and as it turned out, the Bodhi Banquet was a prestigious event held by the Heavenly Court once every five million years.

The Bodhi Banquet's origins came from a Bodhi Dao Tree in the Heavenly Court. It was said that the tree had sprouted at the beginning of time, and that the Bodhi Dao Fruits that it produced granted the consumer an increase of ten million years worth of cultivation base per fruit.

Furthermore, those who consumed the Bodhi Dao Fruit had a chance of attaining the Bodhi Dao Physique, which was immensely beneficial for the cultivation of all law powers.

Originally, the Bodhi Dao Tree could only produce fruit once every hundreds of millions of years, but the Time Dao Ancestor of the Heavenly Court had used his unfathomable powers to accelerate the process, making the tree bear fruit once every five million years.

Furthermore, instead of hoarding all of the Bodhi Dao Fruits for himself, the Time Dao Ancestor would always invite the most powerful forces in all of the immortal regions to attend a banquet where all of the Bodhi Dao Fruits were distributed, and that was the origin of the Bodhi Banquet.

As word of the Bodhi Dao Fruit began to spread, more and more powers requested to take part in the banquet, making it a larger and larger event. Before long, there was too little supply of Bodhi Dao Fruits to meet the increasing demand, and all of the powers began offering extremely valuable gifts to the Time Dao Ancestor in the hopes of securing a fruit.

Initially, the Bodhi Banquet was only an event held to discuss how the Bodhi Dao Fruits should be distributed, but with more and more powers taking part, it became an event for different powers to deepen ties with one another, discuss major events, and establish alliances.

At this point, the Bodhi Banquet was already the undisputed number one event in the entire True Immortal Realm, and there were only less than three thousand years left until the next Bodhi Banquet.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as this information came to light.

There was a very good chance that Gui Lingzi intended to offer up Jin Tong to the Time Dao Ancestor during the Bodhi Banquet.

According to the information provided by the Reincarnation Palace, the Time Dao Ancestor was very fond of all types of exotic treasures and creatures, and a Great Encompassment Stage Gold Devouring Immortal certainly fell into that category.

There was still a chance that Han Li would be able to save Jin Tong from Gui Lingzi, but if she were to fall into the Time Dao Ancestor's hands, then she would be lost forever.

Even though Wyrm 3 had told him that there was a mission regarding the Nine Origins Temple in which the Reincarnation Palace would be able to help him rescue Jin Tong, he still had to rely mostly on himself, and a mere three thousand years was certainly not a lot of time to prepare.

If he wanted to advance further in his cultivation base, then he would have to find two suitable time-attribute law materials that could elevate the number of time law threads of his Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree and his Illusory Dawn Hourglass, but such items were extremely rare.

He had already gotten very lucky with that Water Divination Time Crystal, could he expect to get lucky twice more?

"I'll think of a way to save Jin Tong. You've only just woken up, and you need to recover, so you can take these," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a large pile of immortal treasures and materials for Xiao Bai to consume.

Xiao Bai's eyes instantly lit up upon seeing this, and he hurriedly thanked Han Li, but right as he was about to dig into the feast laid out before him, a thought suddenly occurred to him.

"Oh, by the way, while Boss and I were hunting for that Gold Devouring Immortal, we snuck into the Nine Origins Temple, and I found this in there. I'm unable to digest it, and I'm hoping that it'll be useful to you."

He then opened his mouth to release a yellow bowl, which was a little dilapidated in appearance, looking as if it were an ancient artifact, and there was a series of golden patterns engraved upon it.

Han Li's eyes instantly lit up with elation at the sight of the bowl, which was giving off time law power fluctuations that were very similar to those of the Illusory Dawn Hourglass.

Furthermore, he could sense that the bowl contained even more immense time law powers than the Water Divination Time Crystal that he had recently obtained.

He immediately picked up Xiao Bai and began rubbing his head vigorously in excitement as he said, "Well done, Xiao Bai! This is exactly what I needed!"

"I'm glad to hear that," Xiao Bai replied with a wide grin, then flew away to the side with the immortal treasures and materials given to him by Han Li.

Meanwhile, Han Li picked up the bowl again, and the more he looked at it, the more excited he became.

He took a deep breath to compose himself, then sat down and channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, upon which five bursts of golden light surged out of his body, then came together to form a golden ring around the yellow bowl.

The bowl immediately shattered, and countless specks of golden light that resembled glowing particles of sand emerged from within before fusing into the golden ring.

As many as sixty-three time law threads then emerged from the golden ring, all of which wrapped themselves around the Illusory Dawn Hourglass.

The time law powers within Han Li's body swelled drastically once again, and they also began to circulate in a smoother fashion than before, much to his elation.

Now, all that was left was to find a time law material that was compatible with his Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree, and he would be able to make more attempts at reaching the Great Encompassment Stage.

With that in mind, Han Li pulled out his Reincarnation Palace mask and increased the price that he was offering for time-attribute law materials by 50%.

The Bodhi Banquet was not far away, and he had to reach the Great Encompassment State before then in order to have any chance of saving Jin Tong.

He had over seventy million Immortal Origin Stones at the moment, so there was more than enough for him to spend on time-attribute law materials.

After taking off his Reincarnation Palace mask, Han Li emerged from the Flower Branch domain, then made his way out into the courtyard and instructed the servants outside to inform Lekima that he was planning to continue to stay on Eight Plains Mountain.

After that, he returned to his room, then reentered the Flower Branch domain before sweeping a sleeve through the air to release the Essence Fire Child.

"I have to do something very important in a few centuries that may require your power, so stay here in seclusion and focus on refining the white bead. I'll find a way to recover what you've lost," he instructed.

The Essence Fire Child nodded in response, then flew over to a corner of the Flower Branch domain, where it transformed into a silver fireball that was around ten feet in size, and the white bead was hovering within it, giving off tremendous fire law power fluctuations.

A pleased look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he turned his gaze to the bamboo pavilion in the distance.

Ghostly howls were still ringing out from within, and it was unclear when Weeping Soul would come out of seclusion.

After turning his gaze away from the bamboo pavilion, he flipped a hand over to summon a palm-sized jade tablet, upon which was engraved the diagram for the Celestial Time Array.

He was worried that his memory of the array diagram would fade over time, so he had engraved it onto this jade tablet.

There were still many things that he had to do in addition to progressing to the Great Encompassment Stage, including honing his Almighty Sword Array, Reversal True Axis, and Mantra Domain, so he definitely wasn't going to have enough time. However, if he could replicate that space in the True Mantra Sect in which time flowed far faster than elsewhere, then time would no longer be a problem.

There was an important issue that he still had to address in order to set up a space like the one in the True Mantra Sect, but he was still planning to commence the process anyway.

Chapter 1172: Forging the Array

Han Li swept his gaze over the surrounding area, then flew over to a vacant area near the spirit medicine garden, where he began constructing a giant, golden platform that was thousands of feet in size.

He then summoned a collection of materials and began refining a series of array instruments.

He had already begun planning for this quite some time ago, so he had made sure to keep all of the materials required to set up the array as opposed to selling them.

A long list of materials was required to set up the Celestial Time Array, but thankfully, Han Li had gathered everything that he needed after looting the Tai Sui Immortal Manor.

Meanwhile, in the palace on the summit of Eight Plains Mountain.

Bai Ze was standing in front of the dark red brazier, observing the golden flames that were burning inside.

Right at this moment, Lekima stepped into the room, and he reported, "Father, I've just received word that Han Li has agreed to stay."

"Good. Make sure to fulfill all of his requests, as long as they're within reason, and ensure that he stays until the conclusion of the blood inheritance ceremony," Bai Ze said, and Lekima gave an affirmative response.

"Alright, you can go now," Bai Zi said with a dismissive wave as he turned back to the brazier.

However, Lekima didn't immediately depart. Instead, a hesitant look appeared on his face as he asked, "Father, why do you seem so intent on keeping Han Li on Eight Plains Mountain? If it becomes known by all of the tribes that we're harboring a human, won't that spell trouble for everyone?"

"Are you worried that I'm plotting against this friend of yours?" Bai Ze asked with a faint smile.

"I wouldn't dare," Lekima hurriedly replied as he lowered his head.

"It's very good that you care so much for your friends. That's one of the qualities that a king should possess, but before becoming a True Spirit King, you must also learn the importance of making sacrifices. As a True Spirit King, you must prioritize the welfare of the primordial tribes above all else, and friendships must be sacrificed where necessary," Bai Ze continued.

Lekima's expression instantly changed slightly upon hearing this, but Bai Ze patted him on the shoulder with a smile as he said, "Don't worry, I'm not asking you to make that sacrifice now, and I can assure you that I harbor no ill will toward Han Li. Instead, I'm going to bestow an opportunity upon him, but I must spare you the details for now."

All of a sudden, Bai Ze was looking very distant and unfamiliar to Lekima, like an enigmatic mirage on the horizon.

"You can go now, there are still many preparations that have to be made for the blood inheritance ceremony," Bai Ze said with a dismissive wave, and Lekima extended a parting salute before exiting the palace.

......

Half a year flew by in a flash.

At this moment, the golden platform in the Flower Branch domain was riddled with countless array patterns, and there was also a series of array tools installed upon it to form the Celestial Time Array.

After slotting the final Immortal Origin Stones into the array, Han Li rose to his feet before making a hand seal, and the array instantly began to operate amid a burst of faint buzzing.

Thick pillars of golden light rose up from the array, presenting a spectacular sight to behold, and the flow of time in the nearby area began to speed up.

A hint of elation appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. After half a year of toil, he had finally managed to set up the incredibly complex array.

After taking a moment to admire his own handiwork, he swept a sleeve through to release a series of array flags and array plates, which instantly formed an azure array.

With another sweep of his sleeve, a large pile of Immortal Origin Stones appeared within the azure array.

The array then sprang into action, conjuring up bursts of azure light that carried Immortal Origin Stones into the Celestial Time Array in a steady stream.

As soon as the Immortal Origin Stones entered the array, they immediately disintegrated into bursts of pure energy to power it.

The golden light radiating from the Celestial Time Array instantly brightened even further, as did the pillars of golden light rising up from it, and countless golden runes had also emerged within the pillars of golden light.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, then brought out the Heavenly Wheel Sundial, which flew into the array before hovering in the air above it.

A hint of anticipation appeared in Han Li's eyes as he stared intently at the sundial, which was drawing in all of the golden runes swirling within the array.

The sundial shuddered slightly, as if it had just awoken from a long slumber, and a layer of faint, golden light appeared over its surface.

An elated look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he immediately began making a rapid string of hand seals to operate the Celestial Time Array.

All of the golden runes within the array instantly converged toward the Heavenly Wheel Sundial, but despite Han Li's best efforts, the golden light emanating from the sundial didn't brighten any further, nor did it display any time-altering effects.

Han Li heaved a forlorn sigh upon seeing this.

Sure enough, without a supply of time law powers, there was no way to activate the sundial's power.

The problem was that materials that contained time law powers were extremely precious, and Han Li couldn't even find ones for his own cultivation, let alone to power the Heavenly Wheel Sundial.

It was only thanks to the Xumi Golden Mountain, which contained virtually limitless time law powers, that the True Mantra Sect was able to create and maintain that enormous space of accelerated time.

All of a sudden, his eyes lit up as a thought occurred to him.

Perhaps...

Han Li flipped a hand over to summon a certain item, and it was none other than the Eon Divine Lamp.

The golden flame within the lamp was flickering gently while giving off bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations.

Han Li set the lamp down beside the Celestial Time Array, then chanted an incantation before pointing a finger at it, and the flame within the lamp instantly rose up to form a thick pillar of fire that surged into the array.

After tirelessly refining the Eon Divine Lamp for so many years, he was now able to control it with a far higher level of proficiency.

The Celestial Time Array instantly lit up, and it also began operating several times faster than before while releasing a burst of suction force that began devouring the golden flame within the Eon Divine Lamp.

At the same time, balls of golden light flew out of the array, giving off formidable time law power fluctuations as they surged into the Heavenly Wheel Sundial up above.

The sundial instantly began to glow radiantly, while its golden needle also began to rapidly spin.

Waves of golden light surged out of the Heavenly Wheel Sundial before spreading throughout the entire Flower Branch domain, and the flow of time within the domain was instantly accelerated by over five hundredfold, even faster than in the secret area in the True Mantra Sect.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, then abruptly burst into triumphant laughter.

He didn't have high hopes that the Eon Divine Lamp would be able to power the Heavenly Wheel Sundial, but it had worked even better than he could've ever imagined.

After taking a moment to compose himself, Han Li began chanting an incantation while releasing a dense barrage of incantation seals into the Celestial Time Array.

The array instantly began operating far slower than before, and the rate at which the flame within the Eon Divine Lamp was being devoured was also slowed down significantly, as was the rate at which Immortal Origin Stones were being sucked into the array.

The needle on the Heavenly Wheel Sundial also began to spin around ten times slower than before, reducing the rate of flow of time to be only roughly fiftyfold that of the outside world.

The Eon Divine Lamp was a third tier immortal treasure, so it definitely contained a tremendous amount of time law powers. However, Han Li didn't know exactly how much time law powers it contained, so he had to use it sparingly.

On top of that, the lamp was the most powerful immortal treasure that he was currently capable of using, so he couldn't allow it to be sucked dry by the Celestial Time Array.

On top of that, accelerating time by around fiftyfold was already more than enough.

A pained look appeared on Han Li's face as he turned his gaze to the ever-dwindling pile of Immortal Origin Stones in the azure array.

He had thought that seventy million Immortal Origin Stones would've been enough to last him a very long time, but the Celestial Time Array was essentially an insatiable pit that could never be filled.

Thankfully, it seemed that both the time law powers in the Eon Divine Lamp and his supply of Immortal Origin Stones would be able to last quite some time.

Han Li quickly banished these errant thoughts from his mind as he sat down with his legs crossed, then began to study the Almighty Sword Array.

Two years flew by in a flash, and that was the equivalent of over a hundred years passing in the Flower Branch domain.

The Almighty Sword Array Diagram was hovering above Han Li's head, giving off bursts of gentle light that encompassed his entire body.

A series of sword projections of different shapes and sizes had appeared over the array diagram, and they were constantly flashing and changing, presenting a mesmerizing sight to behold.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyes abruptly sprang open, and two beams of radiant light shot out of his pupils and into the array diagram.

All of the sword projections on the array diagram instantly began to flash erratically before rapidly fusing together.

In the blink of an eye, the countless sword projections on the sword array had been reduced to only thirty-six, and an elated look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

After a century of tireless effort, he had finally begun to grasp the secrets of the Almighty Sword Array Diagram.

He took a deep breath to suppress his own elation, then swept a sleeve through the air to release thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were glowing radiantly, as if they were being affected by the Almighty Sword Array Diagram, and thick arcs of golden lightning sprang out of them in all directions.

Han Li paid no heed to these arcs of lightning as he made a hand seal, and the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew onto the Almighty Sword Array Diagram at his behest to fuse with the thirty-six sword projections there.

Chapter 1173: Blood Inheritance Ceremony

As soon as the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords became one with the thirty-six sword projections, a burst of tremendous suction force abruptly erupted out of the array diagram, sucking in the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in the blink of an eye.

A look of bewilderment appeared on Han Li's face, and he could sense his own immortal spiritual power also being sucked into the array diagram in a frenzy.

In the blink of an eye, close to a third of his immortal spiritual power had been devoured, and all of the nearby world's origin qi was also surging into the array diagram.

On top of that, thick arcs of lightning had begun springing out of thin air before fusing into the array diagram as well.

A surprised look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, but he allowed the array diagram to continue devouring his immortal spiritual power as it pleased.

Meanwhile, the world's origin qi on Eight Plains Mountain was churning violently, and dense, dark clouds were gathering up above, quickly taking up the entire sky.

Immediately thereafter, flashes of lightning began to appear in the dark clouds, accompanied by gusts of ferocious wind.

This lightning was drastically different from normal lightning, and it was giving off bursts of asphyxiating lightning law power fluctuations.

Such a massive commotion naturally attracted the attention of all of the primordial beings on Eight Plains Mountain, and many of them had flown out of their settlements to see what was happening.

"What's going on? Why have all of these dark clouds suddenly appeared?"

"Could it be that someone's triggered a lightning tribulation while making a breakthrough?"

"I don't think so. This doesn't feel like a lightning tribulation. Instead, it seems to be a natural phenomenon brought about by some powerful ability."

All of the primordial beings were perplexed by what they were witnessing, but to their relief, the lightning remained contained within the dark clouds, with none of it crashing down from the heavens above.

It didn't take long before all of the Great Encompassment Stage beings on the mountain were also alerted, and they all began attempting to assess the situation, only for their spiritual sense to be kept out by a burst of immense time law powers.

On the summit of Eight Plains Mountain, Bai Ze emerged from the palace with slightly furrowed brows.

He closed his eyes for a moment, then quickly reopened them as he cast a surprised gaze toward the courtyard where Han Li was staying.

"Impressive," he murmured to himself, then made his way back into the palace.

......

Inside the Flower Branch domain, Han Li was completely oblivious to the phenomena unfolding outside.

At this point, over half of his immortal spiritual power had already been devoured by the Almighty Sword Array Diagram, leaving him looking rather pale.

......

Several years passed by in the blink of an eye.

The primordial tribes were gathering at a rate far faster than Bai Ze anticipated, so he announced that the blood inheritance ceremony was going to be commencing early.

The date was set to around half a year later, and at this point, the entirety of Primordial Garrison City was already in a state of lockdown, with no one permitted to leave after entering the city.

This morning, the sound of a giant drum being struck rang out thrice in succession, causing the entire city to tremble violently. A series of primordial patterns lit up over the city walls, and before long, a vast expanse of dark red light had spread over the entire city.

Han Li emerged from his courtyard with Xiao Bai just in time to see enormous pillars of red light rising up into the sky before exploding like fireworks, forming a dark red light barrier that encompassed the entirety of Primordial Garrison City, Eight Plains Mountain, and the surrounding area in a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers.

The blood inheritance ceremony was finally about to commence!

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the dark red light barrier, and he began to extend his spiritual sense out of the city.

However, as soon as his spiritual sense came into contact with the light barrier, a burst of sharp pain instantly shot through his glabella, while the wisp of spiritual sense that he had released dissipated into nothingness.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

The restriction around the city was extremely formidable, so if anything were to go awry during the blood inheritance ceremony, it would be very difficult for him to escape the city. Thankfully, he always had the trump card of physical transmigration up his sleeve, but of course, that was only to be reserved as a last resort, given the heavy price that he had to pay to use it.

"Is something wrong?" Xiao Bai asked in a concerned manner at the sight of Han Li's dark expression.

"It's alright. Regardless of what happens, I'll be here with you," Han Li replied as he gave Xiao Bai a reassuring pat on the head.

Xiao Bai lowered his head in silence, not pursuing the matter any further.

Ever since he became aware of his Ink-Eyed Pixiu lineage, he had become rather withdrawn and nowhere near as energetic as before. It seemed that he was both looking forward to the blood inheritance ceremony, but also felt a little uneasy.

"Let's go, it's about time that we scaled the mountain," Han Li said as he set off with Xiao Bai toward a plaza at the foot of the mountain.

Even before reaching the foot of the mountain, Han Li could already see countless primordial beings gathered in the distance. There were close to ten thousand of them in total, and at the forefront of the gathering were the Heavenly Fox Tribe and the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe.

Liu Qing was standing at the foot of the mountain with several hundred other Heavenly Fox beings, and situated right next to them was a collection of Mountain Moving Ape beings that also numbered in the hundreds.

Just like the Heavenly Fox Tribe, the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe was also one of the sixteen premier primordial tribes, and it had inherited the bloodline of the Giant Mountain Ape, which was one of the eight True Spirit Kings. However, the bloodline had been diluted further and further generation after generation, and the tribe no longer possessed anywhere the power of the almighty Giant Mountain Ape.

As a result of their thinning Giant Mountain Ape bloodline, they had gradually dropped down the ranks among the sixteen premier tribes, to the point that they were currently considered one of the bottom-dwelling premier tribes.

In terms of physical appearance, Mountain Moving Ape beings were rather similar to Qing Ape beings, except they were far smaller in stature and had dark green fur. Furthermore, they didn't appear as menacing as the Qing Ape beings, and there was a more civilized and intelligent look about them.

Their leader was a hunch-backed elderly man dressed in a white robe with a pair of extremely long, white eyebrows, and he appeared no different from an unremarkable, frail old man.

Even though the two tribes were situated next to each other on the plaza, there was a clear divide between the two of them, indicating that they weren't all that close.

Liu Le'er had already spotted Han Li and Xiao Bai even before they arrived, and a bright smile appeared on her face as she turned to approach them, only to be sternly held back by Liu Qing, who chastised, "Stay focused! We're not here to play around!"

Liu Le'er could only stick out her tongue in a sheepish manner in response.

Han Li gave her a smile and a nod, then calmly made his way onto the plaza with Xiao Bai, while all of the nearby primordial beings looked on with puzzled expressions.

There was a Mountain Moving Ape being nearby that was far smaller in stature than his brethren, standing at only around half the height of an adult human, and his fur was also a pure white color, making him stand out like a sore thumb.

He was looking at Han Li and Xiao Bai with a curious expression, the latter of which bared his fangs in intimidation, clearly not very pleased by the Mountain Moving Ape being's intrigued scrutiny.

Funnily enough, the Mountain Moving Ape beings was quite the coward, and he was so frightened by Xiao Bai's display of intimidation that he immediately ducked behind one of his taller brethren.

Xiao Bai was rather amused by this, and his disgruntled expression was replaced by an amused smile.

The little white ape snuck a glance at Xiao Bai from around the Mountain Moving Ape being that he was hiding behind, and a wide smile also appeared on his face at the sight of Xiao Bai's amused expression.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I understand that His Majesty has given you permission to attend the ceremony, but this is an event of the utmost importance for all of our primordial tribes, so there are some things that I must inform you of," Liu Qing suddenly said.

"Please go ahead, Senior," Han Li prompted.

"A gong will be struck on the mountain summit soon, and that will serve as a signal for the primordial tribes to scale the mountain using the eight paths around the mountain. These mountain paths have restrictions placed upon them by the eight ancient True Spirit Kings, and these restrictions are effective on all living beings.

“Under the effects of these restrictions, even powerful primordial beasts with formidable physical constitutions would struggle to scale the mountain, so make sure to be on your guard and don't push yourself too hard," Liu Qing cautioned.

"Thank you for informing me of this, Senior, I'll keep that in mind," Han Li replied with a nod while taking a concerned glance at Liu Le'er and Xiao Bai.

Neither of them excelled in terms of their physical constitutions, so was it not going to be a struggle for them to scale the mountain?

"There's no need to worry about them. The effects of the restrictions will be less potent on those who possess the bloodlines of the eight ancient True Spirit Kings, so it'll be easier for them to scale the mountain than others," Liu Qing reassured, and Han Li was quite relieved to hear this.

He looked up at the majestic mountain before him to discover that the entire mountain was enshrouded under a layer of dark red light. Directly up ahead was a stone staircase that had been chiseled into the mountain and was over ten thousand feet tall, resembling a giant ladder that led up to the heavens.

Right at this moment, three resounding gong strikes rang out from the mountain summit, sending soundwaves that were visible to the naked eye sweeping through the air in all directions.

These soundwaves seemed to contain some type of special energy fluctuations, and as they washed over him, Han Li felt as if the true spirit bloodlines in his body had been awakened and had begun circulating on their own.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he looked around to discover that all of the surrounding primordial beings' auras had swelled drastically, and faint, pink mist had begun seeping out of their bodies.

Chapter 1174: Scaling the Mountain

All of a sudden, the sound of a melodious horn rang out in the distance, and the sound had a special quality to it that made it impossible for one to ascertain where it was coming from.

Han Li couldn't detect anything special about the sound, but as soon as it traveled into his ears, he immediately felt as if his entire body were filled with boundless strength.

Could this be some type of war song for the primordial tribes?

Immediately thereafter, Han Li heard another sound ringing out directly beside him, and he turned to discover that Xiao Bai had begun emitting a peculiar, snarling sound ringing out from the base of his throat.

"I don't know why, but I was struck by the urge to snarl as soon as I heard the sound of the horn..." Xiao Bai explained to Han Li through their spiritual connection.

Han Li nodded in response, asking no questions on the matter as he began scaling the mountain with Xiao Bai.

As soon as he set foot onto the stone staircase, he immediately felt a burst of indescribable power converging toward him from all directions, making him feel rather heavy and sluggish.

It was a very strange sensation, as if the entire Eight Plains Mountain had transformed into a giant magnet, exerting attractive force upon all those attempting to scale it.

However, this level of interference was not an issue for Han Li, and he was able to continue scaling the mountain just fine.

All of the Heavenly Fox beings and Mountain Moving Ape beings were also largely unaffected, and it didn't take long before all of them ascended past the hundredth step.

Han Li and Xiao Bai were roughly keeping abreast of the Heavenly Fox beings, and the former looked back to discover that there were still several thousand primordial beings standing on the plaza below.

"Le'er, why aren't those people scaling the mountain?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"Because they're not among the top one hundred primordial tribes," Liu Le'er replied. "They're only permitted to stand at the foot of the mountain because they're all subsidiary tribes to the sixteen premier tribes, the other tribes in the city aren't even permitted to approach the holy mountain at all."

"It looks like it's quite an honor to be able to take part in the blood inheritance ceremony," Han Li remarked.

"That is indeed the case. All of the top one hundred primordial tribes have inherited the bloodlines of the eight ancient True Spirit Kings, and that gives them the right to scale the mountain. That's why even Chief Liu Qing was very surprised that you were given permission by His Majesty to scale the holy mountain with Xiao Bai," Liu Le'er explained.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing, but offered no response.

After climbing several hundred more steps, a series of ancient patterns had begun appearing on the steps underfoot, and at this point, many of the primordial beings were beginning to display signs of physical strain.

The Heavenly Fox beings and Mountain Moving Ape beings were still able to maintain their original speed, but the other primordial beings had slowed down to different extents and were gradually being left behind.

To the surprise of all of the Heavenly Fox beings and Mountain Moving Ape beings, Han Li was able to keep up with them just fine, and he wasn't displaying any signs of physical strain in the process.

That served as motivation for them to scale the mountain even faster for fear of bringing shame upon themselves by being left behind by Han Li.

Of course, Han Li wasn't feeling competitive at all, and he continued to scale the mountain with Xiao Bai at a leisurely pace.

Meanwhile, the little white ape was constantly stealing glances at Han Li and Xiao Bai with a curious yet cautious look in his eyes.

Han Li had taken a liking to the little white ape, perhaps due to the fact that he was also carrying the Giant Mountain Ape bloodline himself, so whenever their eyes met, he would give the little ape an encouraging smile.

None of the other Mountain Moving Ape beings seemed to be opposed to what the little white ape was doing, and he eventually worked up the courage to approach Han Li's duo.

However, he was quite wary of Han Li, so he approached Xiao Bai instead.

"What are you doing here?" Xiao Bai asked in a rather unfriendly manner.

The little white ape was unfazed, and he asked, "I hear you have the bloodline of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu, is that right?"

"So what if I do?" Xiao Bai replied.

"Our ancestor was Master Yuan Hong, one of the eight True Spirit Kings, and he was said to have been a very close friend to Master Mo Yu," the little white ape said.

"So what?" Xiao Bai asked with a puzzled expression.

"It's said that the two of them disappeared together," the little white ape replied, and Xiao Bai fell silent upon hearing this.

After a brief silence, he turned to the little white ape and asked, "What's your name?"

"Yuan Shanbai," the little ape replied.

"My name is Xiao Bai. It looks like we both share the bai character in our names," Xiao Bai said with a smile.

"Xiao Bai? Is your name Mo Xiaobai?" the little white ape asked.

Xiao Bai hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then nodded uncertainly in response. With his memories sealed away, he had no idea what his own true name was.

As Xiao Bai and Yuan Shanbai became more and more familiar with each other, the former quickly reverted back to his usual, braggadocious self, rattling off a bunch of stories that had the sheltered Yuan Shanbai jumping with excitement.

After hearing from Xiao Bai that he had an even more powerful boss, Yuan Shanbai's eyes were practically glowing with admiration with yearning.

"I'll introduce you to my boss if I get the chance. She has a rather short temper, but she's a good person at heart. Make sure to prepare a gift for her, and once she accepts you as her lackey, she and I will protect you together," Xiao Bai said.

A look of amusement flashed through Han Li's eyes as he listened to the conversation between the two adolescent beasts.

However, at the same time, he was also in a state of alert, constantly observing the surrounding area for any notable changes.

As he continued to scale the staircase, he discovered that the suction force from the stone steps was only growing stronger and stronger, and many of the tribes had already been left far behind.

On top of that, in addition to the suction force from the ground, bursts of tremendous pressure had also begun to appear in the surrounding space, making it rather arduous for even the Heavenly Fox and Mountain Moving Ape beings to continue their climb.

Upon reaching the halfway mark up the mountain, the pressure in the air had already swelled to over a hundredfold of what could be felt at the foot of the mountain, and even Han Li was beginning to feel short of breath.

Only after channeling the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts did the discomfort fade away, and he continued the ascent.

At this point, all of the other tribes had already been left behind, and many of them had already given up on making further progress up the mountain. Instead, they made their way laterally along the boardwalks to the platforms that were situated partway up the mountain.

Han Li swept his gaze over the mountain to discover a series of round, stone, cushion-like objects laid out over the platforms partway up the mountain, and each of the primordial beings that made their way onto the platforms chose one of those stone cushions to sit on.

As for the Heavenly Fox and Mountain Moving Ape beings, they displayed no intention of stopping as they continued to climb.

The Mountain Moving Ape beings should've possessed superior physical constitutions to the Heavenly Fox beings, but strangely enough, they were collectively slower than the Heavenly Fox beings and were gradually being left behind.

All the while, Yuan Shanbai was leading the way from the forefront while chatting with Xiao Bai.

Upon noticing that his tribesmen were lagging behind, Yuan Shanbai bade farewell to Xiao Bai, then made his way back to the elderly Mountain Moving Ape being's side to continue scaling the mountain with him.

At this point, many of the Heavenly Fox and Mountain Moving Ape beings were stealing puzzled glances at Han Li, wondering how a mere human was able to scale the mountain so easily.

Unbeknownst to them, Han Li currently felt as if he were walking with a huge mountain on his back, and with each step that he took, a shallow footprint would be left behind on the stone step underfoot.

After climbing for several more minutes, Han Li noticed that Xiao Bai seemed to be nearing his limits. Each step that he took was extremely arduous, and he had to take long breaks every few steps.

Han Li slowed down to keep pace with him upon seeing this.

As a result, the Heavenly Fox beings gradually began to overtake him, and only then did they feel a little better about themselves.

Han Li took a glance at Liu Le'er, who had stopped in her tracks and was looking back him with an inquisitive expression. It was clear from the sweat on her forehead and the flush in her cheeks that she was also feeling the strain.

"Go up with Senior Liu Qing, we'll get to the top after you," Han Li said through voice transmission.

Liu Le'er was rather hesitant, but she eventually complied after some urging from Liu Qing.

Han Li knew that Xiao Bai hadn't yet truly awakened his Ink-Eyed Pixiu bloodline, so this was already very close to his limit.

With that in mind, he asked, "Do you need me to help you?"

"No. I heard from Shanbai that scaling the mountain is a test for the eight regal bloodlines in itself. The stronger one's bloodline, the easier it will be for them to scale the mountain. I can't put my bloodline to shame," Xiao Bai replied through gritted teeth, then resumed his ascent with renewed determination.

For a moment, Han Li caught sight of a faint, golden ring of light in Xiao Bai's eyes, but it was only there for a split second before vanishing, leaving Han Li unsure of whether it had only been a figment of his imagination.

Chapter 1175: Reaching the Summit

Before long, it was already noon.

The harsh sunlight was made much softer by the dark red light barrier that the mountain was encompassed within, but many of the primordial beings were beginning to feel a sense of despair at the sight of the distant mountain summit.

There were only a hundred dark red stone steps left between them and the summit, but those hundred stone steps were like an insurmountable barrier to virtually everyone left.

Right at this moment, an agonized cry rang out from the mountain path.

After a long rest, a male Heavenly Fox being had finally mustered up the courage to step onto the first of the hundred dark red stone steps, but in the instant that he set foot onto the stone step, a burst of tremendous power instantly came crashing down upon him from all directions.

As a result, he was crushed to the ground, and a string of loud cracks rang out within his body, indicating multiple broken bones.

Liu Qing's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he strode over to the Heavenly Fox being before tugging him back down a step.

"This is where the real test begins. For those of you who possess weak bloodlines, do not proceed any further beyond this point," Liu Qing warned, and everyone's expressions darkened slightly upon hearing this.

Everyone knew that a massive opportunity had to have been waiting for them on the mountain summit, but the summit was so tantalizingly close, yet simultaneously impossibly far away.

Finally, Han Li also arrived at the foot of the dark red staircase with Xiao Bai.

At this point, he was barely able to breathe, and he was forced to channel the true spirit bloodlines in his body to help alleviate the immense pressure weighing down upon him.

As for Xiao Bai, his fur was completely drenched in sweat, and he was laying at Han Li's feet like a dead dog.

Before long, the Mountain Moving Ape beings had also caught up, but there were only four or five of them left, including Yuan Shanbai and the elderly chief.

All of them stopped near Han Li and Xiao Bai, and Yuan Shanbai took a glance at the latter before giving him a thumbs-up as a sign of respect.

Xiao Bai immediately struggled to his paws again with renewed vigor.

Liu Qing turned back to look at all of the people who had made it to this point, and as his gaze swept over Han Li, the befuddlement in his eyes only grew more pronounced.

Han Li had already grown accustomed to this.

He had even noticed that the elderly chief of the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe was also secretly watching him through his long eyebrows.

Not only were they perplexed, Han Li was also wondering how he had managed to make it to this point. Could it have something to do with the Giant Mountain Ape bloodline in his body? After all, the Giant Mountain Ape was also one of the eight ancient True Spirit Kings.

Right at this moment, the Heavenly Fox Tribe continued its ascent, but only seven of them, including Liu Qing and Liu Le'er, continued onward, while the rest sat down with their legs crossed on the stone steps.

As these seven Heavenly Fox beings stepped onto the first dark red step, all of them began to glow with radiant, white light, with the exception of Liu Qing, and a series of thick, white fox tails extended out of their bodies.

Han Li noticed that most of them possessed seven or eight tails each, while Liu Le'er was the only one who possessed only six tails, but the white light radiating from her body was the brightest of all.

On top of that, Han Li could sense the purest and most potent primordial aura from Liu Le'er, excelling in this regard even beyond Chief Liu Qing.

This was quite reassuring to Han Li, and turned to Xiao Bai as he said, "Let's go up as well."

Xiao Bai nodded arduously in response, and the two of them continued their ascent.

Even though Han Li was already mentally prepared, as soon as he set foot onto the first dark red stone step, he still couldn't help but stumble forward under the immense pressure that abruptly came crashing down upon him.

He was forced to press his hands against the stone step to support himself, and he was unable to stand up from his hunched over posture.

Xiao Bai wasn't faring much better. His legs were trembling incessantly as he struggled against the tremendous pressure, and a strangled sound was coming out of his mouth.

Han Li turned his gaze to Xiao Bai, then let loose a low roar as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and true spirit bloodlines with all his might, instantly transforming into a devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

In this form, he resembled a giant spider that loomed over Xiao Bai, shielding him from some of the pressure in the air.

With Han Li standing over him like a protective umbrella, Xiao Bai was able to just barely steady himself, and he began climbing up the steps.

After climbing around a dozen steps, Xiao Bai felt like he had grown somewhat accustomed to the pressure, and he expressed a desire to continue the climb through his own power.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, but ultimately decided to respect Xiao Bai's wishes and moved away to the side.

As a result, the pressure in the air came crashing down upon Xiao Bai once again in full force, almost crushing him to his haunches.

However, after an almighty struggle, he was able to remain upright and began trudging arduously up the steps.

As they progressed up the stone staircase, the pressure was only becoming more and more immense, and even Han Li felt as if he were nearing his limits, let alone Xiao Bai.

With only ten steps left, blood was beginning to flow out of Xiao Bai's nose and mouth, staining the already red stone steps an even more vibrant shade of red, which Han Li looked on with his brows tightly furrowed with concern.

Right at this moment, a Heavenly Fox being who was only one step away from reaching the mountain summit suddenly fell unconscious, and he toppled backward before hurtling down toward Xiao Bai.

His body wasn't particularly imposing, but compounded by the terrifying spatial pressure, it was akin to a mountain tumbling down in freefall.

At the moment, Xiao Bai was so close to reaching his limit that his ears were ringing incessantly, and his vision had become completely blurred, rendering him completely unable to take any evasive measures. In his current state, even a feather would've been enough to crush him, let alone a tumbling body.

In this dire situation, he saw a black shadow flash past his eyes to intercept the falling Heavenly Fox being, following which both of them were sent tumbling down the mountain.

At the same time, Han Li's voice rang out beside him.

"You're almost there, don't give up!"

Xiao Bai shuddered as some clarity returned to his vision, but Han Li was already nowhere to be seen.

He turned back to discover Han Li tumbling down the mountain with the unconscious Heavenly Fox being.

Moved by Han Li's sacrifice, a sense of renewed strength and determination welled up in his heart as he gritted his teeth and let loose a feral snarl.

At the same time, a ring of golden light appeared around each of his pupils, and all of a sudden, it was as if his body had been granted a burst of unprecedented power.

With this newfound power, he was able to quickly climb his way to the mountain summit, but before he even had a chance to celebrate, his vision faded to darkness as he fell to the ground in an unconscious state.

Liu Le'er had already reached the mountain summit, and she hurriedly rushed over to Xiao Bai to examine his condition.

A handsome, white-robed man approached the scene and said in a reassuring voice, "He's fine. He fell unconscious because he forcibly tapped into the bloodline power that's been sealed away in his body, but he should regain consciousness soon."

"Your Majesty!" Liu Le'er exclaimed as she looked up to discover that it was True Spirit King Bai Ze.

"You can go rest, I'll look after him," Bai Ze said, and Liu Le'er did as she was told.

Bai Ze gently picked Xiao Bai up from the ground, then fed him a red pill as he cast his gaze down the mountain with a pleased expression.

It looks like you chose a splendid master...

At this point, Han Li had already disentangled himself from the unconscious Heavenly Fox being, and he was frantically grabbing at the surrounding stone steps with his six arms to try and steady himself, but he continued to tumble downward in an involuntary manner.

Under the immense spatial pressure, each tumble that he took jolted his body to the core. If he were to fall all the way to the foot of the mountain in this manner, perhaps his external injuries wouldn't be very severe, but his internal organs were sure to sustain some damage.

Right at this moment, a giant hand suddenly reached out from down below to catch him, withstanding the momentum of his tumbling body to stop him cold in his tracks.

Han Li threw up a mouthful of blood upon impact, then turned to discover that he had been intercepted by the chief of the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe.

"Thank you, Senior," Han Li hurriedly said with a grateful salute, and the elderly man gave him a smile before continuing to ascend the mountain with Yuan Shanbai.

Meanwhile, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed, then took a pill before closing his eyes to rest. A short while later, he felt like he had recovered some strength, and he rose to his feet again as he cast his gaze toward the mountain summit.

In the wake of the injuries that he had sustained, scaling the mountain had become even more difficult than before, but he was determined to persevere.

Chapter 1176: You Enter the Palace as Well

Time slowly passed, and before long, the mountain summit had been basked in the light of the setting sun, presenting a beautiful sight to behold.

At this point, there were already close to a hundred people gathered on the plaza on the mountain summit, close to twenty of which were Great Encompassment cultivators, sixteen of whom were the chiefs of the sixteen premier primordial tribes.

Aside from these Great Encompassment Stage beings, the rest of the people gathered on the plaza were all the brightest young talents with the purest bloodlines in the primordial tribes, and only they were able to endure the climb to the mountain summit.

Among the tribes present, the Huntun Tribe had the most people, numbering in excess of ten, while the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe had the least people, namely only Yuan Shanbai and the tribal chief.

The Huntun Tribe was a descendant tribe of the Rahu, one of the eight ancient True Spirit Kings, and theirs was an extremely powerful tribe.

Their current chief was a tall and imposing middle-aged man dressed in a very eye-catching, embroidered purple robe, outside of which was a suit of black scale armor. His entire body was bulging with muscles that gave off an appearance of explosive power.

His facial features were extremely hideous, with his entire face riddled with sharp spkes, and his mouth was as wide as that of a toad. There was also a short, purple beard on his chin, and the individual strands of hair in the beard appeared as sharp and straight as steel needles.

His enormous aura indicated that he was a late-Great Encompassment cultivator, and at this moment, he was scouring the entire plaza with a perplexed look on his face.

After a brief hesitation, he made his way to the center of the plaza, where he extended a respectful salute toward Bai Ze, then asked, "Your Majesty, it appears that everyone has already gathered, so why has the blood inheritance ceremony still not commenced?"

"We're waiting on one more person. He should be here soon," Bai Ze replied.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a low roar suddenly rang out from the northern edge of the plaza, following which a giant spider-like figure sprang up into the air before crashing down onto the plaza.

It was naturally none other than Han Li.

In addition to his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and true spirit bloodlines, he had also been forced to make use of his time law powers, and even then, it had taken him over six hours to finally reach the mountain summit.

Xiao Bai and Liu Le'er immediately rushed over to him with elated expressions, while he reverted back to his human form.

Even so, everyone had already caught a glimpse of his devilish deity form, and aura quickly came under scrutiny as well.

The chief of the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe wasn't all that surprised to see Han Li reach the mountain summit, but the chiefs of the other tribes were far less composed.

The first one to speak up was a purple-faced, middle-aged man with a pair of black wings on his back, and he exclaimed in a furious voice, "That's a human! Why has a human been allowed to scale our holy mountain?"

He was the chief of the Soaring Leopard Tribe, a descendant tribe of the Taowu. However, their bloodline wasn't as pure as that of the Zouwu Tribe, and the founding ancestor of their tribe was none other than a certain patriarch of the Zouwu Tribe.

Hence, even though they were also one of the sixteen premier primordial tribes, they were considered to be inferior in seniority to the Zouwu Tribe.

Another halberd-wielding man with the head of a falcon also sprang to his feet, and arcs of silver lightning flashed over his wings as he yelled, "Why does he possess multiple true spirit auras?"

This man was the chief of the Silver Winged Lightning Bird Tribe, another one of the sixteen premier primordial tribes.

The other tribal chiefs present were also very alarmed by the sight of Han Li, and it was clear that they were far from pleased to see him.

All the while, a hunch-backed elderly man from the Qing Ape Tribe was looking on in silence with a cold smile on his face.

He was the chief of the Qing Ape Tribe, and he had been made aware of Han Li's status as a human before most of the other tribal chiefs present.

Qing Dian and Qing Chu were both standing behind him, glowering at Han Li with resentful expressions.

Bai Ze's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the animosity directed at Han Li, and Lekima immediately took that as his cue to step forward and declare, "Don't be alarmed, everyone. Fellow Daoist Han Li has been invited here by His Majesty to attend the ceremony."

Everyone instantly fell silent upon hearing this, and despite the questioning looks in their eyes, no one raised any objections or queries.

"Rest assured, everyone, Fellow Daoist Han is a friend of our primordial tribes," Lekima continued. "In fact, he was the one who found the only remaining offspring of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu King and brought him back to our primordial land."

"So he's the one..." someone exclaimed.

Clearly, stories of some of Han Li's feats had already begun to make the rounds among the primordial tribes.

Han Li wasn't surprised in the slightest by everyone's reactions, but he was very much taken aback by the sight of a certain figure in the Zouwu Tribe.

Standing at the forefront of the Zouwu Tribe was a white-haired young man with his hands clasped behind his back, observing Han Li with a cold smile.

It was the same person who had attempted to steal his dao pills all those years ago, and there was a clear flash of mutual recognition as soon as their eyes met.

Han Li then turned his gaze to the Heavenly Fox Tribe, and he discovered that there was another familiar figure among them that he hadn't seen before, namely Fox 3.

The two of them exchanged a glance and a nod, but before they had a chance to communicate through voice transmission, Han Li was called over to the center of the plaza by Lekima.

"I pay my respects to the True Spirit King," Han Li greeted as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Bai Ze, who smiled and nodded in response.

"We can begin the ceremony now," Bai Ze declared, and all of the primordial beings present immediately gathered on the platform.

Bai Ze arrived before everyone and said, "Today's blood inheritance ceremony is an event of the utmost importance for our primordial tribes. At the moment, turmoil is building in the entire True Immortal Realm, and the all-encompassing tribulation that was prophesied by the Inky-Eyed Pixiu all those years ago is most likely already upon us."

Most of the primordial beings present were rather perplexed to hear this, but the expressions of all of the chiefs had changed drastically, clearly indicating that they were aware of the prophecy in question.

Han Li was naturally unaware of this prophecy, but he had personally witnessed the brewing unrest in the True Immortal Realm of late, so he was able to understand Bai Ze's concerns.

Xiao Bai was just as oblivious as everyone else, but he was listening particularly intently, seeing as the prophecy in question had been left behind by his father.

"On this day, we will be opening the Holy Primordial Palace and the Asura Blood Gate. The thrones of the eight kings have been empty for far too long, and it's time to restore the eight True Spirit Kings to resurrect the former glory of our primordial land!" Bai Ze continued, and this declaration was met with a collective cheer.

......

The eyes of all of the primordial beings present were glowing with excitement, but Han Li was rather perplexed.

Could it be that this blood inheritance ceremony can somehow summon back the missing True Spirit Kings?

"Representatives of the sixteen premier tribes, step forward!" Bai Ze ordered, and Lekima was the first to oblige, stepping forward in a proud manner.

Liu Le'er emerged from the Heavenly Fox Tribe, while Qing Dian stepped forward from the Qing Ape Tribe. Somehow, the tusk that had been snapped by Han Li had already been restored to its former condition.

The white-haired young man emerged from the Zouwu Tribe, and the representatives of all of the other tribes also quickly stepped forward at Bai Ze's behest.

The representative for the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe was none other than Yuan Shanbai, and he stepped forward before taking a glance in Han Li's direction.

Xiao Bai was standing beside Han Li, looking rather hesitant, only after receiving a smile and an encouraging nod from Han Li did Xiao Bai leave his side to step forward as well.

"All representatives, enter the holy palace with me. Everyone else, remain on the plaza to await the array's activation," Bai Ze ordered, and everyone did as they were told.

With that, Bai Ze began to make his way toward a round, stone palace behind the plaza, followed by Lekima and the other tribal representatives.

All of a sudden, Bai Ze stopped in his tracks, then turned to Han Li as he instructed, "You enter the palace as well."

Chapter 1177: New Kings

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this, while the rest of the primordial beings were nothing short of astonished.

To them, the Holy Primordial Palace was an even more sacred place than the holy mountain. It was the center of their faith, and allowing a human to enter the palace was blasphemy and sacrilege of the highest order!

Even Lekima was rather perplexed by this turn of events.

"Your Majesty, no!" the chief of the Huntun Tribe exclaimed, and all of the other tribal chiefs also voiced their vehement objections to this decision.

Qing Dian and the young master of the Zouwu Tribe had also turned to Han Li with mixed emotions in their eyes. They had no idea that Bai Ze held Han Li in such high regard, and they were beginning to wonder if it would be a good idea to try and exact vengeance against him.

A hesitant look also appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing these vehement objections, but Bai Ze declared in an authoritative voice, "This Holy Primordial Palace was constructed by myself and the other seven True Spirit Kings, so I get to decide who gets to go in."

All of the primordial beings continued to voice their objections, but Bai Ze had already turned to depart.

Lekima and the other representatives hurriedly followed along, and after a brief hesitation, Han Li ultimately decided to oblige.

Even after they had already entered the palace, the objections were still ringing out incessantly.

However, as soon as the heavy gates of the palace were shut, all of the dissenting voices were instantly drowned out.

The interior of the palace was very dimly lit, with a lit brazier at the center of the palace serving as the only light source.

Han Li looked around to discover a series of tall stone statues, of which there were eight in total, and they depicted the Taowu, the Zhuyan, the Rahu, Bai Ze, the Giant Mountain Ape, the Sky Roaming Kun Peng, the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox, and the Ink-Eyed Pixiu.

In front of each statue was a stone chair, but all of them had clearly been vacant for a very long time.

Liu Le'er was staring at the statue of the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox, and she could sense a faint connection to it.

Meanwhile, Xiao Bai was staring intently at the statue of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu. Even though the state was very similar to himself in appearance, he felt no sense of connection or affinity to it at all. Instead, it appeared completely alien and distant.

All of the other representatives were also looking at their corresponding bloodline ancestors with a wide spectrum of different emotions in their eyes, including curiosity, veneration, and excitement.

"These are the statues of the eight ancient True Spirit Kings. Some of them were my close friends, while others were sworn enemies of mine, but all of us set our differences aside for the sake of bringing peace to the primordial land.

“Together, we built this Holy Primordial Palace for it to serve as a home for the Asura Blood Gate, and all of you have gathered here today to use the true spirit king bloodlines in your bodies as keys to unlock these gates," Bai Ze declared.

"Please tell us what needs to be done, Your Majesty," everyone implored in unison.

"Out of the eight True Spirit Kings, the Rahu and the Sky Roaming Kun Peng left Eight Plains Mountain not long after this place was built, while the rest have all gone missing. It's unclear what fates they have met, and it's entirely possible that they could be dead. The only way to find out if any of them are still alive would be through observing the opening of the gates," Bai Ze continued, making no effort to hide these secrets from Han Li.

To all of the primordial beings present, the ancestors who had bestowed their bloodlines upon them were nothing short of legendary deities, and it was very difficult for them to come to terms with the fact that some, or perhaps even most of these legendary figures were no longer of this world.

"There's no need to feel dejected. All of us are born from heaven and earth, and we possess certain innate powers and abilities. Even if we perish, our bloodline powers will fuse with the laws of time, and they'll be gradually devoured by the Heavenly Dao, but won't disappear completely.

“Once the Asura Blood Gate is opened, those bloodline powers will return to the Holy Primordial Palace, and as heirs to their bloodlines, there's a very good chance that you'll inherit their power to become new True Spirit Kings!" Bai Ze declared.

Everyone was astonished to hear this.

The notion of becoming a new True Spirit King was most likely the most alluring thing conceivable for a primordial being.

At this point, their hearts were filled with conflicted emotions, and they didn't know if they should hope for their true spirit ancestors' return, or pray that they had already perished.

Bai Ze could see the changes in everyone's expressions, but he displayed no reaction.

He was well aware of what everyone was thinking, but it didn't matter to him.

"The flame in the brazier before all of you was collectively lit by the eight of us. Right now, it's far weaker than before, indicating that some of them really have perished. All representatives, heed my call," Bai Ze ordered, and everyone stepped forward to surround the brazier, while Han Li trailed along a small distance away, standing behind Xiao Bai as he observed everything in silence.

The animosity that everyone felt toward Han Li abated slightly at this thoughtful gesture, but in their eyes, it was still a disgrace to the holy palace that a human had been allowed to enter it.

However, none of them dared to display their displeasure in the presence of the True Spirit King.

Bai Ze swept his gaze over everyone, then joined his palms together in front of his chest, releasing waves of rippling, golden light that proliferated through the air in expanding layers.

A series of large, golden flowers that resembled lotus flowers emerged over the ground beneath the waves of golden light, and everyone reflexively moved back in retreat upon seeing this.

Han Li focused his gaze on the golden flowers to discover that they were formed by clusters of dense runes that were giving off a very peculiar aura.

In the presence of this aura, everyone felt as if their bloodlines had been connected with their own bodies, following which it felt as if their feet had taken root to the ground, becoming inseparable from the earth.

Han Li's feet were also rooted to the ground like everyone else, and initially, he was quite alarmed by this turn of events, but he quickly discovered that this was simply a result of the true spirit bloodlines in his body connecting with the earth beneath his feet.

He could easily sever this bloodline connection to free himself, but after a brief hesitation, he ultimately decided not to as he could clearly sense that the true spirit bloodlines in his body were quite fond of this connection.

As these golden flowers began to bloom, specks of light that resembled gold dust rose up from the ground to quickly fill the entire palace, giving everything a rather hazy and murky appearance.

A layer of gold dust fell upon the eight True Spirit King statues, all of which began to glow radiantly like manifestations of deities.

A reminiscent look flashed through Bai Ze's eyes upon seeing this, and he strode over to his own statues before sitting down onto the stone chair in front of it.

"Each of you, extract a drop of your own essential blood essence and cast it into the brazier," he instructed.

Everyone immediately carried out the instruction without any hesitation, with each of them extending a hand forward before forcing out a drop of essential blood essence.

The palace was so quiet that the sound of the blood essence dripping down into the brazier was clearly audible, and the golden flame inside instantly reared up, while a series of illusory shadows appeared within it.

Han Li swept his gaze over golden flame to discover that the shadows were projections of the true forms of the eight True Spirit King.

Immediately thereafter, eight fiery shadows flew out of the golden flame, and each of them flew toward one of the eight surrounding statues before vanishing into their glabellas.

The eight statues instantly began to tremble violently while radiating dazzling light, filling the entire stone palace with five-colored radiance.

At the same time, bursts of bright light rose up from all of the mountain paths leading up Eight Plains Mountain, illuminating the entire heavens.

Eight enormous true spirit projections appeared in the night sky, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold, and all of the primordial beings on Eight Plains Mountain immediately fell to their knees and began kowtowing in reverence and prayer.

There was no one striking the gong on the mountain summit or the drum at the foot of the mountain, but they began sounding off on their own, and all of a sudden, the sound of that melodious primordial war song rang out over the entire mountain, spreading far and wide.

Just like the primordial beings on the mountain, millions of primordial beings fell to their knees in prayer in Primordial Garrison City, but right at this moment, the projection of the Giant Mountain Ape in the night sky suddenly faded away.

At the same time, the ball of holy fire that had flown into the statues of the Giant Mountain Ape in the Holy Primordial Palace also faded away, while the gold dust that had fallen upon the statue became completely devoid of luster.

This triggered a chain reaction, and the holy flames on the glabellas of all of the other statues also flew back into the brazier in rapid succession, following which the statues themselves fell completely dim.

Everyone on the plaza on the mountain summit immediately turned to the chief of the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe with furious expressions upon seeing this. The disintegration of the Giant Mountain Ape projection was a clear indication that the chosen bloodline heir was not fit to inherit its bloodline at all.

Chapter 1178: Asura Blood Gate

"It seems like that little white ape from your tribe doesn't possess sufficient bloodline power to serve as a bloodline heir, Fellow Daoist Yuan Jing," the chief of the Qing Ape Tribe remarked.

"I knew your tribe should've been removed from the ranks of the sixteen premier tribes long ago! None of you possess any regal bloodlines in your bodies!" a tall, ape-like man with a mat of long, white fur on his back yelled in an accusatory manner.

He was the chief of the Whiteback Ghost Ape Tribe, one of the sixteen premier primordial tribes that had inherited the bloodline of the Zhuyan True Spirit King. Of course, their bloodline wasn't as strong as that of the Qing Ape Tribe, and it had always served as a lapdog of the Qing Ape Tribe.

The chief of the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe heaved a faint sigh and didn't say anything.

In contrast with the other True Spirit Kings, the Giant Mountain Ape only left behind one descendant bloodline branch in the form of the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe. On top of that, it wasn't a bloodline inheritance in a traditional sense, so their bloodline power had become weaker and weaker with each passing generation.

Yuan Shanbai was an anomaly in the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe in that his Giant Mountain Ape bloodline was far purer than that of his tribesmen, but his bloodline power was clearly still insufficient, perhaps because he was still yet to reach full maturity.

More and more people were beginning to chime in with accusations of their own, and it was a similar scene inside the Holy Primordial Palace, with Yuan Shanbai surrounded by hostile figures with a guilty look on his face.

Xiao Bai couldn't bear to stand by any longer, and he stepped forward in front of Yuan Shanbai as he yelled, "Stop blaming him for everything! It's not like he did it on purpose!"

Liu Le'er didn't say anything, but she had also chosen to stand with them.

"So what if it's not on purpose? That still doesn't change the fact that he's a useless piece of trash!" the young master of the Zouwu Tribe scoffed.

"If we can't open the Asura Blood Gate, then your Mountain Moving Ape Tribe will be to blame!" Qing Dian accused, and this statement garnered widespread support from the tribal representatives, all of whom were furious at losing the opportunity to inherit the bloodlines of the True Spirit Kings because of Yuan Shanbai.

Right at this moment, Bai Ze suddenly called out to Han Li, and everyone instantly fell silent as they turned to Han Li as well.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this. Just as he had anticipated, the True Spirit King had not invited him here for no reason.

Even though he already understood Bai Ze's intentions, he still pretended to be oblivious, turning to Bai Ze with an inquisitive gaze.

Bai Ze stood up from his stone chair, then turned to everyone else present as he said, "All of you were vehemently opposed to my decision to allow Fellow Daoist Han to enter the palace, but unbeknownst to all of you, his assistance will be vital to opening the Asura Blood Gate."

"What?!"

Everyone was astonished to hear this, perplexed about why human intervention was required to open the Asura Blood Gate.

"There's nothing wrong with the bloodline in Shanbai's body, it's just that he's still too young, so his bloodline hasn't been completely activated. Even though Fellow Daoist Han is a human, he possesses the bloodline of the Giant Mountain Ape, and it's far purer than the bloodline of the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe," Bai Ze explained.

Everyone immediately turned to Han Li with stunned expressions upon hearing this.

"Fellow Daoist Han, are you willing to help us?" Bai Ze asked.

"I possess a rather chaotic mix of bloodlines in my body, so I'm not sure if I can live up to your expectations," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

"That's fine, I have a way to bring your Giant Mountain Ape bloodline to the fore. As long as you agree to help us, you can also enter one of the Asura Blood Gate once they're opened, and that will be immensely beneficial to furthering your physical cultivation," Bai Ze said.

Conflicted looks appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this. They were naturally opposed to the prospect of allowing Han Li to enter an Asura Blood Gate, but at the same time, they were forced to rely on his help to open the gates.

Han Li turned to Qing Dian and the young master of the Zouwu Tribe with a peculiar look in his eyes upon hearing this, and both of them were instantly struck by a sense of foreboding.

"I have another request, and if it can be fulfilled, then I'm willing to help," Han Li said.

"Go ahead," Bai Ze prompted.

"I require two drops of blood essence, one of the Taowu and one of the Zhuyan," Han Li declared.

"That's not a problem. Once the Asura Blood Gate is opened, their bloodlines will be inherited, and I can easily extract two drops of the purest blood essence for you," Bai Ze replied with a smile.

"There's no need for that, I'm happy to receive a drop of blood essence each from those two," Han Li said as he gestured toward Qing Dian and the young master of the Zouwu Tribe.

Bai Ze was rather surprised to hear this. After all, the blood essence of Qing Dian and the young master of the Zouwu Tribe were nowhere near as powerful as the actual True Spirit King bloodlines.

Unbeknownst to him, Han Li wasn't pursuing the most powerful individual bloodlines. Instead, he had to ensure that all of the true spirit bloodlines in his body remained balanced, so he wasn't doing this to spite Qing Dian and the young master of the Zouwu Tribe.

At the moment, he was missing two bloodlines from his Twelve Awakening Transformations, and out of the eight True Spirit Kings, and the Taowu and the Zhuyan possessed the most formidable physical constitutions and defensive prowess, making them the ideal choices in his eyes.

Bai Ze hesitated momentarily, then nodded in agreement.

The resentment in Qing Dian's eyes only became more pronounced as he glowered at Han Li, while a hint of rage also flashed through the eyes of the young master of the Zouwu Tribe, but he then quickly put on a smile as he said, "I'm happy to spare a drop of my blood essence to a benefactor of all of our primordial tribes like Fellow Daoist Han."

He then forced a drop of blood essence from the palm of his hand before sending it flying slowly toward Han Li.

Qing Dian turned to him with a perplexed expression, and the latter said to him through voice transmission, "Just comply with his request for now, Fellow Daoist Qing Dian. Once we've inherited the True Spirit King bloodlines, we'll be able to crush him with ease."

An enlightened look appeared on Qing Dian's face upon hearing this, and he immediately handed over a drop of his own blood essence as well.

Han Li drew the two drops of blood essence into his grasp, and after a brief inspection, he was surprised to discover that they hadn't been tampered with at all.

"You have my thanks," Han Li said as he stowed the drops of blood essence away in a pair of jade vials, following which he offered up a drop of his own blood essence to Bai Ze.

Bai Ze drew the drop of blood essence into his grasp, and with a casual sweep of his sleeve, the drop of blood essence began bubbling as if it had been set alight. Before long, all that remained was the blood essence of the Giant Mountain Ape, while everything else had been burned away.

With a flick of his finger, the drop of blood essence flew into the brazier.

The flame inside the brazier instantly reared up as if oil had been spilled into it, and the fire flew toward the glabella of the Giant Mountain Ape statue, basking the entire palace in golden radiance once again.

On the plaza outside, everyone was still reprimanding the chief of the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe when the ground suddenly began to tremble beneath their feet, and bursts of light rose up from the eight mountain paths to reform the projections of the eight True Spirit Kings, this time glowing even brighter than before.

All of the primordial beings on Eight Plains Mountain and in Primordial Garrison City immediately fell to their knees again to resume their prayers.

Meanwhile, more streaks of light continued to rise up from the ground before converging in the heavens, and a series of ancient altar that had been buried for countless years across the boundless primordial land were suddenly awakened, giving off incandescent, golden light even without anyone controlling them.

Countless primordial beings were struck by the instinctive urge to kneel down in prayer, and in this instant, it was as if the entire primordial land had been connected to form a single entity.

Countless streaks of crimson light converged from all directions in the air above the summit of Eight Plains Mountain, forming an enormous gate of crimson light.

There was a giant Asura face on each of the two pillars on either side of the gate, one of which was furious and menacing in appearance, while the other wore a benevolent smile.

The gates in between the pair of pillars displayed a wide array of primordial true spirit projections, not just of the eight True Spirit Kings, but also many others, such as the True Dragon, the Heavenly Phoenix, the White Tiger, and the Xuanwu Turtle.

......

Everyone on the plaza instantly erupted into ecstatic cheers at the sight of the Asura Blood Gate's emergence, and the chief of the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe was also looking very relieved.

In contrast, the atmosphere in the stone palace was rather heavy.

At the moment, six of the eight stone chairs in front of the True Spirit King statues had been occupied, but only the one in front of Bai Ze's statue was actually occupied by a true, living being, namely Bai Ze himself, while all of the other chairs were occupied by humanoid projections that were extremely life-like in appearance, but were only bloodline soul remnants.

Everyone felt a sense of bloodline connection to the projections, but at the same time, the projections also seemed impossibly far away.

Xiao Bai made his way over to the projection of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu, and he looked up at the projection of the handsome middle-aged man with a hopeful look in his eyes.

"It looks like all of the other eight kings have already perished with the exceptions of the Rahu and the Sky Roaming Kun Peng," Bai Ze remarked as he rose to his feet, and there was no detectable melancholy or joy in his voice, only a faint hint of reminiscence.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the crimson projections surged into the brazier in the palace like streams of smoke, and the flame in the brazier instantly rose up to form a fist-sized crimson fireball.

"Come," Bai Ze called out as he drew the fireball into his grasp, then led everyone out onto the plaza outside.

"Your Majesty!" everyone called out in excitement at the sight of Bai Ze's re-emergence.

"Today marks the beginning of the primordial land's return to its former glory!" Bai Ze declared as he made his way over to the Asura Blood Gate, then swept a sleeve through the air to send the crimson fireball flying into the gates.

A dull thud rang out as the crimson fireball exploded, forming a sea of crimson flames that swallowed up the entire gate.

All of the true spirit projections on the gate sprang to life within the sea of fire, and a crimson vortex emerged at its center, marking the official opening of the Asura Blood Gate.

Chapter 1179: Spirit Summoning

Beyond the Asura Blood Gate was a crimson world with bursts of formidable bloodline power fluctuations surging out from within.

Han Li could see that the crimson world was completely filled with liquid-like crimson light that contained unimaginably potent bloodline power, over ten times more potent than that of the blood pond in the altar inside the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

All of the people on the plaza could sense these incredibly potent bloodline power fluctuations, and looks of excitement and yearning surfaced in their eyes.

"The opening of the Asura Blood Gate is a rare opportunity. All of you gathered on the plaza right now may enter," Bai Ze declared, then led the way through the gate.

A chorus of thunderous cheers rang out from everyone on the plaza, and they immediately followed Bai Ze through the gate.

The tribes that had directly descended from the eight ancient True Spirit Kings were the first ones to enter through the gate behind Bai Ze, but as opposed to following her Heavenly Fox tribesmen through the gate, Liu Le'er was looking at Han Li with her brows slightly furrowed.

"Rest assured, Young Mistress Le'er, His Majesty has permitted Fellow Daoist Han to enter the gate, so he'll be coming in as well," Fox 3 reassured, and Liu Le'er gave him a faint smile upon hearing this, then stepped into the Asura Blood Gate.

Fox 3 turned to take a glance at Han Li, then followed along behind her.

The tribes gathered on the plaza entered the Asura Blood Gate one by one in order of power and status, and Han Li didn't want to irk any of the tribes, so he only entered the Asura Blood Gate after everyone else had already gone in.

Due to the fact that Bai Ze had already permitted Han Li to enter the gate, no one dared to say anything, in spite of their clear displeasure at Han Li's presence.

Some of the primordial beings were observing Han Li with clear wariness and animosity in his eyes, but Han Li paid them no heed.

Inside the Asura Blood Gate was a massive space, the entire ground of which seemed to consist of moving, bright red flesh. The entire area was filled with crimson mist, but there was no bloody odor in the air at all. Instead, there was a refreshing scent in the air, and with each inhalation, everyone was struck by a sense of reinvigoration, as if they had been fed some type of energy tonic.

Hovering above the crimson space was a blanket of crimson clouds that were giving off incredibly potent bloodline aura fluctuations, and they were very similar to the Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds in the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

This was not what Han Li had expected to see at all, and he couldn't help but sweep his gaze over his surroundings in an intrigued manner.

All of the younger primordial beings present were also looking around with surprise and wonder in their eyes, but the older primordial beings, such as Liu Qing, were looking far more composed, as if they had already been here in the past.

Bai Ze continued onward without pause, and everyone else hurriedly followed along.

The group quickly made their way deep into the crimson space, arriving in a spacious area where the ground was very flat and level, resembling a crimson plaza.

Standing on the plaza were eight massive, crimson stone pillars that extended all the way up into the crimson clouds above. A giant, majestic beast was engraved onto each of the pillars, and they depicted none other than the eight True Spirit Kings.

The reliefs of the eight True Spirit Kings were extremely vivid and life-like, and they were all giving off tremendous auras like living beings, as if they could spring to life and emerge from the stone pillars at any moment.

Furthermore, there was a dark red brazier embedded into each pillar, but aside from the stone pillars belonging to Bai Ze, the Sky Roaming Kun Peng, and the Rahu, the braziers in all of the stone pillars had been snuffed out.

All of the primordial beings gathered around near the eight stone pillars, then knelt down and kowtowed to the reliefs of the eight True Spirit Kings.

Griefstricken looks appeared on the faces of all of the Qing Ape, Zouwu, Mountain Moving Ape, and Heavenly Fox beings as they knelt down and wept in front of the stone statues belonging to the Zhuyan, the Taowu, the Giant Mountain Ape, and the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox.

Xiao Bai had also arrived in front of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu pillar with tears swimming in his eyes, while Han Li was looking completely out of place, so he quietly distanced himself from everyone.

He looked at the potent bloodline power in the surrounding area, and as he secretly channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, bursts of heat instantly began to spread through his entire body.

Before long, several unopened profound acupoints had begun to stir, but with so many primordial beings present, he didn't dare to act too blatantly, so he could only absorb the bloodline power in the surrounding environment in a surreptitious manner.

At the same time, he was also observing the eight crimson stone pillars up ahead.

Bai Ze's cultivation base was completely unfathomable to him, so he had to have been a Dao Ancestor. Given that the eight True Spirit Kings were all presumably roughly on par in power, the other True Spirit Kings were most likely also Doa Ancestors.

This was a reflection of the primordial land's immense power, and it was unclear whether there were any more Dao Ancestors in the primordial land outside of the eight True Spirit Kings.

After waiting for a short while, Bai Ze said, "I understand your grief at the passing of the True Spirit Kings, but this is the stark reality that we must accept. The Asura Blood Gate will only be open for a limited time, so all of you must collect yourselves to focus on summoning the bloodlines of the True Spirit Kings."

All of the primordial beings present immediately composed themselves and rose to their feet, then quickly sat down with their legs crossed around their tribes' stone pillars.

Due to the fact that Bai Ze was already here, there was no need for him to be summoned, so Lekima was standing together with him.

The Ink-Eyed Pixiu only had a single descendant in the form of Xiao Bai, so he was the only one at his pillar, cutting a rather lonesome figure, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"Fellow Doiast Han," Lekima greeted as he flew over to Han Li's side, and Han Li nodded silently in response.

Lekima could see the concern in Han Li's eyes, and he smiled as he reassured, "Don't worry, Fellow Daoist Han, there's no danger associated with summoning the True Spirit King bloodlines."

Han Li was still a little concerned, and he said, "Xiao Bai is all on his own. I'm worried that he won't be able to stand up to the other tribes."

"Don't worry, summoning the True Spirit King bloodlines doesn't depend on numbers. Xiao Bai may be only one person, but he's the son of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu True Spirit King, which means that he possesses the most potent regal bloodline out of everyone, so things will only be easier for him than everyone else," Lekima reassured.

"Is that right?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Just wait and see," Lekima said with a confident smile.

As soon as his voice trailed off, all of the primordial beings present slit their own wrists with their fingers, but the blood that came flowing out of the gashes didn't reach the ground.

Instead, they hovered in mid-air, forming a series of crimson marks that rapidly intertwined to create a complex, crimson array that encompassed all of the stone pillars within it.

A series of crimson patterns also appeared on the stone pillars, flashing and resonating with the crimson array.

Even though Xiao Bai was only his own, he had also drawn a crimson array with his own blood, and it was glowing far brighter than all of the other arrays.

Meanwhile, Bai Ze conjured up seven identical projections of himself, and each of them appeared beside the brazier embedded in one of the seven stone pillars.

The Bai Ze projections beside the Zhuyan, Taowu, Giant Mountain Ape, Nine Tailed Immortal Fox, and Ink-Eyed Pixiu stone pillars pointed a finger at their respective braziers, and a golden flame was instantly ignited within all of the braziers in unison.

All of the primordial beings present were powering the crimson arrays above them with all their might, and the arrays were radiating dazzling, crimson light, while the golden flames also grew brighter and brighter.

Right at this moment, the five Bai Zes began chanting in unison, and the golden flames beside them began to flicker in a rhythmic fashion.

Rings of crimson and golden light proliferated outward one after another before fusing into the nearby space.

The Lightning Bird Tribe and the Huntun Tribe didn't require Bai Ze's assistance to ignite their primordial flames, and they had also begun operating their crimson arrays.

Rings of crimson and golden light that were invisible to the naked eye continued to rapidly proliferate outward, spreading over all of the immortal regions and major realms to broadcast a summoning signal.

"It'll take some time to summon the bloodlines, so we're in for a bit of a wait. What are your plans after the blood inheritance ceremony, Fellow Daoist Han?" Lekima asked.

Han Li was still secretly absorbing the potent bloodline power in the air while keeping an eye on Xiao Bai as a conversation ensued between him and Lekima.

Before long, close to a day had flown by.

Right at this moment, the space above the stone pillar beside Xiao Bai began to flash, and specks of white light emerged before slowly revolving around the golden flame at the top of the pillar.

"Is that the True Spirit King bloodline?" Han Li asked with an intrigued expression.

The white light was imbued with extremely potent true spirit bloodline power that was very similar to Xiao Bai's bloodline, but was far more regal.

"That's right. The fact that Xiao Bai was able to summon the True Spirit King bloodline before everyone else indicates that he does indeed possess the purest bloodline out of everyone," Lekima replied with a nod.

More and more specks of white light began to emerge, and they came together to form a projection of a white beast that was quite similar in appearance to Xiao Bai, but there was a far more majestic and authoritative air about it.

What was particularly eye-catching was the vertical eye on the projection's glabella, which was giving off rays of peculiar black light.

The same black light appeared in Xiao Bai's eyes as he observed the projections, and a hint of elation appeared on Bai Ze's face upon seeing this.

After Xiao Bai's successful summoning of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu true spirit bloodline, the other primordial tribes also began to find success one after another.

Specks of gray light began to emerge from the space above the Heavenly Fox Tribe's stone pillar, and even speck of light was giving off formidable bloodline power.

These specks of gray light quickly converged to form a projection of a Nine Tailed Immortal Fox, and the Heavenly Fox beings were ecstatic to see this.

Among the Heavenly Fox beings present, a layer of gray light had also appeared over Liu Le'er's body, and a series of gray patterns had also appeared over the exposed parts of her skin, resonating with the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox projection in the air.

Liu Qing's eyes were glowing with excitement at the sight of the changes that had taken place on Liu Le'er's body.

Shortly thereafter, True Spirit King projections also appeared above the stone pillars of the Qing Ape, Zouwu, and Mountain Moving Ape Tribes, much to the elation of the three tribes, but the stone pillars of the Huntun and Lightning Bird Tribes remained unresponsive.

Chapter 1180: Unexpected Turn of Events

"It looks like the Rahu and the Sky Roaming Kun Peng True Spirit Kings still have no intention of returning to the primordial land," Lekima sighed upon seeing this.

"Why didn't they stay in the primordial land like Senior Bai Ze?" Han Li asked.

"The Rahu and the Sky Roaming Kun Peng are both very free-spirited and spend all their time traveling between realms, so even I've never seen them in the flesh before. Given the tumultuous state of the True Immortal Realm, I can only pray that they'll return soon to help Father return the primordial land to its former glory," Lekima sighed.

Han Li nodded in response and remained silent.

Once all of the True Spirit King projections had been manifested, the Bai Ze projections also faded away, following which Bai Ze declared, "The five True Spirit King bloodlines have been summoned. They're not complete, but they should be enough. It's time to select the heirs to inherit these five True Spirit King bloodlines."

All of the primordial beings present immediately rose to their feet before extending grateful bows toward Bai Ze.

It was all thanks to Bai Ze's assistance that they were able to successfully summon the five True Spirit King bloodlines. Otherwise, their blood arrays alone wouldn't have been anywhere near sufficient to get the job done.

Bai Ze gave them a dismissive wave, then made his way toward the Huntun and Lightning Bird Tribe.

The five tribes had already selected their heirs.

Qing Dian, the white-haired young man, and Yuan Shanbai emerged from the Qing Ape Tribe, the Zouwu Tribe, and the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe, respectively, then sat down with their legs crossed in mid-air to begin absorbing the true spirit bloodlines.

Xiao Bai was the only candidate to inherit the Ink-Eyed Pixiu bloodline, so a choice didn't even have to be made there.

From the Heavenly Fox Tribe emerged Liu Le'er, while many other young Heavenly Fox beings looked on with envious expressions, yet right as she was about to begin absorbing the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox bloodline, a dissenting voice suddenly rang out from outside.

"Hold on a second!"

Immediately thereafter, a streak of gray light flew into the crimson space, then faded away to reveal a gray-robed, middle-aged man.

The man had a gentle and refined appearance, but there was a dark and cold look in his eyes, as if his heart were enshrouded in shadow.

"Who goes there?" many of the primordial beings present exclaimed.

This was an extremely important occasion to all of the primordial tribes, and a watertight encirclement had already been formed around the entirety of Eight Plains Mountain, whlie a multitude of powerful restrictions had been set up outside the Asura Blood Gate to prevent the ceremony from being interrupted, so everyone was naturally quite alarmed by this unannounced arrival.

A surprised look appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of the gray-robed man, who he was able to identify as none other than Liu Zizai.

However, he then immediately shook his head as he thought to himself, No, he's not Liu Zizai. He's identical to Liu Zizai in appearance, but their auras are somewhat different.

The cold and menacing aura being given off by the gray-robed man was very different from Liu Zizai's aura, and for some reason, the man struck Han Li with a sense of familiarity, as if they had met somewhere in the past.

Judging from Lekima's expression, it seemed that he also recognized the gray-robed man, while many of the Heavenly Fox beings were staring at the man as if they had just seen a ghost.

"Please pardon my intrusion, everyone. I am also a member of the Heavenly Fox Tribe, and I've come here to compete for the right to inherit the True Spirit King bloodline of the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox." the gray-robed man said as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute toward everyone.

At the same time, an extremely pure Heavenly Fox bloodline aura erupted out of his body, and the aura was so immense that it was causing the space around him to ripple violently like the surface of a disturbed lake.

All of the Heavenly Fox beings were forced to stumble back in retreat by this tremendous aura, and only Liu Qing and two other men standing beside him were able to stand their ground.

Liu Le'er was also sent flying by this aura, and her complexion had paled slightly from the impact.

However, Han Li immediately appeared beside her to catch her, then swept a sleeve through the air to form a golden light around before them, warding off the immense aura that continued to surge out of the gray-robed man's body.

Liu Le'er was able to catch her breath before expressing her gratitude to Han Li, but instead of looking at her, Han Li was staring intently at the gray-robed man.

The man's cultivation base was at the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage, a sliver more advanced than even the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's cultivation base.

"This man is too powerful for us to contend with, so let's take a step back for now," Han Li communicated to Liu Le'er through voice transmission.

Liu Le'er raised no objections to this, and the two of them flew back in retreat.

At the same time, Han Li cast his gaze toward Bai Ze, and he discovered that Bai Ze was also looking at the gray-robed man, but he didn't seem irked at all by the man's unannounced intrusion.

Instead, he was merely observing as the situation unfolded, seemingly content with being a passive bystander.

The expressions of all of the other primordial beings in the primordial space changed drastically upon sensing the gray-robed man's cultivation base, and no one dared to raise any further objections at his intrusion.

All of the Heavenly Fox beings hurriedly steadied themselves, while Liu Qing took a glance at Bai Ze out of his peripheral vision.

His brows furrowed slightly at the sight of Bai Ze's inaction, but he then immediately composed himself before instructing several of his tribesmen to go and protect Liu Le'er.

He had seen Liu Le'er retreating under Han Li's protection, and he made no effort to stop them as he knew that Han Li had her best interests in mind.

Three Heavenly Fox beings appeared around Han Li and Liu Le'er in a flash, namely Fox 3, Elder Mu, and a dark-skinned elderly man who was at the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage.

"Thank you for protecting Young Mistress Le'er, Fellow Daoist Han," Fox 3 said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

His gratitude was echoed by the dark-skinned elderly man, while Elder Mu also cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li, albeit in a very reluctant manner.

"There's no need to thank me, Le'er is just as important to me as she is to all of you," Han Li replied with a nod.

"It hasn't been long since we last met, but you've made some significant strides once again, Fellow Daoist Han. It's very impressive that you're completely mentally unaffected in the face of all of these powerful cultivators," Fox 3 remarked.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

At the moment, all of the Great Encompassment cultivators in the crimson space had released their own auras to contend with that of the gray-robed man, so the entire space was filled with terrifying Great Encompassment Stage pressure. Liu Le'er, Fox 3, and the other High Zenith cultivators were able to keep up a calm facade, but their souls were trembling in their bodies in an instinctive, submissive reaction to the power of all of the Great Encompassment cultivators.

Not only was it a huge stride in cultivation base to progress from the High Zenith Stage to the Great Encompassment Stage, one's soul would also undergo a massive evolution and begin to fuse as one with one's body.

Every single gesture made by a Great Encompassment cultivator carried with it this crushing soul power, so it was almost inevitable for High Zenith cultivators to feel intimidated by their Great Encompassment Stage counterparts, often losing the battle before it had even begun.

Han Li could also feel this sense of spiritual subjugation from Great Encompassment cultivators, but given his mastery of the Spirit Refinement Technique, his soul was far more powerful than that of the average High Zenith cultivator, so the pressure on him was far lessened.

However, in this moment, he couldn't feel this pressure at all, and that was why he was able to react before all of the Heavenly Fox beings to jump to Liu Le'er's aid before everyone else.

It didn't take long for Han Li to realize the reasons behind this change.

Even though he hadn't progressed in his cultivation base of late, he had gained control over the Eon Divine Lamp and attained a large number of time law threads. On top of that, he had also figured out the inner workings of the Almighty Sword Array and successfully set up a space of accelerated time in his Flower Branch domain.

All of these achievements had instilled within him immense confidence, and even though his soul hadn't become any more powerful, this confidence had bolstered his mentality to the extent that the powerful souls of Great Encompassment cultivators no longer had any subjugative effect on him.

This was naturally a very pleasing discovery for Han Li, but he didn't allow his expression to betray his emotions.

Instead, his expression remained unchanged as he said, "You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Liu."

Fox 3 didn't dwell on the subject, and he cast his gaze toward Liu Qing with a hint of concern in his eyes.

At this point, all of the Heavenly Fox beings had already recovered from their astonishment, and they were locked in a confrontation against the gray-robed man.

"How dare you come to the Asura Blood Gate after what you did, Liu Tianhao!" Liu Qing spat with a cold expression.

Liu Tianhao was completely unfazed by the hostility in Liu Qing's voice, and he smiled as he asked, "What did I do? I'll have to ask you to elaborate, Fellow Daoist Liu Qing."

"It seems like you don't have the best memory. No matter, you'll have plenty of time to contemplate your own sins in the afterlife!" Liu Qing said with a cold smile as he swept a sleeve through the air, and all of a sudden, Liu Tianhao found himself in a boundless expanse of inky darkness with a massive river of stars rapidly revolving around him.

It was as if he had suddenly been teleported deep into a boundless starry sky.

All of a sudden, the giant river stars swelled drastically to fill up the entire starry sky, and a burst of terrifying power surged out of it, sweeping up Liu Tianhao and threatening to tear his body to shreds.

At the same time, a storm of asteroids came hurtling out of the river of stars, battering against Liu Tianhao to send him flying back through the air, while blood splattered in all directions from his body.

Liu Tianhao paid no heed to his own injuries as he remarked, "This is not a bad illusory spirit domain, but unfortunately for you, it won't be enough to trap me."

Immediately thereafter, a gray mark appeared over his glabella, then split open to reveal a gray vertical eye, out of which came pouring an endless torrent of gray flames.

The gray flames were giving off extremely pure illusory law powers, and every part of the starry sky that came into contact with them instantly collapsed.

In the blink of an eye, the starry sky was completely destroyed, and Liu Tianhao found himself back in the crimson space, with all of his injuries also instantly erased.

Chapter 1181: Confidence

Even though Liu Qing's spirit domain had been destroyed, he remained completely unfazed. Instead, a faint smile appeared on his face as he remarked, "Flames of Illusory Reality, eh? I suppose I shouldn't be surprised that you've managed to cultivate this spirit flame capable of eradicating all illusion."

Liu Tianhao was rather taken aback by Liu Qing's calm reaction, and before he had a chance to do anything, a long saber that was emanating an eerie, crimson glow suddenly came protruding out of his lower abdomen, having pierced through his dantian from behind.

At the same time, a pair of glowing, white hands appeared in front of him before imprinting themselves against his chest.

As it turned out, two figures had appeared in front of and behind him in a wraith-like manner, executing a perfectly coordinated sneak attack.

His two assailants were none other than the two men that had been standing beside Liu Qing, and blood came spewing out of Liu Tianhao's mouth as his aura began to rapidly wane.

The taller of the two men, the one wielding the crimson saber, yelled, "Liu Tianhao, this is what you get for colluding with those Gray Realm scoundrels to plot against our master!"

At the same time, his physical appearance rapidly changed, and in the blink of an eye, he had transformed into none other than Liu Zizai.

The crimson saber in his hand was giving off incredibly formidable baleful qi, and it was none other than the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber.

Meanwhile, the shorter of the two men drifted back in retreat, but his palm imprints remained on Liu Tianhao's chest, as if they had become a permanent fixture on his body.

Bursts of warped, white light surged into Liu Tianhao's body incessantly from the pair of palm imprints, tearing his internal organs apart incessantly.

Liu Tianhao's entire body was trembling violently, while blood continued to gush out of his nose and mouth.

"I'm not proud of resorting to a sneak attack, but you've shown yourself to be an extremely underhanded and despicable character, and your powers currently far surpass ours, so we've had no choice but to stoop to these lows," the short man said with a serious expression.

His physical appearance also rapidly transformed as he spoke, and in the blink of an eye, he had transformed into a white-robed man who was also identical to Liu Zizai and Liu Tianhao in appearance, but his aura and disposition were far more righteous and benevolent than that of the latter.

Despite his grievous injuries, Liu Tianhao remained as calm as ever, remarking with a faint smile, "Looks like we've all returned to the Heavenly Fox Tribe, Liu Zizai, Liu Haoran. I suppose you two are the only ones capable of getting so close to me without my detection."

Liu Qing, Liu Zizai, and Liu Haoran's expressions changed slightly upon seeing this.

They were certain that the person standing before them was indeed Liu Tianhao in the flesh. His aura and law power fluctuations were completely indistinguishable from those of the original, so this was definitely not an illusion or a clone.

The three of them had all achieved unrivaled mastery over the laws of illusions, so they could also be certain that they hadn't fallen under any illusions themselves.

Liu Zizai let loose a loud roar as he gave the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber a forceful twist, and Liu Tianhao's body instantly exploded into countless pieces of mangled flesh.

However, not only was he not relieved to see this, he was only looking more apprehensive than before.

In the next instant, his expression changed drastically as a burst of crimson light erupted out of the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, forming a crimson saber barrier around him.

However, the saber barrier had only just taken shape when it was destroyed in brutal fashion, and Liu Zizai was sent flying back through the air as if he had been struck by some forceful object.

Liu Haoran's expression also changed slightly as a layer of white light surfaced over his eyes, and his hands also began to glow with radiant, white light as he thrust his palms forward.

Another resounding boom rang out as Liu Haoran was also sent flying back through the air like a drifting leaf in a gust of fierce wind.

An alarmed look appeared on Liu Qing's face upon seeing this, and he hurriedly conjured up his gray spirit domain, which encompassed an area with a radius of several hundred feet around him.

All of the Heavenly Fox beings behind him immediately released their spirit domains as well, protecting themselves and the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox true spirit bloodline projection.

Meanwhile, Fox 3, Elder Mu, and the dark-skinned elderly man had also summoned their spirit domains and an array of immortal treasures to protect Liu Le'er.

Han Li wasn't as tense as the Heavenly Fox beings, and he activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes as he scoured his surroundings while also releasing his spiritual sense, trying to find exactly what it was that had sent Liu Zizai and Liu Haoran flying, but he was unable to find anything.

A slight disturbance had also arisen in the other tribes upon seeing this, while a look of slight bewilderment had appeared on Bai Ze's face.

Lekima had originally been standing with Han Li, but after Han Li stepped in to help Liu Le'er, Lekma had made his way over to Bai Ze's side.

Upon catching sight of the change in Bai Ze's expression, he asked in a quiet voice, "What do you see, Father?"

Bai Ze shook his head and offered no response.

......

Liu Qing was in a state of high alert, but the anticipated attack never came.

Instead, an illusory figure slowly appeared before him as the space up ahead rippled and warped, and the scraps of Liu Tianhao's body turned semi-transparent before slowly vanishing into thin air.

In the instant that the final remnant of his body faded away, the illusory figure took on a substantial form, and it was none other than Liu Tianhao, standing completely unscathed.

"He's mastered the Illusory Dreamscape!" Liu Qing exclaimed with a stunned expression, and all of the other Heavenly Fox beings were also astonished to hear this.

"Do you know what this Illusory Dreamscape is, Le'er?" Han Li asked.

"The Illusory Dreamscape is a legendary ability of our Heavenly Fox Tribe that was invented by the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox himself. Aside from the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox, the only one to have successfully mastered this ability in the history of our tribe is Patriarch Liu Qi. It's said that this ability can transform all injuries sustained by the user into illusions, thereby granting them invincibility," Liu Le'er explained, and a stunned look also appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Even though Liu Zizai and Liu Haoran had been sent flying, neither of them had sustained any major injuries, and after steadying themselves, they immediately prepared to retaliate, only to stop cold in their tracks upon hearing what Liu Qing had just said.

"How were you able to cultivate Master's ability?" Liu Zizai exclaimed with a stunned expression.

"His body is mine, so why is it so inconceivable to you that I was able to master his abilities? You two complacent fools will never be able to imagine just how beneficial his body is to my cultivation!" Liu Tianhao sneered with a triumphant expression.

Both Liu Zizai and Liu Haoran were furious to hear this, and the two of them both began glowing radiantly at the same time, while a layer of dark green fur appeared over their bodies.

In the blink of an eye, the two of them had taken on half-human, half-beast forms, and their robes were flapping audibly from the tremendous auras surging out of their bodies as they prepared to clash again.

Right at this moment, Bai Ze stepped into the fray and yelled in an authoritative voice, "That's enough! We are in the Asura Blood Gate right now, and it cannot withstand too much impact. If you want to resolve your differences, then wait until after you leave this place!"

The four Heavenly Fox beings hurriedly stood down upon hearing this, but Liu Qing's trio was still glowering at Liu Tianhao with intense animosity in their eyes.

At this point, Han Li had developed a decent understanding of the situation, and he asked through voice transmission, "Fellow Daoist Liu, could it be that Liu Tianhao is a corpse soul of Patriarch Liu Qi's?"

"That's right, Liu Tianhao is Patriarch Liu Qi's wicked corpse soul, and you've actually met him before," Fox 3 replied.

"I have?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

He had indeed been struck by a sense of familiarity upon first catching sight of Liu Tianhao.

"Back at the Baleful Cleansing Pond," Fox 3 reminded.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a look of realization appeared in his eyes.

"You're saying that giant fox that we encountered at the time was actually Liu Tianhao instead of Patriarch Liu Qi?"

"That's right. I was swindled by him and even helped him escape his entrapment. What a fool I was!" Fox 3 replied with a look of intense self-resentment.

"What exactly has Liu Tianhao done to warrant such resentment from your Heavenly Fox Tribe? Also, has Patriarch Liu Qi already perished?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"According to my knowledge, Patriarch Liu Qi has indeed already perished, and his downfall was brought about by Liu Tianhao in collusion with beings from the Gray Realm," Fox 3 replied as he glowered at Liu Tianhao with a hateful expression.

An enlightened look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

However, what he couldn't understand was why Liu Zizai and Liu Haoran, who were most likely Patriarch Liu Qi's self corpse soul and kind corpse soul, respectively, were also so resentful of Liu Tianhao. Could it be because Liu Tianhao had killed Liu Qi?

He had thought that corpse souls were supposed to have been in opposition to the host, but it seemed like Liu Zizai and Liu Haoran were quite loyal to Liu Qi.

Right at this moment, the Heaven Controlling Vial Spirit's voice suddenly rang out in Han Li's heart.

"The relationship between a host and their three corpse souls is not as simple as you think. All corpse souls have the innate urge to kill their host and seize their body, but they're also living beings that can be tamed. Given his mastery over the laws of illusions, Liu Qi excelled in manipulating the hearts and minds of others, so taming a pair of corpse souls would not have been a difficult task for him."

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up slightly upon hearing this.

"Senior Vial Spirit! You're finally awake!"

"How did you get swept up in something so dangerous again? If that Dao Ancestor attacks you at such close proximity, even transmigration may not be able to save you in time," the vial spirit harrumphed.

"I didn't anticipate that I would end up in a situation like this, but given that we're already here, I can only ask you to prepare a transmigration at any moment," Han LI sighed.

"As long as you have enough time law threads, I can transmigrate you however many times you please. Oh? It seems like not only have you recovered all of the time law threads that you expended, you've gained many new ones. No wonder you have so much confidence," the vial spirit remarked in a surprised voice.

Chapter 1182: Inheritance

"It's a bit of a long story, but I was blessed with some strokes of fortune. Senior Vial Spirit, is it true that one's three corpse souls can be tamed," Han Li asked.

"Why would I lie to you about something like this? It's possible, but it's not very easy to accomplish," the vial spirit replied in a succinct manner, seemingly not wanting to dwell on this subject.

Han Li had always wanted to find out more about corpse souls, and he certainly wasn't going to pass up this opportunity.

"Senior Vial Spirit, why is it that there's a disparity in power between Patriarch Liu Qi's three corpse souls? Liu Tianhao is at the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage, whereas Liu Zizai and Liu Haoran are only at the mid-Great Encompassment Stage. Could it be that just like cultivators, corpse souls can advance their own powers through cultivation?"

"Didn't I just tell you that corpse souls are no different from living beings? Of course they can cultivate! As for why there's a disparity between the cultivation bases of Liu Qi's corpse souls, that's obviously because his wicked corpse soul was able to attain his physical body, thereby allowing it to progress in its cultivation much faster than the other two," the vial spirit explained in an impatient manner, as if all of this should've already been abundantly obvious.

"Is the body of the host really that important for corpse souls?" Han Li asked.

"Of course. The body of the host concerns the limits of the Great Dao. Without attaining the body of the host, a corpse soul will never be able to become a Dao Ancestor. On top of that, the body of the host contains all of the host's insights in terms of law cultivation, so once a corpse soul obtains the body, their law powers will fuse with it, instantly giving them a drastic enhancement in power.

“Why else do you think all corpse souls are so intent on taking over the body of their host?" the vial spirit explained.

"I see. What kind of relationship exists between a cultivator and their three corpse souls? If the corpse souls are constantly plotting to take over their body, why don't they just kill their corpse souls to permanently eliminate this threat?" Han Li asked.

"The corpse souls are manifestations of a cultivator's attachments, so they're impossible to completely eradicate. Even if the corpse souls are killed, those attachments will return to the cultivator, significantly impacting their mental state and cultivation, so they'll need to be severed again. With each severance, those attachments will only grow in power, making each successive severance more and more difficult.

“Hence, the three corpse souls can't be killed, nor is it a good idea to release them and let them do as they please, so the best way to treat them would be to seal them away," the vial spirit explained, and it seemed to be quite happy to share knowledge on this subject with Han Li.

"What would happen to a cultivator's corpse souls if the cultivator is already dead?" Han Li asked.

"If the host dies, then the corpse souls will have no origin, thereby making it possible for them to be killed, so sometimes, corpse souls will protect their host for their own survival," the vial spirit replied.

Meanwhile, Bai Ze had already arrived near the four Heavenly Fox beings, and Liu Tianhao extended a respectful salute toward him as he said, "Your Majesty, I am a member of the Heavenly Fox Tribe as well, so I should also have the right to inherit the bloodline of the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox, is that not correct?"

"You do indeed have this right, but how do you explain what happened to Liu Qi?" Bai Ze asked.

"I'm sure you're aware that all corpse souls have the innate urge to take over the body of the host, so I can only ask that you pardon me for acting on those urges, Your Majesty," Liu Tianhao replied.

"Nonsense! Patriarch Liu Qi was already a Dao Ancestor, so you would've been no match for him! Your Majesty, Liu Tianhao must've colluded with outsiders to bring about Patriarch Liu Qi's downfall, whether that be the Heavenly Court or the Gray Realm, so he must not be spared for his crimes!" Liu Qing objected vehemently.

"I did indeed collude with the Gray Realm at the time, but since then, I've already renounced them and decided to return to the primordial land. I have primordial blood flowing through my veins, and that's something that I've never forgotten. Now that I've attained Liu Qi's body, I'm only a step away from becoming a Dao Ancestor, so if I were to inherit the bloodline of the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox, my chances of becoming a Dao Ancestor would be far higher than Liu Le'er's," Liu Tianhao proclaimed.

A contemplative look appeared on Bai Ze's face upon hearing this, seemingly swayed by Liu Tianhao's words, and Liu Qing hurriedly interjected in an urgent manner, "Your Majesty, Liu Tianhao is not to be trusted! Patriarch Liu Qi only fell to his demise because he chose to trust Liu Tianhao in a fatal lapse in judgment! We cannot allow him to inherit the bloodline of the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox!"

"Both of you have made valid points. On top of that, this is an internal matter for your Heavenly Fox Tribe, so even as the True Spirit King, it wouldn't be right for me to interfere, so how about this? The bloodline power of the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox possesses a high degree of sentience, so why not let it choose who it chooses to be inherited by?" Bai Ze proposed.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, while a hint of surprise flashed through Liu Qing's eyes at this proposal, following which he agreed after a brief moment of contemplation.

Liu Tianhao also nodded in agreement after some hesitation, then turned to Liu Zizai and Liu Haoran as he said, "You two can come as well. Quit pretending that you're so righteous and noble, I'm sure you also returned to the Heavenly Fox Tribe for the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox bloodline."

Liu Zizai made no effort to deny the notion, and Liu Qing gave an internal sneer upon seeing this, but didn't display any outward derision.

In contrast, Liu Haoran shook his head with a serious expression as he said, "I returned to the Heavenly Fox Tribe because I promised Master to protect the Heavenly Fox Tribe in his stead. I have no intention of fighting over the regal bloodline, so don't get me involved."

"You're still as righteous as ever, Fellow Daoist Haoran. How admirable," Liu Tianhao praised in a mocking fashion, while a sheepish look flashed through Liu Zizai's eyes, only to quickly be replaced by a look of determination.

Liu Qing took a grateful glance at Liu Haoran, then beckoned to Liu Le'er and the others.

Liu Le'er had been observing the unfolding scene this entire time, and she turned to Han Li with a nervous expression, clearly intimidated by the prospect of having to compete over the regal bloodline with someone as powerful as Liu Tianhao.

Han Li smiled as he gave her a reassuring pat on the head and said, "Don't worry, Chief Liu Qing looks very assured, so I'm sure he's very confident that this method of selection will yield a favorable outcome. Just do your best, and don't put too much pressure on yourself."

Liu Le'er was very reassured to hear this, and she flew over to Liu Qing with Elder Mu and the others.

Liu Qing latched onto Liu Le'er's hand, giving it a gentle pat as he said, "Just do your best, Le'er. You are the true heir of our Heavenly Fox Tribe, and I'm sure the bloodline of our esteemed ancestor will choose you."

At the same time, a drop of gray blood essence flew out of his storage ring before seeping into the palm of her head in secret.

Liu Le'er was rather taken aback by this, but she was able to catch herself before any surprise could appear on her face.

"Rest assured, Chief Liu, I won't disappoint you," she said as she extended a graceful curtsey.

All of a sudden, Liu Tianhao turned to take a glance at Liu Qing and Liu Le'er with a perplexed look in his eyes.

"Go on," Liu Qing said with a smile and a nod of encouragement, and Liu Le'er drifted up into the air before landing in front of the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox projection.

Before long, she was joined by Liu Tianhao and Liu Zizai.

"Let's begin," Bai Ze declared, and gray light began to glow from all three of their bodies.

Due to the disparities in cultivation base, the brightness of light radiating from their bodies varied drastically.

Liu Tianhao was glowing so bright that he was almost impossible to look at, while Liu Zizai was glowing a little dimmer, but both of them were far outshining Liu Le'er.

Their bloodline powers were also on full display, with a Heavenly Fox projection appearing behind each of them.

Both of Liu Tianhao and Liu Zizai's Heavenly Fox projections had nine tails, while Liu Le'er's only had six.

The three Heavenly Fox projections each extended a paw toward the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox bloodline to release bursts of receiving force.

Even though the gray light emanating from Liu Le'er's body was being outshone by the other two, the six-tailed fox projection behind her was extremely clear, even more so than the nine tailed fox projections behind Liu Tianhao and Liu Zizai.

Liu Zizai's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he channeled his Heavenly Fox bloodline with all his might, causing the gray light radiating from his body to glow even brighter, but his nine tailed fox projection displayed no changes.

Liu Tianhao's expression also darkened slightly as he took a glance in Liu Le'er's direction.

Right at this moment, the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox projection rippled slightly, then turned to the three candidate heirs as if it were a living being.

It swept its gaze briefly over Liu Zizai, then immediately turned its attention solely to Liu Le'er and Liu Tianhao, much to Liu Zizai's despair.

The Nine Tailed Immortal Fox projection's gaze roamed back and forth between Liu Le'er and Liu Tianhao, seemingly unable to make a choice between them.

Right at this moment, Liu Tianhao made a strange hand seal while letting loose a melodious cry, and the Heavenly Fox projection instantly became a little clearer and brighter.

The Nine Tailed Immortal Fox projection instantly turned its gaze to him, seemingly having made its choice, but before it was able to do anything, a radiant, water-droplet-shaped gray mark suddenly appeared on Liu Le'er's glabella.

The gray patterns all over her body instantly lit up, and they also began moving as if they had sprung to life.

Immediately thereafter, the Heavenly Fox projection behind her became almost twice as bright as before, comprehensively outshining Liu Tianhao's nine tailed fox projection.

A hint of elation flashed through the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox projection's eyes, and it immediately abandoned Liu Tianhao for Liu Le'er, opening its mouth to release a pillar of gray light that began fusing into Liu Le'er's body, while the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox projection began to rapidly fade.

Chapter 1183: Opening the Three Gates

Liu Le'er shuddered as the pillar of gray light fell upon her, and a pained look appeared on her face.

The gray patterns on her body flashed violently while rapidly spreading and widening, and the Heavenly Fox projection behind her was also quickly becoming brighter and brighter.

At the same time, it began to grow more tails, with the number quickly increasing from six to nine.

Once the Heavenly Fox projection had attained all nine tails, the pain on Liu Le'er's face abated slightly, and she took a deep breath before sitting down with her legs crossed, focusing wholeheartedly on receiving the bloodline power of the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox.

Han Li was very relieved and elated to see this, while Liu Qing and the other Heavenly Fox beings erupted into thunderous cheers.

Judging from the reactions of the other tribes, they were clearly also quite pleased by this outcome.

Deep down, they also harbored a great deal of distrust toward Liu Tianhao, so Liu Le'er was the preferable heir to the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox bloodline in their eyes.

As for Bai Ze, there was no change in his expression, but the subtle gleam deep in his eyes indicated that this was also a desirable outcome for him.

Liu Tianhao was standing beside Liu Le'er with a look of fury and indignation on his face, but he didn't dare to do anything with Bai Ze so close by.

With Liu Le'er commencing the process to inherit the NIne Tailed Immortal Fox bloodline, Qing Dian, Yuan Shanbai, Xiao Bai, and the young master of the Zouwu Tribe also began receiving the bloodlines of their respective True Spirit Kings.

Right at this moment, the Lightning Bird Tribe's stone pillar abruptly shuddered violently, immediately following which the primordial flame on it swelled to several times its original size.

The entire crimson space suddenly began to tremble violently, while an earth-shattering commotion rang out from outside.

The souls of everyone in the crimson space also began to tremble violently, and they stumbled back unsteadily in retreat, while the five True Spirit King projections released bursts of protective light to shelter their bloodline heirs, allowing them to remain unaffected.

Han Li's soul was also trembling in his body, and he hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to stabilize it while casting his gaze out of the crimson space.

At this moment, countless black clouds had appeared out of nowhere above Eight Plains Mountain, and thick bolts of lightning were flashing through the clouds, while countless black tornados emerged from the ground, resembling giant pillars that connected heaven and earth.

It was a phenomenon that was countless times more violent than what Han Li had triggered by activating the Almighty Sword Array, and the entire mountain was trembling in fear, as if it could be devoured by the dark clouds in the sky at any moment.

All of the primordial beings on Eight Plains Mountain erupted into a blind panic, hurriedly activating all of the restrictions on the mountains to protect themselves, but it seemed that their efforts were going to be completely futile.

Deep within the dark clouds, a gargantuan black shadow could be seen, slowly roaming over the heavens. The shadow was unfathomably enormous, and it seemed to be some type of monolithic beast.

The occasional glimpse of a body could be seen through the clouds, but those weren't enough to allow the primordial beings to gauge just how massive the creature was.

Inside the crimson space, Bai Ze cast his gaze outside with an elated expression.

Liu Tianhao immediately pounced on this perceived opportunity, instantly appearing beside the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox projection before reaching out to make a grab for it.

A burst of tremendous power erupted out of Liu Tianhao's head, enshrouding the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox projection in an attempt to seize it by force.

"How dare you!" Bai Ze yelled in righteous fury as he swung around to face Liu Tianhao, and everything in the entire crimson space instantly fell still.

Liu Tianhao's attempt to seize the bloodline projection was instantly thwarted, and an alarmed look appeared on his face as he tried to flee, only to discover that his body had been completely immobilized by Bai Ze's unfathomable power.

"You must have a death wish, you insolent scoundrel," Bai Ze said in a cold voice as he pointed a finger at Liu Tianhao, unleashing a thick finger projection that struck him on the chest.

A huge hole was instantly blown through Liu Tianhao's chest, almost splitting his body into two.

Blood instantly came spewing out of his mouth, but his body quickly took on an illusory, semi-transparent form.

"You think your Illusory Dreamscape will work on me?" Bai Ze harrumphed coldly as he swept a sleeve through the air, unleashing a burst of invisible power that instantly swept through the entire crimson space.

A ball of gray light erupted several thousand feet away, and Liu Tianhao re-emerged before being sent flying back through the air, throwing up another mouthful of blood in the process.

However, he had no time to attend to his own injuries, and he made a rapid string of hand seals, upon which a burst of blindingly radiant gray light erupted out of his body before manifesting countless illusions that included celestial bodies, mountains, rivers, trees, cities, palaces, lightning, fire, crowds of people, packs of fierce creatures...

It was as if an entire world had been manifested to fill the entire crimson space, creating an immersive environment that had everyone looking dazed and confused.

At the same time, the light in everyone's eyes was quickly fading away, as if the power of their souls were being devoured by this illusory world.

A cold look appeared in Bai Ze's eyes as he swept a sleeve through the air, and all of the illusions were instantly eradicated, but at this point, Liu Tianhao was already nowhere to be seen.

Everyone in the crimson space instantly snapped back to their senses, and they began gasping for air as if they had just endured immense physical exertion.

A look of lingering fear surfaced in Han Li's eyes.

Just now, he had felt as if his soul had been on the verge of being sucked out of his body.

Bai Ze paid no heed to Han Li and the others as he reached out with his right hand to make a grabbing motion in a certain direction, and the space there was instantly torn apart, forcing Liu Tianhao to stumble out into the open.

Right at this moment, a burst of tremendous power erupted out of the shattered space to sweep up Liu Tianhao, and he abruptly vanished into thin air.

So he even had an escape plan prepared... Bai Ze thought to himself with tightly furrowed brows.

Liu Zizai and the others were all exchanging bewildered glances with one another, struggling to comprehend what had just happened.

Liu Qing opened his mouth to say something, but before he had a chance to say anything, Bai Ze turned his gaze to Liu Le'er as he said, "I'll look into this matter, but right now, your priority is to inherit the bloodline, so don't get distracted."

Liu Le'er nodded in response and returned her attention to the task at hand.

Bai Ze then swept a sleeve through the air toward the top of the eight stone pillars, and the eight golden flames up there drifted down before combining as one.

After that, he released a few incantation seals, then thrust both palms toward the space behind the stone pillars.

The combined ball of golden flames flew onto the plaza behind the stone pillars at Bai Ze's behest, then exploded into countless golden flames that instantly ignited the entire space there.

Immediately thereafter, the eight stone pillars began to radiate dazzling, crimson light, and one true spirit projection after another flew out of the stone pillars before rising up into the crimson clouds above.

The crimson clouds in the sky began to churn violently, and a vast expanse of crimson light descended from the clouds above to connect with the golden flames down below.

A burst of powerful primordial fluctuations swept through the air, and three giant gates appeared within the golden flames and crimson light, all of which were thousands of feet tall.

The three gates were standing next to one another with several hundred feet of space between them, and their lower halves had been illuminated a golden color by the golden flames down below, while their top halves were enshrouded in crimson light.

Everyone was stunned by the sight of the giant gates, and even as a human, Han Li couldn't help but feel a sense of awe and veneration in the face of the gates.

This feeling was even more potent in the hearts of the primordial beings present, many of whom were even struck by the urge to kneel down and kowtow in reverence.

Han Li's gaze settled onto the gate on the left, then slowly moved to the right, roaming over the gates one after another.

The first gate was giving off an extremely antiquated aura, and there were eight reliefs etched upon it, depicting the true forms of the eight True Spirit Kings, all of which looked as if they had been hand-carved onto the gate.

The eight True Spirit King reliefs were all giving off extremely formidable true spirit auras, so much so that even Han Li was struck by a sense of asphyxiating pressure at the mere sight of them, forcing him to avert his gaze.

The second gate also had engravings etched upon it, but the designs were far more sloppy and illegible, consisting of only some rough lines that laid out a seemingly haphazard piece of scenery in the primordial world.

As Han Li's gaze fell upon the gate, he was struck by a rather peculiar sensation.

It felt to him as if the scenery on the gate had suddenly begun to move, transforming into a vast expanse of crimson light that encompassed his entire body. It was as if the scene engraved onto the gate had sprung to life and dragged him into the depicted world.

Inside this strange world, Han Li instantly felt as if he had been plunged into a fiery pit, and it was an extremely grueling sensation, but his true spirit bloodlines were pumping joyfully through his body, as if they had found a wonderful paradise.

A wave of intense heat instantly washed over his entire body, and his face and neck instantly turned bright red.

Everyone else's attention had been drawn to the giant gates, so only Bai Ze had the wherewithal to detect Han Li's condition, and a hint of bewilderment flashed through his eyes as his gaze fell upon Han Li.

However, he chose not to intervene, merely observing passively from the side, as if he wanted to see how long it would take for Han Li to free himself from this abnormal state.

Chapter 1184: I Want to Try

As soon as Han Li detected the abnormal changes taking place in his body, an alarmed look instantly appeared on his face as he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, and a burst of sharp pain pierced through his consciousness, snapping him back to his senses.

He wiped the cold sweat from his forehead, then looked around to discover that no one seemed to have noticed what had just happened to him. At the same time, it occurred to him that he seemed to have been the only one to have fallen into that strange state just now.

All of the other primordial beings merely took cursory glances before moving on, so it was clear that none of them had been struck by the same sensation as Han Li.

Han Li took a moment to compose himself, and right as he was about to turn his gaze to the third gate, a look of shock and elation suddenly appeared on his face.

What happened? I just opened an acupoint!

Just now, a profound acupoint had just been opened up in his body without any warning.

To think that he was able to open a profound acupoint after just a brief glance at the second gate... It seems like he really is no ordinary human, Bai Ze thought to himself as he continued to observe the changes taking place in Han Li's body.

Could it be...

Han Li turned his gaze back to the second gate with a hopeful expression, but this time, he wasn't able to enter that same profound state.

However, his true spirit bloodlines were still dancing joyfully in his body, and they were full of yearning toward the giant gate.

Han Li's gaze lingered on the second gate for a moment longer before moving onto the final gate.

Compared with the previous two gates, the third one appeared very rough and neglected. There were no engravings on its surface, only countless pits and craters, as if it had previously been bombarded by a meteor shower.

After observing the gate for a moment, Han Li didn't find anything special about it, and he quickly looked away.

"The space beyond these three gates that you see right now is the true Holy Primordial Palace. The stone palace on Eight Plains Mountain is nothing more than a place that we constructed to store the Holy Primordial Flame," Bai Ze revealed.

"There are three Holy Primordial Palaces?" Liu Qing asked in a surprised manner.

Even though he was the chief of the Heavenly Fox Tribe, it seemed that he didn't know much about the Holy Primordial Palace.

"There's only a single Holy Primordial Palace, but the three gates each leads to a different level of the palace. The first gate is the foundation of the inheritance of the eight regal bloodlines, so the chosen bloodline heirs can enter this gate to inherit the True Spirit King bloodlines," Bai Ze explained.

As soon as this was revealed to everyone, Qing Dian was unable to wait any longer, rushing headfirst into the golden flames.

As soon as he flew into the flames, he immediately let loose an agonized roar.

Everyone was alarmed to hear this, and they turned to discover that a series of fiery red cracks had appeared all over Qing Dian's entire body, giving him the appearance of a piece of chinaware that was on the verge of cracking from excessive heat.

"The Holy Primordial Flame can incinerate the impurities in your bodies. After you've endured it, you'll be able to inherit the regal bloodlines," Bai Ze declared.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a thunderous roar rang out as Qing Dian's body swelled rapidly in size, transforming into a massive Qing Ape.

He then crashed into the first gate, vanishing into it amid a flash of golden light.

The young master of the Zouwu Tribe quickly followed suit, also leaping into the golden flames, followed by Liu Le'er, Yuan Shanbai, and Xiao Bai.

A chorus of loud roars rang out within the golden flames as all of them took on their true forms before crashing through the first gate, just as Qing Dian had done earlier.

In the wake of their departure, the entire plaza fell silent.

"All of you can cultivate on the plaza. The bloodline power in this place won't be as potent as what's in the Holy Primordial Palace, but it'll still be vastly beneficial to your cultivation, so don't miss this opportunity."

Everyone sat down with their legs crossed upon hearing this, preparing to begin cultivating.

Right at this moment, the chief of the Whiteback Ghost Ape suddenly asked, "Your Majesty, would it be possible for us to enter the other two gates? Surely the space beyond those two gates will be even more beneficial to our cultivation."

Everyone else also turned to Bai Ze with hopeful expressions upon hearing this, eagerly awaiting his response.

"The five bloodline heirs were only able to pass through the golden flames because they have the protection of the True Spirit King bloodlines, what makes you think you can do the same? If you're not afraid to die, then go ahead," Bai Ze said in an indifferent manner.

The chief of the Whiteback Ghost Ape Tribe shuddered slightly upon hearing this, then said in a sheepish manner, "My apologies, Your Majesty."

"Alright, just be content with cultivating here. Once the five bloodline heirs return, I'll reopen the Asura Blood Gate so all of you can leave," Bai Ze said.

Right as everyone was settling down to cultivate, an unexpected voice rang out.

"Senior Bai Ze, I would like to give it a try."

Everyone turned with stunned expressions to discovered that the one who had spoken was none other than the human that everyone detested.

"Shut your mouth, you insolent bastard!" the chief of the Qing Ape Tribe roared, and many of the other primordial beings present also began hurling abuse at Han Li.

Even Fox 3 and Lekima were shaking their heads with furrowed brows, clearly of the opinion that this was too bold a move from Han Li.

Han Li paid no heed to the dissenting voice as he cupped his fist in a salute and implored, "I would like to try and enter the second gate. Would that be possible, Senior Bai Ze?"

"Our primordial tribes are indebted to you, so of course you can give it a try if you like. However, I must caution you that this is no ordinary gate. In fact, the space beyond this gate played a vital role in allowing the eight of us to transcend above all of the other countless primordial beings to become True Spirit Kings.

“With your human body and your Giant Mountain Ape bloodline alone, you may not even be able to pass through the Holy Primordial Flame, let alone enter the gate. Do you still want to try?" Bai Ze said.

Not only was everyone stunned to hear this, even Han Li was beginning to doubt his own conviction. Was this really a good idea?

However, he quickly made up his mind, cupping his fist in a salute as he declared, "I still want to give it a try."

He was willing to take this risk partially because he was confident in his own bloodline, and also because he was intent on attaining more power as quickly as possible in order to maximize his chances of successfully rescuing Jin Tong.

"In that case, go ahead," Bai Ze acquiesced after a brief hesitation.

"Thank you, Senior Bai Ze," Han Li said with a grateful salute.

"Those of you who think that you'll also be able to pass through the Holy Primordial Flame to enter the gates, go ahead and try, but be warned that you'll be doing so at your own risk," Bai Ze declared, then departed from the crimson space through the Asura Blood Gate.

Everyone exchanged a few glances with one another, then turned collectively to Han Li, who took a deep breath, then rushed straight into the Holy Primordial Flame.

His intention was to make it directly to the second gate in one go, but in the instant that he rushed into the flames, his entire body was struck by an incredibly agonizing sense of scorching pain, and wisps of fire wrapped themselves around him to drag him down.

He tried to advance through the flames, but he was unable to make any progress, and it was as if the entirety of Eight Plains Mountain were weighing down upon him.

At the same time, it was as if the blood in his body had been set alight, pumping through his veins like a stampede of wild horses, and whenever it reached his heart, a loud thump akin to the beating of a giant drum would ring out.

The sound was so loud that not only could Han Li hear it, it was clearly audible even to the primordial beings outside.

He was urgently calling upon the Essence Fire Raven to come out and protect him, and the Essence Fire Raven was able to hear his call, but it was unable to emerge from his body, as if it had been sealed inside somehow.

"What an insolent fool! His Majesty already told him that it would be very difficult to endure the primordial flames without the protection of a powerful True Spirit King bloodline, yet he still insisted on rushing straight to his death," the chief of the Qing Ape Tribe said with a cold smile.

Most of the other primordial beings present were clearly also going to be far from distraught to see Han Li meet his demise here.

Lekima took a glance in Han Li's direction, then sat down with his legs crossed and began absorbing the immense bloodline power in the air.

Fox 3 shook his head and heaved a forlorn sigh, clearly of the opinion that Han Li had bitten off more than he could chew.

Han Li was completely oblivious to everyone's reactions. At the moment, all he could hear was deafening rumbling, and his entire body had been charred black, giving him the appearance of a tree that had been struck by a bolt of lightning.

Right at this moment, a burst of five-colored light appeared around him, and a Giant Mountain Ape projection flew out of his body, followed by a Lightning Bird, then a True Dragon, and before long, a total of ten true spirit projections had emerged one after another to orbit around him, releasing bursts of ancient and powerful auras.

Chapter 1185: Entering the Gate

"What's going on?"

"This is impossible!"

"How could a human possess such a wide array of true spirit bloodlines?" the chief of the Qing Ape Tribe exclaimed in an astonished manner.

The chief of the Mountain Moving Ape Tribe also raised an eyebrow in befuddlement as he mused, "Our primordial bloodlines make it very difficult for us to incorporate true spirit bloodlines into our bodies, yet humans have a unique advantage in their bloodlines won't clash with true spirit bloodlines, thereby presenting the possibility of the incorporation of true spirit bloodlines. Having said that, it's still inconceivable that his body hasn't fallen apart after taking in so many true spirit bloodlines."

Lekima had already entered a state of meditation, but he was roused by the commotion, and a look of amazement appeared in his eyes as he observed Han Li from afar.

......

Meanwhile, two of the eight stone chairs in the Holy Primordial Palace on Eight Plains Mountain had been filled.

Bai Ze was seated on his chair, while another nearby chair had been occupied by a black-robed man.

The man had a very imposing physique, but his clothes were tattered and riddled with holes, much like the attire of a beggar.

The man removed his hook to reveal an angular face with a gray stubble and a pair of slightly sunken eyes that glowed particularly brightly in the dimly lit palace.

The man was none other than the Sky Roaming Kun Peng, who had just returned.

"Welcome back, Yue Mian. I knew you wouldn’t have strayed too far away from the primordial land, but I didn't think you would get back so soon," Bai Ze said with a warm smile.

However, his warm demeanor was not reciprocated by Yue Mian, who said in a cold voice, "Cut the chit-chat. Why have you suddenly opened the Asura Blood Gate? Is our primordial land facing a crisis?"

Bai Ze was unbothered by Yue Mian's hostility, and he asked, "Are you aware that the Heavenly Court is about to hold the Bodhi Banquet?"

"What does that have to do with anything?" Yue Mian asked in a combative manner.

Bai Ze's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he said, "I know that you blame me for what happened all those years ago, but..."

"The Heavenly Court wanted to take Mo Yu by force for his abilities, but instead of allowing our primordial land to go to war with the Heavenly Court, you chose to stand by and watch 'for the greater good'. How did that work out? Not only was Mo Yu killed, Old man Yuan died with him as well, and we don't even know where their bodies are!

“Even if the Heavenly Court is up to no good again, our hearts are no longer together, so you can't expect us to work together like the old days," Yue Mian said with a cold smile.

"It wasn't my decision not to go to war with the Heavenly Court. Mo Yu had foreseen the outcome of such a decision, and he threatened me with his life, asking me not to intervene," Bai Ze said with a pained expression.

Yue Mian's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he knew that Bai Ze was telling the truth.

"Yuan Gang knew about this as well, but he still chose to go to Mo Yu's aid. For all these years, I've been constantly regretting my decision, but that won't amount to anything," Bai Ze sighed.

"Indeed, it's all in the past now," Yue Mian sighed as he stood up to leave.

"The Taowu and the Zhuyan have also perished, so you, me, and the Rahu are the only ones left," Bai Ze said, and Yue Mian was instantly rooted to the spot upon hearing this.

"The Asura Blood Gate has been reopened, and I've found suitable bloodline heirs to inherit the True Spirit King bloodlines, but they need time to grow," Bai Ze continued.

"So you summoned me and Rahu back here in case the Heavenly Court finds out what you're doing and decide to attack, is that right?" Yue Mian asked as he sat back down onto his chair.

"Our primordial land needs you," Bai Ze said in an earnest fashion.

"Truth be told, I've been constantly waiting for the day that I make my return to the primordial land. The day must come when the Heavenly Court is made to pay for their crimes," Yue Mian said as a cold aura of killing intent began emanating from his body.

"That day won't be too far away," Bai Ze mused.

Right at this moment, Yue Mian's brows suddenly furrowed slightly, as if he had detected something.

An intrigued look had appeared on Bai Ze's face as well, and he mused, "How intriguing. Now that you're back, let's take a look together."

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke to release a burst of golden flames, depicted within which was none other than Han Li with all of his true spirit projections revolving around him.

"How could a human possess so many true spirit bloodlines? Even mine and Old Man Yuan's bloodlines are in there!" Yue Mian exclaimed.

"Not only that, but he also asked me of the bloodlines of the Taowu and the Zhuyan not long ago," Bai Ze chuckled.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a pair of jade vials suddenly flew out of Han Li's body, then disintegrated to release two drops of blood essence, which seeped into his charred body as a cloud of blood mist.

With the infusion of these two true spirit bloodlines, Han Li's Twelve Awakening Transformations sprang into action on its own, and his body began to bulge and transform in an erratic fashion, phasing back and forth between a giant, ape-like creature and a five-colored tiger with a pair of wings on its back.

"He's going to self-detonate at this rate," Yue Mian remarked with slightly furrowed brows.

"That's precisely what's so remarkable about him," Bai Ze said, and as soon as his voice trailed off, all of the true spirit projections revolving around Han Li flew back into his body one after another.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li displayed all twelve true spirit transformations in rapid succession, and as he cycled through these different forms, his aura began to stabilize bit by bit, while his charred body also began to revert back to its original state, like a withered plant resurrected by the warmth of spring.

"How is he doing that?" Yue Mian asked with a stunned expression.

"It seems like he's mastered some type of cultivation art designed to allow the cultivator to refine true spirit bloodlines. It looks to me like he was only missing two bloodlines to complete his mastery of the cultivation art, and he's completed the full set now," Bai Ze speculated.

Yue Mian's brows furrowed slightly in apprehension upon hearing this.

Bai Ze could tell what his concerns were, and he smiled as he said, "Rest assured, he's no enemy of ours. Instead, he's going to be a real thorn in the Heavenly Court's side."

"Does that mean you intentionally allowed him to enter the Holy Primordial Palace so that he can refine his bloodlines and physical constitution?" Yue Mian asked.

"Not only that, but I also wanted everyone to personally witness his bloodline refinement cultivation art. As for how much they'll be able to get out of observing him, that'll be up to them," Bai Ze replied.

"I see. I think he has great potential, but I'm not optimistic about his chances. I don't think there's any chance that a human like him will be able to open that gate," Yue Mian said.

"I disagree. He asked for my permission to try and enter the second gate, and it wasn't a request made out of hubris. Instead, it was because his bloodline reacted to the second gate. Otherwise, given his personality, he wouldn't have made such a request," Bai Ze said, and a look of surprise appeared on Yue Mian's face upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly let loose a thunderous roar and transformed into a devilish deity with three heads and six arms, then trudged through the golden flames as he barreled toward the second gate.

Unlike the bloodline heirs, he was unable to crash his way through the gate. Instead, he was stopped cold in his tracks, and a resounding boom rang out from the impact of his body against the gate.

"It seems like the Holy Primordial Palace isn't going to accept him, after all," Yue Mian mused.

"Perhaps so," Bai Ze said as he swept a sleeve through the air to scatter the golden flames on the ground.

Inside the crimson space, all of the primordial beings were staring after Han Li with dumbstruck looks on their faces. What they had perceived to have been a suicide mission had unfolded in a direction completely contrary to their expectations.

However, it seemed that the farce had finally come to an end. There was no way that Han Li was going to be able to open the gate, and with that in mind, everyone hurriedly began focusing on their own cultivation.

"So close yet so far," Fox 3 murmured to himself in a wistful manner as he sat down with his legs crossed.

However, right at this moment, twelve true spirit projections flew out Han Li's body once again, and they fell upon the second gate one after another before fusing into it.

The rough lines on the gate instantly lit up, and a peculiar, primordial aura erupted out from within.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li let loose a thunderous roar as he crashed into the gate once again while pushing against it with his six enormous arms with all his might.

In a miraculous turn of events, the gate was pushed inward slightly to create a small opening, out of which a cloud of dense blood mist came gushing forth.

An ecstatic look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he instantly reverted back to his human form before rushing through the opening in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, the gate swung shut behind him with an almighty rumble.

"He... He did it..." the chief of the Qing Ape Tribe exclaimed, and his incredulity was mirrored on the faces of all of the other primordial beings around him.

Chapter 1186: Inheritance

While everyone else was looking on in astonishment, Lekima made a rapid string of hand seals before making a beckoning motion toward the second gate, and the crimson mist that had spilled out from within instantly came sweeping toward him.

Fox 3 immediately snapped back to his senses as well before hurriedly doing the same thing.

By the time everyone else realized what was happening, most of the crimson mist had already been claimed by the two of them, and the rest of the primordial beings were left to split what little remained in a dismayed fashion.

As soon as Fox 3 drew the crimson mist into his own body, his expression instantly changed drastically, and it seemed that he was in an immense amount of pain.

He channeled his bloodline power with all his might, doing everything in his power to stabilize his own internal condition, and only after a long while did everything return to normal at which point a look of alarm and concern appeared in his eyes as he thought to himself, It must be countless times more unbearable for Brother Han in there!

Lekima had taken in even more of the crimson mist than Fox 3, and even though he had fared much better, he was still astonished by the tremendous influx of violent power that had entered his body, and he was also beginning to fear for Han Li.

Meanwhile, Han Li was drifting unsteadily back and forth with the gusts of ferocious, crimson winds blowing through the space beyond the second gate.

It took quite some effort to stabilize himself, and he swept his gaze over his surroundings to discover that he was in a boundless, crimson space, with an extremely intense bloody odor permeating throughout.

Hanging above his head was an enormous, crimson sun that was radiating rays of crimson light in all directions, while down below was a series of massive, crimson vortexes that resembled almighty tornados, giving off bursts of chaotic and violent power.

Han Li was struck by a sense of familiarity upon sensing this power.

Back when he had suffered bloodline backlash in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, his bloodlines had clashed against each other with the same type of chaotic and destructive power as what was present in this space.

This was perhaps why his body had somehow felt a connection to this space, ultimately convincing him to venture through the second gate.

After some contemplation, Han Li cast these thoughts aside and sat down with his legs crossed, then channeled his Twelve Awakening Transformations and Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts in unison.

Twelve true spirit projections appeared in a circular formation behind him, then began revolving around his body.

Seemingly in response to this, the crimson vortexes down below instantly sped up drastically in their revolution, releasing corkscrew-shaped plumes of crimson mist that surged into the circle formed by the twelve true spirit projections.

All of a sudden, it was as if the twelve true spirit projections had sprung to life, and they began greedily devouring the crimson mist surging toward them.

Han Li felt a burning sensation in his back, as if molten lava had been injected into his body, and his blood was instantly set alight, causing him to let loose an involuntary roar.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of incredibly formidable bloodline power crashed its way into his body, inflicting bouts of indescribably intense agony upon him.

At the same time, his unopened profound acupoints began to loosen with this influx of power.

Han Li's eyes had turned bright red, but his complexion was deathly pale, and he was gritting his teeth with all his might as sweat poured down from his forehead, mixing together with the blood that was seeping out of the corners of his eyes.

......

Meanwhile, in the first crimson gate.

Even though Liu Le'er and the others had all entered through the same gate, each of them seemed to have been transported into an independent space, and none of them were able to see one another.

At this moment, Liu Le'er was situated on a massive, circular altar with nine enormous pillars around her, pillars that were etched with countless patterns that were giving off radiant, crimson light.

A gargantuan white fox was hovering high up in the air above her with its nine tails wrapped around the nine pillars, and rays of light were flowing down from its body and into the altar along the pillars.

At the center of the altar was a far smaller six-tailed white fox, which was laying flat against the ground with several crimson chains pierced through its body, rendering it completely immobile. Even so, it was still glowering intently up at the nine-tailed fox above with its teeth tightly clenched and its head held high.

The six-tailed fox was naturally none other than Liu Le'er, while the nine-tailed fox was a manifestation of the True Spirit King bloodline.

The latter possessed no sentience, yet Liu Le'er felt a type of strange bloodline connection between them, and this bloodline connection made the agony that she was being forced to endure not so unbearable.

As more and more bloodline power flowed into Liu Le'er's body through the altar, her aura began to gradually elevate, and a seventh tail began to appear beside the existing six.

......

Inside another space, there was no altar, but a giant mountain was suspended in mid-air.

The mountain was entirely crimson in color with a massive ape engraved upon it, and it was none other than the Giant Mountain Ape.

Beneath the mountain was Yuan Shanbai in his true form as a giant, white ape, and he was carrying the enormous mountain on his back as he trudged forward in a hunched over fashion.

The flesh on his shoulders had become mangled and bloody, while his fingers had also embedded themselves into the crimson mountain. It was as if his entire body had fused as one with the mountain, forcing him to trudge onward.

The bloodline power that Yuan Shanbai had to inherit was inside the crimson mountain, so he had to constantly trudge forward with it on his back without pause.

Only once the mountain had completely fused as one with his body would he have truly inherited the bloodline of the Giant Mountain Ape.

For the sake of his tribe and the primordial land, he had to persevere no matter what.

......

In another inky black space, there was no altar or mountain, only a winding stream that was flowing along peacefully.

A black-robed, middle-aged man and a white-robed child were seated next to each other on the bank of the creek, and both of them had their feet submerged in the creek with tranquil looks on their faces.

The black-robed man had a set of handsome facial features, the centerpiece of which was a golden mark that resembled a vertical eye on his glabella.

The child beside him was still quite childlike in appearance, but there was already some resemblance between the two, and it was clear that the child was going to grow into a very handsome young man himself.

"Xiao Bai is not a bad name," the man said with a warm smile.

"What's my real name, Father?" the child asked.

"You'll take after my surname of Mo, but I didn't get a chance to give you a name," the man replied in an apologetic manner, and the child was a little disappointed to hear this.

The man was none other than the Ink-Eyed Pixiu, Mo Yu, while the child was Xiao Bai in his human form.

"While I was traveling through the Immortal Realm, I fell in love with your mother, even though she was a human, and I hid my identity to be with her. Not long after we had you, we were attacked by Heavenly Court cultivators, and in order to ensure our safe return to the primordial land, your mother went to divert away a Dao Ancestor of the Heavenly Court... She never came back," Mo Yu sighed.

Xiao Bai was furious to hear this, and he asked, "Was my mother killed by the Heavenly Court because of me?"

"Your mother wasn't the only victim. Your Uncle Yuan Gang also came to our aid, and the two of us were evenly matched against three Heavenly Court Dao Ancestors. However, we were overwhelmed when Gu Huojin entered the fray," Mo Yu said with a hint of melancholy in his voice.

"What a dirty scoundrel! He must've attacked you after you were already exhausted from your battle against the other three Dao Ancestors!" Xiao Bai said in a furious manner.

"Gu Huojin's powers are unfathomable even among Dao Ancestors. Even if he hadn't taken advantage of the situation, Yuan Gang and I may not have been able to oppose him. Xiao Bai, you have to promise me not to seek revenge against him," Mo Yu implored in a serious manner.

Xiao Bai was naturally unwilling to make such a promise, but he could only nod in agreement to assuage his father's concerns.

"What happened after that, Father?"

"We had a battle for the ages, killing one of the three Heavenly Court Dao Ancestors and injuring another, so Gu Huojin was forced to intervene. Yuan Gang and I perished not long after his intervention, and I used all of my remaining power to seal most of my bloodline power in your body. I also sealed away all of your memories and also sealed your physical form so that you wouldn't be discovered," Mo Yu replied.

"No wonder I wasn't able to attain a human form before now," Xiao Bai mused with an enlightened expression.

"I had no choice but to do it. Having said that, it was quite nice to see you look the exact same as I remember even after all these years," Mo Yu said with a smile as he patted Xiao Bai on the head.

Jin Tong was also fond of patting Xiao Bai's head like this, but whenever she did this, he would always be struck by the urge to move his head away. However, it was a far more comforting experience coming from his father.

"Why was the Heavenly Court hunting us down?" Xiao Bai asked.

"They wanted to take advantage of our innate ability. Once we've opened our True Spirit Ink Eyes, we can see certain future trajectories that one's life is destined to take. In other words, we can predict the future, to an extent," Mo Yu explained.

Chapter 1187: Emergence

"Did the Heavenly Court want to use us to predict something?" Xiao Bai asked.

"Gu Huojin seemed to have gleaned some type of disturbance in the Heavenly Dao, and he wanted to use my power to help him see his own future. However, that would've gone against the natural order, so I refused to help him.

“On top of that, the Heavenly Court had always been an enemy of our primordial land, so I was never going to help him anyway. Once you awaken this ability, make sure to use it with caution as it incurs an extremely heavy price," Mo Yu explained.

"Why is it that only Uncle Yuan Gang came to your aid, Father? Uncle Bai Ze says that he was a close friend of yours as well, so why didn't he help you?" Xiao Bai asked.

"Don't blame him for his inaction, I was the one who forbade him from helping me. If all of the True Spirit Kings had been swept up into the conflict, then that would've sparked an all-out war between our primordial land and the Immortal Realm, resulting in destruction and loss of life of unimaginable magnitudes," Mo Yu sighed, and Xiao Bai fell silent again upon hearing this.

"I feel very blessed to have been able to tell you all of this myself. Xiao Bai is a fine name. You can call yourself Mo Xiaobai from now on," Mo Yu said with a warm smile.

......

Over a century flew by in a flash.

On the plaza in the Asura Blood Gate, the eight stone pillars were glowing far dimmer than before, while the bloodline power in the air had also become very faint.

Some figures were gathered in several small groups at the center of the plaza, speaking to one another in hushed tones.

The group with the most number of people was the Heavenly Fox beings, and they were joined by Yuan Shanbai and Mo Xiaobai, but Liu Zizai and Liu Haoran were nowhere to be seen.

As opposed to his former canine form, Xiaobai had turned into a handsome young boy with a golden mark on his glabella that resembled a closed vertical eye.

Yuan Shanbai's appearance had also undergone a drastic change. His ape-like features were no longer as pronounced as before, and his tusks had turned into a pair of canine teeth, giving him a rather adorable appearance.

Among the three of them, the physical change in Liu Le'er was most pronounced. She also had a golden mark on her glabella, but it was in the form of a flower petal, and her body had become even more lithe and graceful, giving off an alluring quality that made it difficult for one to look away.

Standing not far away from them were Qing Dian and the young master of the Zouwu Tribe, both of whom were looking far more physically imposing than before.

The sharp horn on Qing Dian's head had already vanished, giving him a much closer resemblance to the Zhuyan, while the young master of the Zouwu Tribe had adopted his human form, so the changes to his true form were unclear for now, but his aura had clearly become significantly more powerful than before.

After inheriting the True Spirit King bloodlines, their powers were going to be drastically enhanced over the course of the near future. On top of that, their future cultivation paths were going to become far smoother than before, allowing them to make far faster progress than their peers.

Lekima was also present, and he was standing by himself, leaning back against a stone pillar as he observed the three giant gates.

Why has he still not come out?

"The Asura Blood Gate is going to close soon. If you ask me, Han Li has most likely already perished in there," Qing Dian said with a wide smile.

"That's what he gets for his hubris and insolence!" the young master of the Zouwu Tribe chuckled with vengeful glee.

"Shut your mouths! He's not dead!" Xiaobai snapped in a furious manner.

"That's not up to us to decide. In one more hour, the three gates will disappear, and the Asura Blood Gate will also close. Once that happens, his fate will be sealed," Qing Dian chortled with undisguised elation.

"I'm actually a little sad about this," the young master of the Zouwu Tribe said, despite the clear smile on his face.

Having just inherited their True Spirit King bloodlines, he and Qing Dian's powers had been drastically elevated, and he was eager to take this opportunity to humiliate Han Li, but now that Han Li was dead, they had been robbed of the opportunity.

Xiaobai was even more furious to hear this, and he immediately began to approach the two, with Yuan Shanbai following along to back him up.

However, they were stopped by Liu Le'er, who remained calm and collected as she said, "Let them say what they want. Once Brother Rock comes out, they'll be forced to eat their words."

She was the only one present who had absolute confidence in Han Li's return.

Back in the Spirit Domain Realm, Han Li had given her an unrivaled sense of security, so she was always going to have unwavering belief in him from the bottom of her heart.

Liu Qing could only heave an internal sigh upon seeing this.

After everything that had taken place, his opinion on Han Li had completely changed. Of course, in his eyes, Han Li still couldn't compare with Liu Le'er, but he was willing to regard Han Li as a powerful ally of their Heavenly Fox Tribe.

Unfortunately, it seemed that he had chosen a path that had led to his demise.

Fox 3 remained silent this entire time, and his expression didn't betray any emotion, but internally, he was also feeling very concerned.

Time slowly passed by. It was only an hour, but it felt like an eternity, and as more and more time slipped away, Liu Le'er was praying that the remaining time would pass by even slower.

The golden flames in front of the three gates had already faded, but the gates remained shut.

"Are you still going to wait? He's dead for sure!" Qing Dian chortled.

"Let's go, there's no need to wait any longer," the young master of the Zouwu Tribe said as he turned to leave.

In his eyes, the fun was already over, as was the life of the human that he so detested.

However, in the instant that he turned away, a heavy groaning sound rang out from behind him, and the second gate was slowly pushed open.

The young master of the Zouwu Tribe stopped in his tracks, then turned back around to see an enormous figure emerge from the second gate amid a cloud of crimson mist that was giving off a vast primordial aura.

The figure was almost as tall as the gate itself, and its body crimson and black in color and covered in turtle-shell-shaped scales. It had six enormous arms that were holding the gate open and three huge heads on its head, namely those of the Zhuyan, the Taowu, and the Xuanwu.

The giant figure was naturally none other than Han Li, and he had already completely mastered the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, attaining all four devilish deity forms, and the bloodline aura emanating from his body was nothing short of terrifying.

In this instant, he seemed more like a primordial true spirit than all of the actual primordial true spirits present.

"Impossible..." Qing Dian murmured to himself in a stunned manner, while the young master of the Zouwu Tribe was already astonished beyond words.

Any thought of humiliating Han Li with his newfound power had already evaporated into thin air, and even Liu Qing couldn't help but exclaim, "Is he really still a human?"

Lekima remained silent, but he was just as dumbstruck as everyone else.

In contrast, Liu Le'er was ecstatic, and she immediately rushed toward Han Li, followed closely by Xiaobai and Yuan Shanbai.

Han Li quickly reverted back to his human form, and his entire body was glowing with dense clusters of profound acupoints that were giving off an astonishing bloodline aura.

"That has to be over a thousand profound acupoints!" Fox 3 exclaimed, and at this point, he was beginning to feel a little numb from all of the astonishment.

Only after close to twenty seconds had passed did the profound acupoints on Han Li's body fade away, following which his aura also receded.

He gently exhaled as he flipped a hand over to produce an azure robe before putting it on, and while making his way out of the second gate, he suddenly stopped in his tracks and cast his gaze toward the third gate.

As soon as his gaze fell upon it, the surrounding scene instantly changed drastically. He felt as if he could see another primordial world, and while there were no primordial beasts to be seen, he could sense an unprecedentedly pure primordial aura.

It was a true primordial aura, one that was completely unrestrained and unfettered by the laws of heaven and earth.

Before he had a chance to examine this world, a burst of terrifying tearing force abruptly erupted out from within, threatening to tear him to shreds.

Han Li instantly snapped back to his senses with a slight shudder, and cold sweat was already pouring down his forehead.

However, as he turned his gaze to everyone else, he discovered that no one seemed to have noticed anything, as if time had stood still for a moment just now.

Han Li didn't dare to look at the third gate any further, and he hurriedly made his way back to everyone.

"What took you so long?" Xiaobai complained.

"My apologies, I didn't mean to worry you," Han Li said with a wide smile.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the entire surrounding space began to tremble violently, and the three gates behind him sank down into the ground, following which the plaza also began to fade out of existence.

"Let's get out of here first," Han Li said as he grabbed onto Xiaobai and Liu Le'er before rushing toward the Asura Blood Gate.

Chapter 1188: Rejection

Several figures appeared on the summit of Eight Plains Mountain, while the Asura Blood Gate faded away after standing for over a century.

The dark red light barrier over the plaza on the mountain summit had also receded, and at the moment, the plaza was basked in the golden glow of the morning sun.

Han Li took a deep breath of fresh air as he cast his gaze toward the rising sun.

All of a sudden, a burst of spatial fluctuations emerged beside him, and he hurriedly turned just in time to witness the arrival of Bai Ze and Yue Mian.

"Congratulations, Fellow Daoist Han, I can see that you've made massive strides in your physical cultivation," Bai Ze said with a pleased expression, while Yue Mian was also observing him with keen interest.

Han Li was rather disconcerted by Yue Mian's intrusive gaze, and a stunned look flashed through his eyes upon sensing the man's aura, which was as vast as the sea and not inferior to Bai Ze's in the slightest.

Could he also be a Dao Ancestor? Now that I think about it, the summoning array of the Lightning Bird Tribe registered a very strong reaction earlier. Could it be that this man is the Sky Roaming Kun Peng?

Despite these thoughts running through his mind, Han Li remained calm and collected as he extended a salute toward Bai Ze and said, "Thank you for granting me this opportunity, Senior Bai Ze. Otherwise, I shudder to imagine how long it would've taken me to make these strides on my own."

"Don't mention it, it's just a trivial matter," Bai Ze replied with a faint smile.

"It may only be a trivial matter in your eyes, but it's a huge favor that I'll never forget. If you require my services for anything in the future, please feel free to tell me," Han Li said in a serious manner.

The opportunity that Bai Ze had bestowed upon him was no lesser a blessing in his eyes than the guidance that he had received from Patriarch Miro.

"In that case, I will state a request for you. If our primordial land ever comes under any crisis, I hope that you'll help us to the best of your abilities," Bai Ze said with a faint smile.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this. The primordial land now had two True Spirit Kings, and the bloodlines of all of the deceased True Spirit Kings had also been inherited. In addition to that, it also had a whole host of powerful Great Encompassment cultivators. How could he possibly hope to make a difference in a crisis that even the primordial land couldn't overcome on its own?

"If such a day does come, then I'll be sure to do my best to help, although I can't guarantee that I'll be of much help," Han Li replied in a solemn fashion.

Bai Ze nodded in response, then turned to Yue Mian as he introduced, "Fellow Daoist Han, this is another True Spirit King of our primordial land, the Sky Roaming Kun Peng, Yue Mian. He's very interested in you."

This came as no surprise to Han Li, who had already guessed Yue Mian's identity, and he cupped his fist in a salute toward him as he greeted, "Han Li pays his respects to Senior Yue Mian."

Everyone else had already noticed Yue Mian, but they had never met him before, and only after hearing Bai Ze's introduction did they step forward to offer respectful bows.

"Don't bother, I'm not a stickler for formalities like Bai Ze. Where did you get your bloodline refinement cultivation art from?" Yue Mian asked as he looked intently into Han Li's eyes.

Han Li was abruptly overcome by a sense of feebleness, and the truth almost involuntarily slipped out of his mouth as he replied, "I obtained it from the belongings left behind by a Kun Peng Tribe senior in a lower realm."

"You obtained the cultivation art from a lower realm?" Yue Mian asked with a surprised expression, then nodded and turned his gaze away from Han Li.

The feebleness in Han Li's body slowly faded away, and he was rather alarmed and chagrined by what Yue Mian had done, but he was also left feeling very powerless.

Even though he had made some significant strides of late, he was still completely vulnerable in the face of Dao Ancestors.

Then again, even the peak-Great Encompassment Stage Liu Tianhao had been no match for Bai Ze, so of course he stood no chance.

With that in mind, what little resentment had welled up in his heart immediately faded away.

"If you want to know something, then just be civilized and ask him! How could you just go and control him like that? It's incredibly rude! This is why us primordial beings have such a bad reputation," Bai Ze reprimanded with tightly furrowed brows.

Yue Mian's brows also furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he turned to Han Li with a rather awkward expression.

"It's fine. Senior Yue Mian is clearly a very straightforward person, and all he did was ask me a question," Han Li said with a smile.

"You hear that? Fellow Daoist Han isn't even complaining, so you should learn to not be so naggy," Yue Mian said with a pleased smile, and he was feeling a little fonder of Han Li for coming to his aid.

Bai Ze shook his head in a resigned manner and didn't say anything further.

"Fellow Daoist Han, you possess the Kun Peng bloodline, and I like your personality. Are you interested in serving as my Dao Ancestor Envoy?" Yue Mian asked with a smile.

"Dao Ancestor Envoy?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression, having never heard of this term before.

Most of the other primordial beings present displayed much the same reaction as Han Li, but the rest of them, such as Liu Qing, Qing Dian, and the young Master of the Zouwu Tribe, were all stunned to hear this, and they turned to Han Li with envious expressions.

"Fellow Daoist Han, you're still not at the Great Encompassment Stage yet, so there are many things about Dao Ancestors that you still don't know about. Dao Ancestors like Father and Senior Yue Mian spend all of their time in seclusion and very rarely show themselves to the public. If it wasn't for the unrest brewing the Immortal Realm, Father wouldn't have come out of seclusion.

“Hence, all Dao Ancestors will select some powerful cultivators who they deem to possess great potential to serve as their envoys, essentially acting as their representatives. There are immense benefits to be reaped from this. Firstly, you'll have a Dao Ancestor as a backer, so the vast majority of people will think twice about opposing you.

“On top of that, Dao Ancestors will often bestow upon their envoys powerful immortal treasures and abilities, as well as provide guidance in their cultivation. This is a rare opportunity that's not to be missed," Lekima communicated through voice transmission.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, but he didn't offer an immediate response as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he quickly extended a slight bow and said, "I'm very grateful that you think so highly of me, Senior Yue Mian, but I already have my hands full with various private matters that I must attend to, so I'm afraid I must turn down your kind offer."

He was harboring too many secrets, so he was very apprehensive about establishing close ties with people far more powerful than himself.

On top of that, he knew next to nothing about Yue Mian, so he was naturally not going to accept this offer.

Everyone who was aware of the gravity of Yue Mian's offer was stunned to hear this.

He must be insane to have passed up such an offer!

Qing Dian was both stunned and elated by Han Li's refusal, as was the young master of the Zouwu Tribe.

Yue Mian wasn't angered by Han Li's response. Instead, he merely nodded in response and turned his gaze elsewhere, much to Han Li's relief.

Bai Ze took a long glance at Han Li, then turned to everyone else as he said, "Alright, the blood inheritance ceremony is now over, so return to your respective settlements. The True Immortal Realm is going to enter an age of immense turmoil soon, so preparations must be made."

Everyone present gave a collective affirmative response before departing, including Qing Dian and the young master of the Zouwu Tribe, but not before each of them had taken a cold glance in Han Li's direction.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

It seemed that the two of them harbored very deep resentment toward him. At the moment, they were no match for Han Li, but having inherited True Spirit King bloodlines, there was a chance that they could become Dao Ancestors in the future.

Normally, he would've made sure to eliminate such enemies, but he naturally couldn't do that with both Bai Ze and Yue Mian present.

"Brother Rock, I've only just inherited the regal bloodline, and it's yet to completely fuse with my body, so I'll have to return to the Heavenly Fox Tribe and go into seclusion. It doesn't look like you'll be staying in the primordial land for long, so you have to make sure to come back to see me," Liu Le'er said as she turned to Han Li with tears welling up in her eyes.

"I promise I'll come to visit," Han Li replied with a smile as he patted her on the head, and a smile instantly broke through her tears as she returned to her fellow tribesmen.

Liu Qing, Fox 3, and the others also bade farewell to Han Li, following which all of the Heavenly Fox beings departed.

Before long, Han Li, Xiao Bai, Bai Ze, Yue Mian, and Lekima were the only ones left on the plaza.

"Senior Bai Ze, Senior Yue Mian, I'm very grateful for the warm hospitality that you've displayed, but I have some matters to take care of, so I must also depart," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute toward the two True Spirit Kings.

He had already been in the primordial land for over a century, and he had no idea how Jin Tong was doing or if the Reincarnation Palace had already made its move against the Nine Origins Temple, so he had to return to the immortal regions right away.

"Looks like this is where we part ways then, Fellow Daoist Han," Bai Ze replied with a nod, then turned to Xiaobai as he continued, "Xiaobai, even though you've reached the Great Encompassment Stage, the bloodline power in your body is yet to completely stabilize, so stay here and cultivate on Eight Plains Mountain."

"Thank you for your concern, Your Majesty, but I want to follow my master," Xiaobai replied with a shake of his head, and Bai Ze's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this.

"Xiaobai, I only accepted you as my spirit pet because I was unaware of your identity. Now that you've inherited a True Spirit King bloodline, there's no need to continue to refer to me as master. Just call me Fellow Daoist Han," Han Li hurriedly said.

Xiaobai could refer to him however he wanted in private, but he didn't want to irk the two Dao Ancestors present.

"What difference does it make? I'm used to calling you master, so I'll continue to stick with that," Xiaobai said.

Chapter 1189: Two Hundred Year Agreement

"Don't be so wilful, Xiaobai! You are currently the only Ink-Eyed Pixiu in existence, so we can't afford to have you taking such risks," Bai Ze scolded in a stern manner.

Xiaobai opened his mouth to object, but Bai Ze raised a hand to stop him.

"I know what you and Fellow Daoist Han are planning. I know far more about the Nine Origins Temple than you do, and it's an entity that possesses power beyond your imagination. You need to stay here on Eight Plains Mountain and focus on your cultivation. As for you, Fellow Daoist Han, I advise you not to take the risk, either. It could quite easily be the last decision that you ever make," Bai Ze said in a serious manner.

"Pardon me for being frank, Fellow Daoist Han, but among all of the powers allied to the Heavenly Court, the Nine Origins Temple easily ranks in the top five, so it's still far too powerful for you to oppose for now," Lekima chimed in.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Indeed, it would've been nothing short of a suicide mission for him and Xiaobai to try and rescue Jin Tong from the Nine Origins Temple on their own, and there was no way that he would've done something so irrational. If he were to die, then Jin Tong's fate would also be sealed.

However, with the Reincarnation Palace thrown into the mix, things were going to be completely different. However, this was a secret that was not his to divulge, so he chose to remain silent.

"I can cultivate wherever. Master has a spatial treasure that I can cultivate in, and I'm not afraid of any danger that may come my way," Xiaobai objected in a determined manner.

Bai Ze was very displeased to hear this, and he gave Han Li a subtle look.

"Senior Bai Ze is right, Xiaobai. It's far too risky for you to come with me, so I also think you should stay here," Han Li said.

Even though Xiaobai had reached the Great Encompassment Stage, it still made virtually no difference in the face of a superpower like the Nine Origins Temple. On top of that, there was a good chance that the Heavenly Court was already aware of what happened on Eight Plains Mountain. Given that Xiaobai had inherited the bloodline of the Ink-Eyed Pixiu, he was almost certainly going to have a huge target on his back.

Even more importantly, taking Xiaobai away would pit him against the primordial land, so it was better to leave him here.

"Back when Boss and I were surrounded by those Nine Origins Temple cultivators, she had a chance to escape, but she gave that opportunity to me. Otherwise, I would already be dead, so how can I cower in the primordial land with her in such grave danger? I understand your kind intentions, Your Majesty, but this is something that I must do.

“Otherwise, with this guilt weighing on my heart, there's no way I can ever make any progress in my cultivation base," Xiao Bai said with unmatched determination in his eyes, and Han Li fell silent upon hearing this.

Bai Ze was clearly still very reluctant to let Xiaobai go, but before he had a chance to say anything, Yue Mian chimed in with his opinion.

"Bai Ze, us primordial beings have always been true to ourselves. We must follow our own hearts. Xiaobai clearly already has his mind made up, so just let him go," Yue Mian said.

"What nonsense are you spouting now? Don't tell me you don't know how powerful the Nine Origins Temple is!" Bai Ze snapped.

"His heart isn't here, so even if you keep him here by force, it won't do him any good. This is something that must be done, and I can tell that Fellow Daoist Han is not a reckless individual, so I'm assuming he must already have a plan for rescuing his friend," Yue Mian said.

"I do indeed have a plan in mind, but it concerns some secrets that I cannot divulge. Having said that, you can rest assured that I won't do anything reckless," Han Li said.

"You see? Your concerns are unnecessary. If you're still worried, then you can just give Xiaobai a few protective treasures," Yue Mian said.

Bai Ze was silent for a moment, then finally acquiesced, "Fine, go if you must, but take these with you."

He flipped a hand over as he spoke, summoning an azure jade talisman, a golden talisman, and a white cloth pouch.

The jade talisman was around three inches wide and five inches in length with a peculiar, array-like design etched upon it.

Bursts of gentle, azure light were emanating from the array, circling around the talisman before fusing back into it in a never-ending cycle.

The golden talisman was roughly palm-sized, and it was riddled with countless spirit patterns that were giving off incredibly formidable law power fluctuations.

As for the cloth pouch, it was completely unremarkable in appearance, nor was it giving off any law power fluctuations.

"The azure talisman is called the Heaven Moving Talisman, and it's capable of concealing your aura and physical body to such an extent that even a late-Great Encompassment cultivator may not be able to see through it. Sealed within the golden talisman is an attack imbued with a third of my power.

“As for the cloth pouch, that was your father's bonded immortal treasure, and it's been with me this entire time. Now that you've inherited his bloodline, you can have it," Bai Ze explained.

"Thank you, Your Majesty," Xiao Bai said in a grateful manner as he hurriedly accepted the three treasures.

He stowed the two talismans away after just a brief inspection, focusing most of his attention on the white cloth pouch.

Han Li was also quite pleased to see this.

With these three treasures at their disposal, they had three more safety nets that they could fall back on.

Right at this moment, Bai Ze suddenly swept a sleeve through the air, and twelve bursts of white light shot out of his hand like lightning before vanishing into Xiaobai's body with unerring accuracy. Countless white runes surged out of the white light, forming twelve circular arrays around Xiaobai that flashed momentarily before slowly fading away.

Both Han Li and Xiaobai were quite alarmed to see this, but Bai Ze had acted far too quickly for them to react.

"Don't worry, I've only planted a teleportation array in Xiaobai's body. I can allow you to leave with Fellow Daoist Han, but you only have two hundred years, after which you must return to the primordial land no matter what. Otherwise, the teleportation array will forcibly teleport you back here," Bai Ze warned.

Xiaobai's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he turned to Han Li with a concerned expression.

Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly upon hearing this. Up to this point, he had received no information from the Reincarnation Palace on when the mission was to be carried out.

He wasn't placing his hopes on the Reincarnation Palace, but their intervention would certainly be a huge help to him.

I hope we can make it in time, Han Li thought to himself as he gave Xiaobai a reassuring nod.

"Alright, I'll definitely come back in two hundred years," Xiaobai vowed to Bai Ze, and the latter's expression eased slightly upon hearing this.

"Thank you for allowing Xiaobai to accompany me, Senior Bai Ze. Rest assured, no matter what happens, I will ensure Xiaobai's safety," Han Li promised.

"Alright, I'll leave Xiaobai in your capable hands then," Bai Ze said.

The four of them chatted for a while longer before Han Li bade farewell to the two True Spirit Kings, then summoned the Ink Dragon Flying Boat, which quickly vanished into the distance with him and Xiaobai onboard.

Following their departure, Bai Ze took a glance at Lekima, who took that as his cue to depart as well, leaving only the True Spirit Kings remaining on the plaza.

"Here," Yue Mian said as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a ball of crimson light, which contained twelve projections, and they were none other than the twelve true spirit bloodline projections in Han Li's body.

In addition to the twelve true spirit projections, the ball of crimson light also contained a passage of text that formed a cultivation art.

If Han Li had still been present, he would've been shocked to discover that the cultivation art was fundamentally almost identical to the Twelve Awakening Transformations, with only some minor differences here and there.

Bai Ze's eyes lit up as he reached out to catch the ball of crimson light.

"I was able to glean the bloodline circulation in Han Li's body through his Kun Peng bloodline, thereby allowing me to get a rough idea of the inner workings of this bloodline refinement cultivation art. It is indeed a very advanced cultivation art, I wonder why it appeared in a lower realm," Yue Mian mused.

"This is a very remarkable cultivation art for sure. There are also some bloodline fusion cultivation arts in our primordial tribes, but only for four or five types of true spirit bloodlines at most. Any more than that, and the cultivator's body will self-detonate from an excessive number of conflicting true spirit bloodlines.

“The calculation required to create a cultivation art that can balance twelve types of true spirit bloodlines is nothing short of incredible. With this cultivation art, all of the primordial tribes will be able to become a lot more powerful," Bai Ze said with a pleased nod.

"If you wanted the cultivation art, you could've just searched his soul or asked him to hand it over. Why go through all this trouble to obtain it through such a roundabout fashion?" Yue Mian asked in a disgruntled manner.

"It may sound ridiculous for me to say this, but he's not someone that we can afford to mess with," Bai Ze replied with a shake of his head.

"Oh? Who exactly is he?" Yue Mian asked in an intrigued manner.

Bai Ze took a glance at Yue Mian, then pulled out a black badge with a sinister beastly head engraved upon it.

"It's him?" Yue Mian exclaimed with a surprised expression.

Chapter 1190: Five Light Lightning Pond

The Ink Dragon Flying Boat quickly left Eight Plains Mountain and flew away in a certain direction.

Not long after leaving Eight Plains Mountain, Han Li summoned some puppets to operate the flying boat in his stead, then cast several concealment and protective restrictions upon the flying boat, following which he made his way into the cabin of the boat before entering the FLower Branch domain with Xiaobai.

Upon entering the domain, Han Li activated the Celestial Time Array and the Heavenly Wheel Sundial to accelerate the flow of time inside.

Xiaobai immediately sensed the change in the flow of time, and he said, "Something feels different in here. Did you do something with this place, Master?"

"Time flows around fifty times faster than it does outside. Find a place to cultivate," Han Li replied.

"That's incredible! Your mastery over the laws of time must've improved significantly since we last parted ways!" Xiaobai praised, then sat down with his legs crossed to cultivate.

Han Li also found a place to sit down, then put on a Reincarnation Palace to examine the advertisement he had released to purchase time law materials.

Unfortunately, even with the high price that he was offering, there were still no takers, and there were no messages from Wyrm 3, either.

A hint of agitation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he clenched his fist slightly, causing the space by his hand to quiver and warp.

With his increased physical prowess, even the slightest gesture was enough to have a physical impact on the space around him. On top of that, he had a multitude of trump cards up his sleeve, such as the Eon Divine Lamp and the Almighty Sword Array.

However, his power was limited by the fact that he was still only at the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage.

So long as the Great Encompassment Stage remained out of his grasp, his potential would remain capped.

All of a sudden, Han Li's gaze fell upon a message that had appeared in the trading interface, and a smile appeared on his face as he murmured to himself, "Finally, a glimmer of hope after so long. I suppose it can't hurt to give it a try."

After that, he stowed the mask away, then sat down with his legs crossed and continued cultivating the Almighty Sword Array, as well as his Mantra Domain and Reversal True Axis abilities.

......

On the northwestern border of the primordial land near the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, many of the primordial tribes in the area had been forced to evacuate due to the pressure exerted by the Heavenly Court, leaving only some unintelligent primordial beasts behind.

The beast cores, blood essence, bones, and other body parts of these primordial beasts were precious materials, so there were more and more cultivators drawn to the area on hunting trips.

Even though there were no longer any primordial tribes present, there were still many hazards in the area. In addition to all of the primordial beasts, there were also many naturally occurring perilous areas that could trap and kill even High Zenith and Great Encompassment cultivators.

There was an area in this region where the mountains and ground were all black in color, and there was also a blanket of dark clouds in the sky with thick bolts of lightning flashing through them. Occasionally, the lightning would strike down from above, and the deeper one ventured into the area, the more frequent the lightning strikes became.

In the deepest part of the area, lightning fell from the sky like a destructive waterfall, and it was as if the entire sky were falling.

The lightning here came in all types of different colors, and just the mere sight of them was enough to raise goosebumps on the skin of the beholder.

This lightning area was enormous, stretching as far as the eyes could see in all directions.

The area was called the Five Light Lightning Region, and it was a very renowned perilous area near the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region.

Occasionally, some cultivators could be seen near the Five Light Lightning Region, venturing into the area in search of treasures under the cover of all types of protective immortal treasures.

The Five Light Lightning Region was an extremely perilous place, but it was also home to a vast array of lightning-attribute materials.

The outskirts of the Five Light Lightning Region weren't all that dangerous, but the same couldn't be said for the area in the heart of the region. The lightning on the outskirts wasn't all that powerful, so as long as one remained vigilant and didn't encounter terrible luck, they generally wouldn't find themselves in any life-threatening danger.

Of course, it was a different story for those who did encounter bad luck.

Somewhere on the outskirts of the Five Light Lightning Area, three cultivators, consisting of two men and one woman, were standing together with their backs facing one another.

Circling around them were around a dozen purple snakes that were over a thousand feet in length. All of them were formed entirely by purple lightning, and thick arcs of lightning were erupting out of their mouths before intertwining to form a giant lightning net around the trio.

Among them was a late-Golden Immortal Stage gray-robed elderly man, and he was joined by a hideous man clad in a suit of black armor and a young woman in red, both of whom were at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage.

The immortal treasures that they were using were also quite powerful, but the attacks from these purple lightning snakes were extremely difficult to withstand.

If it weren't for the fact that they had cultivated a secret technique that allowed them to connect their immortal spiritual power together, their defenses would've already been breached long ago.

"Why are there so many lightning beasts so far out?" the armorclad man yelled in an agitated voice as he conjured up a flurry of staff projections with a thick purple staff to keep the oncoming attacks at bay.

In addition to the lightning in the Five Light Lightning Region, the lightning beasts that naturally arose here also posed a major threat.

The lightning beasts here were formed by the lightning essence in the Five Light Lightning Region, and all of them were extremely powerful, but they generally only resided deep in the region, only venturing into the outskirts on very rare occasions.

"Complaining isn't going to do us any good, Fellow Daoist Zhao. Celestial Maiden Miao, you still have more Meridian Fire Beads, right? Use them to break this lightning net so we can make one final attempt to break out of this encirclement. If we're stuck here any longer, all of us are going to die!" the gray-robed elderly man yelled in an urgent voice.

"I only have one Meridian Fire Bead left, and we've tried that before. The bead is able to break this lightning net and temporarily free us, but it's unable to harm these lightning snakes, and they're far faster than us, so we won't be able to get away anyway," the woman in red said in a hesitant manner.

"Not to worry, I have a spatial restriction talisman that can immobilize these lightning snakes for a short period of time. I didn't use it because we were still quite deep in the Five Light Lightning Region earlier, but now that we've reached the outskirts, all we need is to have the lightning snakes off our backs for a short while to allow us to escape," the gray-robed man explained.

"You should've told us that earlier, Fellow Daoist Sun!" the woman in red said in an ecstatic manner as she flipped a hand over to summon a fist-sized crimson bead.

The bead was riddled with dense, fiery patterns that were giving off intense fire law power fluctuations, and it was clear that the woman was getting ready to use it.

The armorclad man's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to say anything, the woman had already released the crimson bead, sending it flying toward the purple lightning net.

An earth-shattering boom as an enormous crimson sun that was over a hundred thousand feet in diameter rose up in the sky, sending huge waves of fire sweeping through the air in all directions.

The purple lightning net was instantly torn to shreds by the crimson sun, and the two of the nearby lightning snakes were also swept up by the spreading waves of crimson fire, but not only were they not startled into retreat, all of them pounced at the trio of cultivators instead.

The gray-robed elderly man flipped a hand over to produce a white talisman with a series of silver patterns engraved upon it, then opened his mouth to release a ball of globule of blood essence.

The blood essence vanished into the talisman in a flash, and it transformed into a ball of silver light that vanished into the nearby space.

Countless rays of silver light instantly emerged from the surrounding space in a radius of dozens of kilometers to bind the lightning snakes and render them immobile, but the same also applied to the armorclad man and the red-robed woman.

In contrast, the gray-robed elderly man was enshrouded in a layer of silver light that shielded him from the same immobilizing effects.

"Sun Chongshan, what is the meaning of this?!"

The armorclad man and the red-robed woman were naturally furious at this turn of events.

"Please forgive me, fellow daoists. This talisman of mine immobilizes all living beings in a nearby area upon activation, and I'm afraid there was nothing I could've done to prevent this," the gray-robed elderly man said in an apologetic manner, then cupped his fist in a parting salute before flying away as a streak of silver light.

The armorclad man and the red-robed woman were staring daggers after him, but they could only watch helplessly as he made his escape.

Meanwhile, the lightning snakes were roaring in fury while struggling with all their might, and the rays of restrictive silver light around them was beginning to give out.

The armorclad man and the red-robed man also began struggling vehemently upon seeing this, hoping to free themselves before the lightning snakes could.

However, the rays of silver light were extremely resilient, and neither of them had much immortal spiritual power, so their struggles proved to be completely futile.

In contrast, the lightning snakes were able to absorb the nearby lightning to bolster their powers, and it didn't take long before the rays of silver light around them were snapped one after another.

Looks of despair appeared on the faces of the armorclad man and the red-robed woman upon seeing this, but right at this moment, an earth-shattering boom suddenly rang out from deep in the lightning region, drowning out even the rumbling thunderclaps ringing out in the area.

Immediately thereafter, seventy-two streaks of golden swordlight appeared in the distance, traversing through the lightning like seventy-two roaming dragons.

Each streak of swordlight was giving off unrivaled sword intent and lightning law power fluctuations, and they were devouring all of the lightning in their path.

Even though the streaks of swordlight were still very far away from the pair of trapped cultivators, their immense sword intent and law power fluctuations were clearly detectable even from afar.

Chapter 1191: Sword Refinement

"Such formidable lightning law power fluctuations! Those have to be at least fifth tier immortal treasures! Could it be that some Great Encompassment Stage senior is refining their immortal treasures in the Five Light Lightning Region?" the armorclad man exclaimed.

The lightning snakes seemed to have been intimidated by the powerful aura emanating from the streaks of swordlight, and they had turned to peer deep into the lightning region with wary looks in their eyes.

The armorclad man and the red-robed woman exchanged a glance with each other, following which the two of them yelled with all their might, "Save us, Senior!"

Alerted by their cries for help, the lightning snakes began struggling against their restraints once again, and in the blink of an eye, all of the rays of silver light around them were snapped, following which they pounced at the pair of trapped cultivators, both of whom could only look on with expressions of despair.

However, right at this moment, a ray of golden light rose up into the heavens, then formed a giant, golden disc.

The seventy-two streaks of swordlight fused into the giant disc in a flash, following which the disc abruptly vanished, transforming into an enormous, golden lightning cloud that was thousands of kilometers in size with countless arcs of golden lightning flashing within it.

A chorus of harrowing howls rang out from within the golden lightning cloud, while countless spatial rifts appeared in the sky with radiant arcs of golden lightning springing out from within, presenting an awe-inspiring sight to behold.

A burst of tremendous devouring force erupted out of the golden lightning cloud in all directions, causing the surrounding space to tremble violently.

Everything within a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers were sent flying involuntarily toward the golden lightning cloud, and the lightning snakes and the two cultivators were no exception.

In the blink of an eye, the pair of cultivators were sucked into the lightning cloud, and they found themselves in a murky golden space that stretched as far as the eye could see in all directions.

Thick bolts of golden lightning were flashing rapidly through the air above the golden space, forming one lightning array after another, and powerful lightning deities could be seen high up in the heavens, giving off incredibly destructive lightning law power fluctuations.

As soon as the armorclad man and the red-robed woman were sucked into the lightning cloud, the rays of silver light around them instantly disintegrated, restoring their freedom, but the immense pressure emanating from the lightning up above made them feel as if they had an enormous mountain weighing down upon them, rendering them even more immobile than before.

The lightning snakes had also been immobilized nearby, and given their limited intelligence, they instinctively lashed out in retaliation, opening their mouths to release thick bolts of purple lightning to strike at the golden lightning above, but to no effect.

All of a sudden, around a dozen bolts of golden lightning came crashing down from above to strike the lightning snakes on their heads, which instantly exploded like overripe watermelons.

Arcs of golden lightning then spread over their headless bodies to tear them to shreds, reducing them to tiny arcs of golden lightning that were sucked into the golden lightning cloud, while armorclad man and the red-robed woman looked on with astonished expressions.

"This is Cardinal Heavenly Lightning, said to be the most destructive of the thirty-six heavenly lightnings!" the armorclad man exclaimed in a stunned manner.

He was also a cultivator of the laws of lightning, and he hailed from a powerful sect, so he was very knowledgeable when it came to lightning-attribute abilities, but he had no idea what this lightning space was.

An astonished look also appeared on the red-robed woman's face upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, a dull thump suddenly rang out overhead, and a majestic, golden, heavenly gate appeared within the golden lightning.

The gate was etched with countless golden lightning runes, giving it a very antiquated appearance.

A burst of suffocating pressure came crashing down from the heavenly gate, and it was over ten times more potent than the pressure released by the golden lightning.

The armorclad man and the red-robed woman both threw up a mouthful of blood as their complexions turned deathly pale, and they were on the verge of being crushed into mincemeat.

They had thought that they had encountered their savior, but it seemed like they had jumped out of the frying and into the fire instead.

Right at this moment, an azure-robed man appeared up above before making a hand seal, and the golden heavenly gate quickly faded away along with the surrounding golden space, exposing the three of them to the Five Light Lightning Region again.

The immense pressure on the armorclad man and the red-robed woman was instantly lifted, and they began gasping for air.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, and the golden lightning cloud also dissipated into seventy-two golden flying swords and an octagonal jade plate that began revolving around him.

With another sweep of his sleeve, a burst of green light emerged, sweeping up the flying swords and the jade plate before sucking them up his sleeve.

After that, Han Li flew over to the two cultivators, then asked, "Are you two cultivators of the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region?"

"That's right. My name is Zhao Sanlei, and I'm a disciple of the Divine Heavens Sect. This is Celestial Maiden Miao, an itinerant cultivator. Thank you for saving our lives, Senior. May I have the honor of knowing your name?" the armorclad man asked as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute, while the red-robed woman also extended a respectful curtsey toward Han Li.

"My surname is Shi, there's no need for you to know my name. Do either of you have a map of the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region?" Han Li asked.

It had taken Han Li over twenty years to reach the Five Light Lightning Region from Eight Plains Mountain, and during this time, he had been studying the Almighty Sword Array extensively in the Flower Branch domain.

The Almighty Sword Array was incredibly powerful, but his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were far inferior in power, resulting in a slight mismatch.

Hence, he had been ecstatic to stumble upon this Five Light Lightning Region, and he had immediately ventured deep into the region to use the lightning here to refine his flying swords.

Using several types of lightning secret techniques in the Five Lightning True Mantra in conjunction with the power of the Profound Heavenly Gourd, he was able to refine his seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords once again, elevating all of them to fifth tier immortal treasures.

Additionally, the lightning that they contained had also evolved into Cardinal Heavenly Lightning, which was certainly a very pleasant surprise.

"Yes, I have one here," Zhao Sanlei hurriedly said as he summoned a jade slip before handing it to Han Li, who inspected its contents with his spiritual sense before giving a pleased nod.

The map in the jade slip was quite detailed, with all of the major powers such as the Nine Origins Temple and the Hundred Creations Mountain clearly marked out.

"Are you planning to travel to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, Senior? I'm very familiar with the immortal region, so I can serve as your guide if you'd like," Zhao Sanlei offered with a hopeful expression.

"There's no need for that, this map will be sufficient to guide me. This is a very dangerous place, so I advise you not to linger here any longer," Han Li replied.

A hint of disappointment appeared on Zhao Sanlei's face upon hearing this.

His true objective was to invite Han Li to the Divine Heavens Sect.

The Divine Heavens Sect specialized in lightning techniques, so if he could convince Han Li to visit their sect, then that would undoubtedly be a major contribution. Unfortunately, it seemed that things weren't going to pan out as he had hoped.

"You're right, Senior, it was far too reckless of us to have ventured into this place. If you require my assistance with anything, feel free to come and find me in the Divine Heavens Sect at any time," Zhao Sanlei said as he extended a parting salute toward Han Li, then departed with the red-robed woman.

However, right as the two of them turned to depart, they were abruptly rooted to the spot with dazed looks in their eyes.

Han Li descended before the two of them, then tapped a finger against their glabellas, using a secret technique to examine their memories to ensure that they hadn't managed to identify him.

Even though he was currently in disguise, his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had already been exposed, and it was possible that someone who had seen his information in an Immortal Outlet could've been able to guess his identity through his swords. He wasn't far away from the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region at the moment, and he wasn't going to take any chances.

Rays of translucent light then seeped into the glabellas of the two cultivators from Han Li's fingertips, and close to an hour later, the two of them emerged from the Five Light Lightning Region.

"Where do we go now, Fellow Daoist Zhao? Do we go back to Golden Swallow City?" the red-robed woman asked.

"Of course! We can't just let Sun Chongshan get away with what he did to us! Thank heavens there just so happened to be a lightning tide that scared those lightning snakes away. Otherwise, we would already be dead by now!" Zhao Sanlei harrumphed coldly.

"You're right, we can't just let him off the hook," the red-robed woman agreed with a disgruntled expression.

With that, the two of them set off toward the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region as two streaks of light.

Only after the two had faded into the distance did Han Li emerge from the Five Light Lightning Region.

He had just altered their memories, erasing their encounter with him and replacing it with a false memory of a lightning tide that had startled the lightning snakes away, thereby saving their lives.

It would've been more convenient to just kill them, but that wasn't Han Li's style, so he would rather make the effort to avoid senseless slaughter.

On top of that, once he reached the Great Encompassment Stage, he would have to sever his three corpse souls, and engaging in senseless slaughter would've had some impact on his mental state.